@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Tetaplah/O bekerja/O keras/O walau/O dalam/O perasaan/O semalas/O apa/O pun/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@prabowo/O :/O @Wawan_karwantoo/O Mohon/O sampaikan/O salam/O saya/O kembali/O Sudah/O lama/O saya/O tidak/O ke/O Madiun/LOCATION Banyak/O orang/O dekat/O saya/O ,/O sahabat/O saya/O dari/O Madiun/LOCATION 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Katakanlah/O Aamiin/O atau/O Retweet/O ,/O jika/O doa/O senja/O ini/O adalah/O doa/O Anda/O juga/O https://t.co/qXAUR1q7zh/O 
@Info_Sumsel/O :/O BMKG/ORGANIZATION :/O Sumsel/LOCATION Berawan/O Dan/O Berpeluang/O Hujan/O Sedang/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Turut/O berduka/O Hari/O berkabung/O utk/O kita/O semua/O Semoga/O keluarga/O diberi/O ketabahan/O #AirAsia8501/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Choe/PERSON Song-Hyok/PERSON ,/O Komunis/O Pertama/O di/O Liga/O Italia/LOCATION https://t.co/OG3XRFSpUH/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Adik-adik/O yang/O saya/O sayangi/O ,/O pagi-pagi/O gini/O enaknya/O kita/O cool/O tweet/O tentang/O apa/O ya/O ?/O 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O #Info/O #Longsor/O debit/O sungai/O naik/O &/O gerus/O lereng/O balai/O RW/O 1/O Mulyorejo/LOCATION Skrg/O sdh/O diberi/O grs/O pembatas/O Masy/O agar/O hati2/O https://t.co/AkkuzBkXp5/O 
<47>/O Alhamdulillah/O hari/O ini/O saya/O dapat/O berbuka/O puasa/O bersama/O 0/O/O000/O anak/O yatim/O se-Jabodetabek/O https://t/O/Oco/QiqUYvwEZO 
@detikcom/O :/O Film/O Pendek/O Animasi/O '/O Kapur/O Ade/O '/O Raih/O Penghargaan/O Viddsee/O https://t.co/a5nUxwafUg/O via/O @detikHot/O 
@detikcom/O :/O '/O Kungfu/O Panda/O 3/O '/O (/O 3D/O )/O :/O Tetap/O Kocak/O dan/O Hangat/O ,/O dengan/O Aksi/O Lebih/O Banyak/O https://t.co/ku308bnvqT/O via/O @detikhot/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Alasan/O Wanita/O dan/O Anak/O Rentan/O Mengidap/O Infeksi/O Saluran/O Kemih/O https://t.co/lqo86DRDIt/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O Nuhun/O ,/O Bandung/LOCATION kota/O kembang/O lagi/O Insya/O Allah/O ,/O titip/O siram/O //O pemeliharaan/O ya/O pak/O Camat/O salam/O hormat/O https://t.co/8eJxmdxLuR/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O 3/O komplotan/O ini/O sdh/O sy/O ingatkan/O dgn/O lisan/O belasan/O kali/O 4/O Sdh/O dirazia/O Skogar/O berkali-kali/O ,/O krn/O ada/O oknum/O aparat/O jd/O beking/O skg/O play/O victim/O 
<67>https://t.co/dKegEmW1d4/O Mau/O Selfie/O Sama/O Ular/O Piton/O Eh/O Leher/O Pria/O Ini/O Malah/O Digigit/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Evakuasi/O Senja/O Utama/O Solo/LOCATION Masih/O Berlangsung/O ,/O 1/O Gerbong/O Belum/O Terangkat/O https://t.co/iu2DBKh3uP/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Turis/O Mancanegara/O di/O Belitung/LOCATION Merinding/O dan/O Puas/O dengan/O Penampakan/O Gerhana/O https://t.co/Gn93uyWtBg/O https://t.co/mT63T0ja0u/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Begini/O Cara/O India/LOCATION Salip/O Pertumbuhan/O Ekonomi/O China/LOCATION https://t.co/jsAFweo2cv/O via/O @detikfinance/O https://t.co/b0qTzIQ2by/O 
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O sibuk/O berkomentar/O yang/O tak/O dipahami/O dan/O tak/O perlu/O dikomentari/O 
@WindaaPutri1/O :/O RT/O @WOWFAKTA_KPOP/O :/O Munculnya/O foto/O masa/O kecil/O Seolhyun/PERSON membuatnya/O didaulat/O memiliki/O kecantikan/O murni/O dikalangan/O artis/O KPop/O #WOWfakta/O 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @bpbd_jatim/O :/O Info/O Gempa/O Mag/O :/O 3/O 3/O SR/O ,/O 27-Feb-16/O 09:44:18/O WIB/O ,/O dilaut/O ,/O 114/O km/O Selatan/O Kab/O Malang/LOCATION -/O JATIM/LOCATION ,/O Kedlmn/O :/O 10/O Km/O @BMKGTretes/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O para/O Pengurus/O DPC/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION se-Dapil/O 8/O dan/O Dapil/O 9/O Jawa/LOCATION Tengah/LOCATION Purwokerto/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O ,/O 16/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/k5EDo9zNfq/O 
@prabowo/O :/O RT/O @kutub_bumi/O :/O Tetaplah/O teriakkan/O kebenaran/O ,/O walaupun/O hanya/O sendiri/O https://t.co/auxVl9qSwI/O 
@Cholbang/O :/O Monitor/O Kerja/O Sama/O ,/O Wapres/O Swiss/LOCATION Kunjungi/O BMKG/ORGANIZATION 
@yogi_013/O :/O RT/O @_BangWahyu/O :/O Jika/O bertanya/O ,/O jangan/O mendiktekan/O jawabannya/O ,/O agar/O informasi/O baru/O bisa/O bertamu/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Perang/O Mulut/O Anas/PERSON dan/O Nazaruddin/PERSON di/O Pengadilan/O Tipikor/O https://t.co/CqcThNbl5Z/O 
<39>/O Pianis/O Cilik/O Fenomenal/O Joey/PERSON Alexander/PERSON Rilis/O Album/O Terbaru/O https://t.co/fMXsTeifIR/O 
<89>/O Sandiaga/PERSON Uno/PERSON Tak/O Takut/O Meski/O Ahok/PERSON Tidak/O Cuti/O https://t.co/Ho9KG7yh3f/O #KASKUSNews/O 
@infodishub/O :/O H/O +/O 2/O ,/O JUMLAH/O PENUMPANG/O ANGKUTAN/O LEBARAN/O SELURUH/O MODA/O RATA-RATA/O MENGALAMI/O PENURUNAN/O http://t.co/NpOPzoNTcr/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@nurria_riah/O :/O RT/O @Trenzcrackers/O :/O Trenzetter/O ,/O coba/O acak/O hurufnya/O dan/O klik/O !/O Ayo/O sebutin/O nama/O kota/O dengan/O awalan/O huruf/O yang/O kamu/O dapat/O :/O D/O 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @bpbd_jatim/O :/O #BMKG/O #PeringatanDini/O Cuaca/O Jatim/LOCATION 25/O Februari/O 2016/O ,/O Pkl/O 10.58/O WIB/O https://t.co/Viz2gfmf2H/O 
@detikcom/O :/O #MostPopular/O Gadis/O Pemanis/O Beraksi/O di/O Bangkok/LOCATION Motor/O Show/O 2016/O https://t.co/QMlotZoRyc/O via/O @detikOto/O https://t.co/vthhx0Ippa/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Ada/O waktu/O bagi/O segala/O sesuatu/O Ada/O waktu/O bagi/O rezeki/O ,/O dan/O ada/O waktu/O bagi/O cinta/O jika/O ingin/O disegerakan/O ,/O pantaskan/O diri/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<30>/O Ahli/O Kembali/O Yakinkan/O Mirna/PERSON Tewas/O Bukan/O Karena/O Sianida/O https://t/O/Oco/7FGizAXirk/O https://t/O/Oco/MHsag1ouJ9/O 
@aagym/O :/O Jauhi/O komentar/O ,/O celetak/O celetuk/O ,/O pertanyaan/O iseng/O yang/O dapat/O merusak/O suasana/O ,/O kebersamaan/O dan/O merusak/O kebahagiaan/O orang/O lain/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O RT/O @republikaonline/O :/O Bantah/O Tampar/O Sopir/O Angkot/O ,/O ini/O Kronologi/O Versi/O Ridwan/PERSON Kamil/PERSON https://t.co/MZuHIX5WPM/O 
@infodishub/O :/O LIMA/O MASKAPAI/O AJUKAN/O TAMBAHAN/O PENERBANGAN/O SELAMA/O ANGKUTAN/O LEBARAN/O http://t.co/q6O2enIAJI/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O suguhan/O sirih/O dari/O Tari/O Pasambahan/O Universitas/ORGANIZATION Negeri/ORGANIZATION Padang/ORGANIZATION Padang/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O 9/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/yUJ3XETvSM/O 
<34>/O 7/O Superfood/O Untuk/O Turunkan/O Kolesterol/O https://t/O/Oco/aceBzkwEpy/O https://t/O/Oco/sBkhV4prU3/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Caballero/PERSON Berharap/O Hart/PERSON Lekas/O Pulih/O https://t.co/rpuqK4aJHY/O https://t.co/rh6H9MCi7B/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Adakah/O peningkatan/O kualitas/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION FC/ORGANIZATION bersama/O manajer/O baru/O ?/O https://t.co/76Jge9IXg5/O 
<32>/O 700/O Jemaah/O Haji/O Indonesia/LOCATION akan/O Dipulangkan/O Melalui/O Filipina/LOCATION https://t/O/Oco/xTv2rT3tl2/O https://t/O/Oco/Yx3AHjh6RW/O 
@Indri_Adler/O :/O Buku/O favorit/O banyak/O ,/O haahahaha/O Tp/O Harry/PERSON Potter/PERSON yg/O favorit/O dr/O jaman/O sekolah/O dulu/O https://t.co/mV380MnYEr/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Dukacita/O mendalam/O atas/O gugurnya/O 13/O prajurit/O TNI/ORGANIZATION dalam/O jatuhnya/O helikopter/O TNI/ORGANIZATION AD/ORGANIZATION HA/O 5171/O di/O Poso/LOCATION Mereka/O gugur/O jalankan/O tugas/O negara/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@aainaa_namr/O :/O RT/O @FoodPornMlaysia/O :/O Nama/O artis/O boleh/O retweet/O takkan/O nama/O yang/O indah/O ini/O tak/O boleh/O ?/O http://t.co/ZBbihBpoaV/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Dipanggil/O Kejati/ORGANIZATION ,/O La/PERSON Nyalla/PERSON Ancam/O Bakal/O Mangkir/O Lagi/O https://t.co/CO4tziaYL4/O 
@PustakaJustitia/O :/O RT/O @klinikhukum/O :/O Kajati/O DKI/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION dan/O Aspidsus/O Diduga/O Terkait/O Suap/O PT/ORGANIZATION Brantas/ORGANIZATION Abipraya/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/FPCePcgFDk/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Dari/ Buffon/PERSON untuk/O yang/O Senantiasa/O Dipunggunginya/O ,/O dengan/O Cinta/O https://t.co/4r3g435OBk/O https://t.co/xLx0Bwx3Yx/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Mendampingi/O salah/O satu/O anak/O yang/O mengikuti/O sunatan/O massal/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION Madura/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/MVWBvzQdv7/O 
<52>/O Chris/PERSON Brown/PERSON Kembali/O Disorot/O Netizen/O https://t/O/Oco/6YslcrTIaY/O https://t/O/Oco/ujOsfRGKA4/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Selamat/O sore/O ,/O masih/O tetap/O semangat/O dan/O selalu/O berusaha/O #Laruno/O https://t.co/j0yQKHV7jc/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Ahok/PERSON Pusing/O Soal/O Pilgub/O DKI/LOCATION ,/O Pilih/O Fokus/O Garap/O APBD/O 2017/O https://t.co/CYqfXKzlRM/O https://t.co/OnvPHXcrKJ/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Om/O Mario/PERSON ini/O ternyata/O lucu/O juga/O ya/O ?/O -/O Ya/O ,/O terkadang/O saya/O harus/O agak/O lucu/O ,/O supaya/O tidak/O terlihat/O terlalu/O bijak/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selamat/O hari/O lahir/O Pancasila/O Jaya/O selalu/O bersama/O seluruh/O bangsa/O Indonesia/LOCATION yang/O kita/O cintai/O ini/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Teman/O Ahok/PERSON gelar/O gerai-gerai/O pengumpulan/O KTP/O utk/O dukung/O Ahok/PERSON #KompasSiang/O pkl/O 11/O 00/O WIB/O 
@KepoanNabilah/O :/O Sejatinya/O seorang/O wanita/O tidak/O menuntut/O banyak/O kecuali/O sebuah/O pengertian/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Cara/O Pasang/O 2/O SIM/O Card/O dan/O 1/O Kartu/O Micro/O SD/O di/O Samsung/ORGANIZATION Galaxy/O S7/O Edge/O https://t.co/3SuYewkJBY/O https://t.co/Bbpr02sTar/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Saat/O Ahok/PERSON Membandingkan/O Gaji/O Pengemudi/O TransJ/O Lebih/O Besar/O dari/O Sopir/O Taksi/O https://t.co/p1o6fhky5o/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Polres/ORGANIZATION Jepara/LOCATION akan/O Tindak/O Tegas/O Angkutan/O Berpelat/O Hitam/O https://t.co/V30rItmykG/O 
@prabowo/O :/O "/O Cintai/O rakyat/O kamu/O ,/O dan/O gunakan/O akal/O sehat/O dalam/O memimpin/O Jangan/O khianati/O cinta/O itu/O Biarkan/O kecintaan/O kamu/O menuntun/O kamu/O "/O -/O Ben/PERSON Mboi/PERSON 
@kwektions/O :/O #JokopediaID/O "/O @arbib/O JAKARTA/LOCATION -/O Pimpinan/O Pusat/O (/O PP/O )/O Muhammadiyah/ORGANIZATION telah/O menggelar/O pertemuan/O https://t.co/rQI1Imke4d/O 
@ThiwiPrathiwi/O :/O Menyesal/O jg/O menolak/O kerja/O di/O perusahaan/O yg/O lbh/O baik/O karena/O jarak/O yg/O jauh/O dan/O bertahan/O di/O tmpt/O yg/O msh/O satu/O kota/O smg/O kesabaran/O berbuah/O manis/O 
@siwaedu/O :/O Cigna/ORGANIZATION Hadirkan/O Family/O Proteksi/O Optima/O 
@bqkhyun10/O :/O Informasi/O saja/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Menerima/O @Yusrilihza_Mhd/O yg/O akan/O meluncurkan/O buku/O Ensiklopedia/O dlm/O rangka/O Ultah/O ke-60/O https://t.co/4Id31Dij5c/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Membanggakan/O !/O Fransiska/PERSON Dimitri/PERSON Inkiriwang/PERSON &/O Mathilda/PERSON Dwi/PERSON Lestari/PERSON dari/O Unpar/ORGANIZATION bisa/O menaklukkan/O Aconcagua/LOCATION ,/O puncak/O tertinggi/O benua/O Amerika/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Amerika/LOCATION Godok/O RUU/O untuk/O Menghukum/O Apple/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/ihp8X2adw0/O 
@adilanisa311/O :/O HARGA/O EMAS/O 6/O APRIL/O 
@ayu_yuliarizka/O :/O RT/O @mujiaries/O :/O Jangan/O lewatkan/O ya/O HajiBelajarNgaji/O mulai/O Senin/O 4/O April/O Pindah/O Jam/O Tayang/O 21.00/O WIB/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Mitos/O https://t.co/sMO9cH7akT/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Tepung/O sagu/O secara/O ekonomi/O sangat/O potensial/O Ekosistem/O gambut/O dan/O pesisir/O cocok/O ditanami/O sagu/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/YDKNKrcuJ8/O 
@parhan_1928/O :/O RT/O @KicauanAldo/O :/O Jakarta/LOCATION tetap/O menjadi/O kota/O para/O pemenang/O ,/O anak/O metropolitan/O tidak/O kampungan/O spt/O mereka/O ,/O kita/O melawan/O dgn/O cara/O yg/O elegan/O 
@revolusisosmed/O :/O RT/O @AYA_S0F1A/O :/O RIP/O Komisi/O Pelindung/O Koruptor/O @KPK_RI/O Bekerja/O cc/O @LBH_Jakarta/O @RatnaSpaet/O @AndiArief_AA/O 
<61>Kamu/O generasi/O 90-an,/O pasti/O ingat/O dong/O dengan/O lagu-lagu/O ini./O Nostalgia/O yuk!>>/O https://t.co/HkxwCyin0w/O https://t.co/1LDpLEuQj7 
@RadjaMention/O :/O Penghasilan/O Rp/O 4,5/O Juta/O per/O Bulan/O Kini/O tak/O Kena/O Pajak/O 
<88>/O Budi/PERSON Gunawan/PERSON Kini/O Berpangkat/O Jenderal/O ,/O Ini/O Reaksi/O Tito/PERSON Karnavian/PERSON https://t.co/eAHkYIzNnU/O #KASKUSNews/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O RT/O @KotaJaksel/O :/O JKT/LOCATION Baru/O tdk/O sekedar/O slogan/O ,/O JKT/LOCATION Bersih/O nyata/O adanya/O @KotaJaksel/O cc/O @slankdotcom/O @basuki_btp/O 
@eyda_chan/O :/O gmbr/O sekolah/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O "/O Persatuan/O &/O Kesatuan/O ,/O kedamaian/O ,/O keadilan/O &/O Krisis/O lingkungan/O di/O dunia/O juga/O memerlukan/O perhatian/O "/O #SalatigaMeeting/O https://t.co/nIcX4yOwbm/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Dokter/O Penghina/O Pemkot/O Semarang/LOCATION via/O Medsos/O Shock/O ,/O Tak/O Jawab/O soal/O Motif/O https://t.co/Ngt95vRiBs/O 
@infodishub/O :/O WAMENHUB/O :/O PASTIKAN/O KAPAL/O ANGKUTAN/O LEBARAN/O LAIK/O LAUT/O http://t.co/TeTcExoF1C/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Turki/LOCATION -/O Yunani/LOCATION Tandatangani/O Kesepakatan/O Kerja/O Sama/O Migran/O https://t.co/MtEyY4UBrC/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Gue/O jg/O punya/O band/O FILIPINA/LOCATION favorit/O !/O Band/O ini/O namanya/O Freestyle/O ,/O semi/O jazz/O gitu/O ,/O ini/O lagu/O mereka/O yg/O paling/O gue/O suka/O :/O https://t.co/ZxoWxyX9yj/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Netizen/O yg/O beri/O pendapat/O relatif/O lengkap/O :/O 2/O 614/O Setelah/O ditelaah/O ,/O 70/O %/O tak/O setuju/O revisi/O UU/O KPK/ORGANIZATION ;/O 12/O %/O setuju/O &/O 18/O %/O lain/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Berdialog/O tentang/O perkembangan/O UMKM/O binaan/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Kenjeran/LOCATION Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/HE2j8O8GyJ/O 
@aagym/O :/O Masya/O Alloh/O Senangnya/O membaca/O anjuran/O Kapolda/O Sumsel/LOCATION ini/O ,/O ,/O semoga/O jadi/O inspirasi/O bagi/O para/O pemimpin/O lainnya/O ya/O https://t.co/AdkrvKSdLy/O 
@muhmaulawarman/O :/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION Pastikan/O Penyesuaian/O Harga/O di/O SPBU/LOCATION 
<77>/O PDIP/ORGANIZATION :/O Kenapa/O Sih/O Komisi/O II/O Ngotot/O Ingin/O Terpidana/O Maju/O Pilkada?/O https://t.co/TNO5PSAPsp/O #KASKUSNews/O 
@indgrnproperty/O :/O Anda/O menginginkan/O informasi/O tentang/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Tapi/O entah/O kenapa/O ya/O ,/O semaleman/O denger2in/O lagu2/O pop/O Myanmar/LOCATION kayak/O lg/O denger/O lagu2/O Indonesia/LOCATION tahun/O 90/O 'an/O Mirip2/O gmn/O gitu/O 
<51>/O Aji/PERSON Santoso/PERSON Targetkan/O Bawa/O Persela/ORGANIZATION ke/O Papan/O Tengah/O https://t/O/Oco/LyxZ7x551F/O 
<66>https://t.co/HRHdtUYBKZ/O Idola/O Mahmud,/O Kubu/O Ahok/PERSON :/O Gubernur/O Jakarta/LOCATION Tak/O Cukup/O Modal/O Ganteng/O 
<91>https://t.co/mNflYgUh0w/O Ephy/PERSON Sekuriti/O Rela/O Syuting/O Bareng/O Monyet/O Untuk/O 'HUMOR/O BAPER'/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Jangan/O sepelekan/O 1/O Rupiah/O ,/O karena/O 1/O miliar/O Rupiah/O tidak/O jadi/O 1/O miliar/O tanpa/O 1/O Rupiah/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<7>/O RT/O @tvOneNews:/O Malam/O Penganugerahan/O PAB/O XIV/O Tahun/O 016/O ,/O Malam/O Ini/O ,/O Minggu/O 8/O Agustus/O 016/O Pukul/O 9/O/O00/O Wib/O ,/O Jangan/O Lewatkan/O https://t/O/Oco/JdWÖ 
@kicauaceh/O :/O Orang/O Tak/O Rela/O Pungutan/O Pajak/O Tinggi/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Selaku/O Ketua/O Dewan/O Pembina/O PB/O Muaythai/O meninjau/O Pelatnas/O atlet/O Muaythai/O di/O GBK/LOCATION Senayan/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O Selasa/O 8/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/OdIwcIRx7F/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Demo/O Tolak/O Uber/ORGANIZATION ,/O Pengusaha/O Rental/O Bakal/O Temui/O Dishub/ORGANIZATION DKI/LOCATION https://t.co/vYidO0CxXK/O 
@dyananurh/O :/O Gedung/LOCATION 4/LOCATION ,/O Fakultas/O Ekonomi/O UNS/ORGANIZATION 
@radityadika/O :/O Meeting/O produksi/O film/O Koala/O Kumal/O Kangen/O juga/O jd/O sutradara/O lagi/O :/O '/O )/O https://t.co/eZK1rkVV5P/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Rame/O ing/O gawe/O ,/O sepi/O ing/O pamrih/O Pendekar/O sejati/O berbuat/O untuk/O orang/O banyak/O ,/O untuk/O negara/O ,/O tidak/O untuk/O diri/O sendiri/O http://t.co/wlq2qnGG1Y/O 
<35>https://t.co/6lCavQ8J8r/O Indah/PERSON Permatasari/PERSON Tak/O Mau/O Gabung/O Teman/O Yang/O Ajak/O Main/O Hingga/O Pagi/O 
<82>/O Chelsea/ORGANIZATION Gagal/O Pertahankan/O Tren/O Kemenangan/O https://t/O/Oco/YvUplhm5zp/O 
@akbar_felayati/O :/O RT/O @OdiSumantri/O :/O agen/O LPG/O NPSO/O (/O non-subsidi/O )/O 
@bukanisti/O :/O Zaskia/PERSON Sungkar/PERSON ,/O Shiren/PERSON Sungkar/PERSON 
<48>https://t.co/lcEZHlH8TC/O Sudah/O 8/O Tahun/O ÔøΩÔøΩ/O Masih/O Single,/O Kiki/PERSON CJR/ORGANIZATION Tak/O Takut/O Dicap/O Gay/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Koruptor/O memang/O kelihatannya/O banyak/O uang/O ,/O tapi/O itu/O jenis/O uang/O yang/O jumlahnya/O juga/O menentukan/O ukuran/O siksa/O dunia/O dan/O akhiratnya/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@detiksport/O :/O Sempat/O Tertinggal/O di/O Babak/O Pertama/O ,/O Napoli/ORGANIZATION Kalahkan/O Genoa/ORGANIZATION 3-1/O https://t.co/g5Ozmd58tM/O https://t.co/zQVuINTQIi/O 
@barcbels/O :/O RT/O @EGC_Seulgi/O :/O Rumah/O ?/O Rumah/O masa/O depan/O kita/O ?/O Uwuwuwuwu/O https://t.co/5LjJgUp8mM/O 
@aagym/O :/O Waspada/O beli/O sendal/O atau/O sepatu/O ,/O ada/O yg/O dengan/O niat/O buruk/O membuat/O produk/O menggunakan/O lafadz/O Alloh/O ,/O naudzubillah/O http://t.co/pyLbyDwJX4/O 
<62>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O Surga/O Cantik/O Itu/O Terlihat/O Jelas/O dari/O Puncak/LOCATION Pulau/LOCATION Padar/LOCATION https://t.co/G1esIYuu5p/O https://t.co/YYBOGYcAMV/O 
@berita_gresik/O :/O Reklamasi/O Pantai/O Kian/O Sulitkan/O Nelayan/O di/O Gresik/LOCATION 
@CitaSehat/O :/O ICD/O DANDANGAN/O BINAAN/O CSF-RZ/O LOLOS/O MEWAKILI/O KEDIRI/LOCATION TINGKAT/O PROVINSI/O DALAM/O LOMBA/O PELAKSANA/O GOTONG/O ROYONG/O TERBAIK/O https://t.co/Aj1JnT9oGX/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Adalah/O komitmen/O KMP/ORGANIZATION untuk/O terus/O bermitra/O kritis/O dengan/O pemerintah/O KMP/ORGANIZATION akan/O terus/O memberi/O saran/O demi/O kebaikan/O #1TahunKMP/O 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @PuspitaFM/O :/O #JMR/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION trpilih/O sbagai/O role/O model/O pnyelenggaraan/O playanan/O publik/O khususnya/O terkait/O PTSP/O cc/O :/O @pemkotmalang/O 
@mahasiswaub_/O :/O @andalus911/O Radio/O @andalus911/O mengucapkan/O ,/O Dirgahayu/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION ke-102/O Makin/O jaya/O https://t.co/vK5U1AcY9h/O 
@campinatour/O :/O Hal/O lucu/O apa/O yang/O sudah/O ,/O Sahabat/O Campina/ORGANIZATION lakukan/O bersama/O kerabat/O //O keluarga/O hari/O ini/O ?/O 
<16>/O 9/O Tanda/O Anda/O dan/O Pasangan/O Ditakdirkan/O Bersama/O Selamanya/O https://t.co/O k0H7KFdT5/O https://t.co/1z67nfQnjA/O 
<83>/O iPhone/O 7/O Kurang/O Diminati?/O https://t/O/Oco/XLeo4a0JUS/O https://t/O/Oco/ZfDbS2lR9A/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Kebetulan/O https://t.co/BTSz9PXkoK/O 
<92>/O Sebelum/O meninggalkan/O Nagrek/LOCATION ,/O Ibu/O Ani/LOCATION diberi/O bekal/O bala-bala/O panas/O dr/O Ibu/O Cucu/O penjual/O makanan/O #SBYTourDeJava/O https://t.co/XK4ZgmTUB8 
@pinkyzhoui/O :/O Biarkan/O oppa/O menjadi/O tulang/O punggung/O keluarga/O kecil/O kita/O kelak/O 
@nendrabertus/O :/O RT/O @didadidu/O :/O @RBerbagi_Ilmu/O mereka/O adl/O org2/O hebat/O penggerak/O pendidikan/O di/O Kab./O ROTE/LOCATION NDAO/LOCATION ,/O yang/O sangat/O saya/O kagumi/O adalah/O ketulusan/O hati/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O Kabupaten/O Bandung/LOCATION mhn/O dibiasakan/O menulis/O dengan/O lengkap/O agar/O tdk/O salah/O kaprah/O hatur/O nuhun/O https://t.co/da0Z38LnLN/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Singapura/LOCATION Masih/O Jadi/O Kota/O dengan/O Biaya/O Hidup/O Termahal/O di/O Dunia/O https://t.co/CQB2vOicza/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Semoga/O malam/O ini/O tim/O Thomas/O Indonesia/LOCATION dapat/O memberikan/O yang/O terbaik/O melawan/O tim/O Malaysia/LOCATION Semangat/O !/O 
@Chenny_Owan/O :/O Karawang/LOCATION pastikan/O tarif/O angkutan/O umum/O turun/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Djan/PERSON Faridz/PERSON Usung/O Lulung/PERSON Jadi/O Cagub/O DKI/LOCATION dari/O PPP/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/zwhhVgu3Dj/O 
@Tanya_Udin/O :/O Cinta/O itu/O simpel/O ,/O tidak/O pernah/O menuntut/O !/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Gol/O memang/O tidak/O terjadi/O atas/O backpass/O berbahaya/O tersebut/O Tapi/O itu/O membuat/O Hart/PERSON mengalami/O cedera/O saat/O menyapu/O bola/O dari/O kejaran/O Martial/PERSON 
@inmalangraya/O :/O Kocak/O !/O Jelang/O Final/O Piala/O Bhayangkara/O 2016/O ,/O Wali/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION dan/O Bandung/LOCATION Sepakat/O Taruhan/O https://t.co/5n2eiR8rn2/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Di/O Mukomuko/LOCATION -/O Bengkulu/LOCATION ,/O #GMT9Mar16/O teramati/O antara/O pukul/O 06/O :/O 21/O WIB/O (/O saat/O Matahari/O terbit/O di/O Mukomuko/LOCATION )/O hingga/O pukul/O 08/O :/O 27/O :/O 08/O ,/O 7/O WIB/O 
@infodishub/O :/O MENHUB/O BUKA/O PENYELENGGARAAN/O RA/O V/O -/O 16/O http://t.co/AAUlb9HGgD/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Berkat/O doa/O semua/O temen2/O di/O Korea/LOCATION https://t.co/KEYqJVSNCT/O 
@aagym/O :/O Insyaa/O Alloh/O Ahad/O besok/O di/O TV/O kajian/O nikmatnya/O bertauhid/O dalam/O hidup/O ini/O https://t.co/ZFMNOuhEsZ/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Bangganya/O Van/PERSON Gaal/PERSON dengan/O Kemenangan/O MU/ORGANIZATION di/O Derby/O https://t.co/5Zn1OX3YSf/O https://t.co/OsdqvByHg3/O 
<88>/O 4/O Tips/O Mudah/O Hilangkan/O Stres/O dan/O Malas/O Saat/O Bekerja/O https://t.co/V43RDtNYer/O https://t.co/VbpGdMPegc/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Menerima/O @RHaryantoracing/O yg/O meminta/O restu/O dan/O dukungan/O untuk/O berlaga/O di/O ajang/O F1/O Video/O ;/O @husainabdullah1/O https://t.co/nzfszxZDRv/O 
@infodishub/O :/O 4/O 937/O PESERTA/O MUDIK/O GRATIS/O DIBERANGKATKAN/O DENGAN/O BUS/O http://t.co/6EEmu4f9Uv/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Titik/O kelima/O di/O jalur/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O adalah/O Balikpapan/LOCATION ,/O Kalimantan/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION Tepatnya/O di/O Lapangan/LOCATION Helipad/LOCATION Pertamina/ORGANIZATION Balikpapan/LOCATION 
@aagym/O :/O Ayoo/O berani/O jujur/O berapa/O banyak/O waktu/O yang/O digunakan/O untuk/O masing/O masing/O ?/O Mana/O yang/O bakal/O jadi/O bekal/O pulang/O https://t.co/myA4QalSL0/O 
@BeritaCrime/O :/O Penggeledahan/O Kejati/O DKI/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION Selesai/O ,/O Penyidik/O KPK/ORGANIZATION Belum/O Keluar/O https://t.co/Xm9RfnrdIu/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O rata2/O warga/O miskin/O pny/O agunan/O berharga/O BPR/O Bdg/LOCATION visinya/O spt/O grameen/O bank/O Stlh/O 8/O bulan/O ,/O NPL/O =/O O/O tdk/O ada/O yg/O ngemplang/O https://t.co/KnXjsquqBD/O 
@OBe21551655/O :/O RT/O @Sagita__clara/O :/O Avail/O JAKARTA/LOCATION EXPO/O :/O Jogja/LOCATION 12-14/O APRIL/O WA/O :/O 081322467006/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O Pataka/O kepada/O perwakilan/O DPC-DPC/O Kab/O Sumedang/LOCATION ,/O Kab/O Bandung/LOCATION dan/O Kota/O Bandung/LOCATION Rabu/O 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/vCppqR5qc3/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Mancini/PERSON Tetap/O Optimistis/O dengan/O Inter/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/907GszaLlq/O 
<81>/O Demi/O Konsumen/O ,/O Samsung/O Bisa/O Matikan/O Galaxy/O Note/O 7/O dari/O Jarak/O Jauh/O https://t/O/Oco/1UR3jH1QwB/O https://t/O/Oco/aPyRwQRpgz/O 
<73>/O Penyesalan/O Terbesar/O Inzaghi/PERSON terkait/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON https://t/O/Oco/X0QTWDsk8B/O 
<48>/O [Populer]/O Bocoran/O Sementara/O Spesifikasi/O Samsung/ORGANIZATION Galaxy/O A3/O 017/O https://t/O/Oco/zYWpDQYYyM/O https://t/O/Oco/PRWmk7I29V/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PT/ORGANIZATION KAI/ORGANIZATION DIMINTA/O BANGUN/O FASILITAS/O PETIKEMAS/O di/O SEJUMLAH/O STASIUN/O http://t.co/uObGKXpo1k/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@adrianazman/O :/O RT/O @emmaazmann/O :/O Bila/O kau/O bangun/O dari/O tidur/O kau/O tengok/O semua/O orang/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Harapan/O Alex/PERSON Usman/PERSON atas/O Vonis/O Hakim/O Hari/O Ini/O https://t.co/BajjXoFyxu/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Didampingi/O Menkopolhukam/O ,/O bertemu/O dg/O Tokoh/O Agama/O ,/O Tokoh/O Ormas/O //O Masyarakat/O membahas/O ttg/O radikalisme/O Di/O Rudin/O Wapres/O https://t.co/lpvbbulnDZ/O 
<74>/O Persela/ORGANIZATION Akhirnya/O Dapatkan/O Pengganti/O Sutan/PERSON Harhara/PERSON https://t/O/Oco/XWxrgGFopw/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Bersama/O Koalisi/O Merah/O Putih/O ,/O kami/O berkomitmen/O untuk/O berjuang/O agar/O setiap/O rakyat/O Indonesia/LOCATION dapat/O hidup/O sejahtera/O Mohon/O doa/O dan/O dukungannya/O 
@noelNDL/O :/O RT/O @joeyakarta/O :/O Haryadi/PERSON ro/O Imam/PERSON ki/O meh/O ngapa/O e/O ?/O Mimpin/O #Jogja/O berdua/O bareng/O sj/O gagal/O Apa/O meneh/O malah/O mau/O maju/O dewe2/O Mung/O bakal/O saya/O 
@aagym/O :/O Ayoo/O ada/O yang/O mau/O ikutan/O belajar/O olah/O raga/O Sunnah/O berkuda/O memanah/O di/O Daarussunnah/LOCATION ecopsantren/LOCATION Dt/LOCATION Bandung/LOCATION https://t.co/IoGFZJMUQ3/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O mas/O @ganjarpranowo/O ,/O mohon/O maaf/O liverpool/ORGANIZATION menang/O 
<47>https://t.co/Y7sXyXsr30/O Bukti/O Hantu,/O Foto/O Ini/O Rekam/O Penampakan/O di/O Rumah/LOCATION Angker/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Tottenham/ORGANIZATION Hotspur/ORGANIZATION Kalahkan/O Bournemouth/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/HEMS4q1jE2/O https://t.co/FdYscp6fPm/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Jaga/O Kulit/O Cantik/O Anda/O dengan/O Kombinasi/O Susu/O Bubuk/O https://t.co/mvNq9jIqR3/O 
<31>/O Jalan/O Pintas/O Pemulihan/O Warga/O Negara/O Arcandra/LOCATION Tahar/O https://t.co/kcPK43VqlM/O #KASKUSNews/O 
<29>/O Efek/O Samping/O Obat/O Statin/O terhadap/O Tubuh/O https://t/O/Oco/0FoSzJytlT/O https://t/O/Oco/AABTnsIGzj/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O GMT/O yg/O bs/O dilihat/O 375/O thn/O sekali/O di/O titik/O yg/O sm/O di/O Bumi/LOCATION terjadi/O kemarin/O Baca/O #GMT2016/O @hariankompas/O hari/O ini/O https://t.co/EtIbhHg6NO/O 
@chandra1998991/O :/O Fokus/O (/O Fahrub/PERSON Mie/O Jogja/LOCATION "/O Lestari/O "/O ,/O Langsa/LOCATION )/O https://t.co/6zVrjYPInY/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Jatuh/O itu/O biasa/O ,/O tapi/O jangan/O lama/O berbaring/O di/O situ/O Masih/O banyak/O yang/O bisa/O kita/O lakukan/O untuk/O memperbaiki/O keadaan/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@ulfarizkiaa/O :/O RT/O @SCTV_/O :/O Yuk/O nonton/O penampilan/O @fstvlst/O pkl/O 19.00/O WIB/O di/O #ToraCinoCoolExpression/O Yuk/O langsung/O datang/O ke/O kampus/O UMY/ORGANIZATION ,/O Jogja/LOCATION 
@undoyy/O :/O Doh/O gatot/O ngemas/O rumah/O 
<31>/O Hadang/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O PAN/ORGANIZATION Ajukan/O Rizal/PERSON Ramli/PERSON https://t.co/9bXhMuNmdP/O #KASKUSNews/O 
<57>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O TUI/ORGANIZATION Travel/ORGANIZATION PLC/ORGANIZATION Pun/O Bersemangat/O Memasarkan/O Wonderful/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/Rg6oDSqnAq/O https://t.co/k0Ai3AKXfq/O 
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @TaMeritaMerita/O :/O @infomalang/O min/O info/O dong/O yg/O bisa/O bikin/O desain2/O bwt/O pameran/O indoor/O seperti/O gapuranya/O dll/O 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O #Himbauan/O Salurkan/O sedekah/O pd/O saluran&tmpt/O yg/O tepat/O Jgn/O di/O jalanan/O Slain/O ganggu/O ktertiban/O ,/O jg/O rawan/O penyalahgunaan/O https://t.co/fQtrVxViFV/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O Sekarang/O bayar/O parkir/O meter/O sudah/O bisa/O menggunakan/O uang/O elektronik/O (/O e-money/O )/O dari/O 6/O bank/ORGANIZATION Dimulai/O di/O jln/LOCATION sabang/LOCATION http://t.co/xQqSbRhy8O/O 
<71>/O Daftar/O 07/O Jemaah/O Haji/O Indonesia/LOCATION Wafat/O di/O Arab/LOCATION Saudi/LOCATION https://t.co/2z2M8LllRa/O 
@JurnalAkuntansi/O :/O mengapa/O bukti-bukti/O yang/O diperoleh/O secara/O eksternal/O lebih/O dapat/O diandalkan/O 
<40>Tulis/O Artikel/O Cara/O Mengatasi/O Anyang-Anyang/O dan/O Dapatkan/O Uang/O Jutaan/O Rupiah/O https://t.co/JKFxEEwA2X 
@Yta_Surentu/O :/O Karawang/LOCATION pastikan/O tarif/O angkutan/O umum/O turun/O 
@amarilis_ayu/O :/O Mahathir/PERSON Mohamad/PERSON Mundur/O dari/O Posisinya/O di/O PT/ORGANIZATION Proton/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/oEz5x1sCne/O https://t.co/UpG3MEs9py/O 
<42>https://t.co/SJr8DFNsYY/O Deddy/PERSON Corbuzier/PERSON Undang/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON Untuk/O Bicara/O Sebagai/O 'Pria'/O 
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O ikut/O ikutan/O tiup/O terompet/O ,/O selain/O tak/O jadi/O amal/O juga/O bekas/O ditiup/O pembuatnya/O ,/O pedagangnya/O dll/O ,/O tidak/O terjamin/O kebersihannya/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Saya/O mengucapkan/O terima/O kasih/O setinggi-tingginya/O kepada/O seluruh/O jajaran/O pengurus/O ,/O kader/O ,/O simpatisan/O yang/O berkorban/O membesarkan/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION 
<48>/O ARB/PERSON ;/O Kehidupan/O Berbangsa/O Tak/O Sesuai/O Pancasila/O https://t/O/Oco/hRsV9PAhEV 
@HancelGoruDolu/O :/O RT/O @Indonesia1_co/O :/O BRG/O Akan/O Restorasi/O 834/O Ribu/O Hektar/O Lahan/O Gambut/O di/O 4/O Kabupaten/O https://t.co/yyWTjOayVU/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PEMBERLAKUAN/O ERP/O di/O JAKARTA/LOCATION PALING/O LAMBAT/O AKHIR/O 2015/O http://t.co/y1jj2R9apd/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersilaturahmi/O dengan/O Bupati/O Bandung/LOCATION Bpk/O Dadang/PERSON M/PERSON Naser/PERSON di/O Rumah/LOCATION Dinas/LOCATION Bupati/LOCATION Bandung/LOCATION Kab/O Bandung/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/12ozUlrrMR/O 
@mrik280/O :/O info/O @Zaskia_69/O avail/O wajib/O DP/O JKT/LOCATION https://t.co/Gn974Ma6uO/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Bocah/O Keterbelakangan/O Mental/O Berusia/O 11/O Tahun/O Diikat/O Orangtuanya/O https://t.co/opZAxZuqS1/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Ketua/O DPD/ORGANIZATION Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION Kota/O Bandung/LOCATION Bpk/O Muhammad/PERSON Ferrari/PERSON Nurrachadian/PERSON https://t.co/g5HAVrsGAb/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Pertahankan/O kualitas/O &/O tingkatkan/O estetika/O Agar/O dapat/O bersaing/O dlm/O Masyarakat/O Ekonomi/O Asean/LOCATION (/O MEA/ORGANIZATION )/O #SBYTourDeJava/O https://t.co/e02mSMDXfX/O 
@aagym/O :/O Mohon/O doa/O ,/O tugas/O dakwah/O di/O Qatar/LOCATION semoga/O diberkahi/O Alloh/O yaa/O ,/O nuhuuun/O ,/O sobat/O di/O Qatar/LOCATION sampai/O jumpa/O nanti/O sore/O https://t.co/LhSDr2QST3/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @PDemokrat/O :/O Jangan/O Paksa/O Bangun/O Infrastruktur/O Saat/O Ekonomi/O Sulit/O https://t.co/8eIPOCU0V1/O @SBYudhoyono/O @hincapandjaitan/O @FPD_DPR/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Tidak/O ada/O orang/O yang/O mempercayai/O ramalan/O nasib/O yang/O damai/O hidupnya/O ,/O walau/O pun/O untuk/O sementara/O waktu/O mungkin/O kaya/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@detikcom/O :/O Menderita/O Leukemia/O Diduga/O Jadi/O Penyebab/O Suwito/PERSON Gantung/O Diri/O https://t.co/DrFqU2HPUj/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Mendengarkan/O harapan/O &/O aspirasi/O rakyat/O ,/O Jika/O pemerintah/O baik/O kita/O dukung/O ,/O namun/O jika/O kurang/O tepat/O kita/O kritisi/O #SBYTourDeJava/O 
@threefmaceh/O :/O Bupati/O Bireuen/LOCATION Gotong/O Royong/O Bersama/O Bersihkan/O Waduk/O https://t.co/snb1eW6hBo/O 
@schubratta/O :/O RT/O @LBH_Jakarta/O :/O salah/O satu/O permasalahannya/O :/O kewenangan/O reklamasi/O ada/O di/O menteri/O bukan/O di/O gubernur/O DKI/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION sesuai/O dg/O Perpres/O no/O 122/O 
@nnnabilaa/O :/O RT/O @IzzatIzzmyJasme/O :/O sekolah/O aku/O tak/O boleh/O terima/O 
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @rofiqteub/O :/O @infomalang/O min/O ,/O mohon/O info/O toko/O jual/O printer/O epson/ORGANIZATION yang/O paling/O murah/O dimana/O ?/O Tks/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Tulisan/O netizen/O penting/O dalam/O menumbuhkan/O optimisme/O ,/O kejujuran/O dan/O etos/O kerja/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
<53>/O Kemenangan/O di/O Kiev/LOCATION ,/O Kado/O Ulang/O Tahun/O Sang/O Istri/O https://t/O/Oco/AAXwY3dvAm/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Bersama/O Presiden/O @Jokowi/O ,/O SBY/PERSON menghadiri/O peresmian/O gedung/O baru/O KPK/ORGANIZATION di/O Jakarta/LOCATION Dukungan/O kpd/O KPK/ORGANIZATION sangat/O diperlukan/O 
<35>/O Berbincang/O bersama/O @prabowo/O (Ketua/O umum/O GERINDRA/ORGANIZATION )/O ,/O @ZUL_Hasan/O (Ketua/O umum/O PAN)/O ,/O dan/O @msi_sohibuliman/O (Presiden/O PKS/ORGANIZATION )/O https://t/O/Oco/vwy7lJHnJx 
@prabowo/O :/O Jangan/O kita/O jadi/O partai/O besar/O tapi/O berisi/O maling-maling/O Lebih/O baik/O kecil/O tapi/O bersih/O dari/O maling-maling/O Bersih/O dari/O para/O komprador/O 
@firdaus1019771/O :/O 7/O GAMBAR/O -/O LAWATAN/O MENGEJUT/O LEONARDO/PERSON DICAPRIO/PERSON KE/O ACEH/LOCATION https://t.co/q575eFLARb/O 
@detiksport/O :/O '/O 15/O City/ORGANIZATION menekan/O Tendangan/O mendatar/O Navas/PERSON dari/O dalam/O kotak/O penalti/O dihalau/O De/PERSON Gea/PERSON menggunakan/O kakinya/O 
@Rudiyanto_8/O :/O Sektor/O hulu/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION terdiri/O dari/O kegiatan/O eksplorasi/O ,/O pengembangan/O dan/O produksi/O minyak/O dan/O gas/O 
<72>/O Gadis/O 6/O Tahun/O Asal/O Sidoarjo/LOCATION Ini/O Miliki/O Berat/O Badan/O 25/O Kg/O https://t/O/Oco/O Q1pkZ2nEN/O https://t/O/Oco/gvwHamnnzH/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O RT/O @brunuxs/O :/O @PRFMnews/O mobil/O ini/O buang/O sampah/O sembarangan/O di/O depan/O pom/O bensin/O dago/LOCATION ,/O yg/O buang/O ibu2/O meni/O murudul/O @ridwankamil/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Komentar/O Jay/PERSON Subiyakto/PERSON soal/O Musisi/O Jadi/O Politikus/O https://t.co/IUy0QlYt37/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Titik/O ketiga/O di/O jalur/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O adalah/O Tanjung/LOCATION Pandan/LOCATION ,/O Kepulauan/LOCATION Bangka/LOCATION Belitung/LOCATION Tepatnya/O di/O lokasi/O wisata/O Tanjung/LOCATION Kelayang/LOCATION 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Bom/O Brussels/LOCATION ,/O Uber/ORGANIZATION dan/O Google/ORGANIZATION Gratiskan/O Layanan/O https://t.co/HRPqlVRzpT/O 
@wasman05/O :/O RT/O @cutmeichy/O :/O madridista/O Jogja/LOCATION proudly/O present/O #madridistajogja/O #ketemuyuuk/O #halamadrid/O https://t.co/YSQymnSTv1/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Saya/O memberikan/O kuliah/O umum/O lbh/O dari/O 100/O universitas/O Saya/O ingin/O bangkitkan/O semangat/O generasi/O muda/O bangun/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/G22AcMs7Cy/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Indonesia/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION Kian/O Populer/O bagi/O Warga/O Australia/LOCATION https://t.co/PxebPWOCZI/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Jangan/O bosan/O belajar/O cara/O //O teknik/O bertani/O baru/O Di/O Taman/O Teknologi/O Pertanian/O Pacitan/LOCATION bisa/O hasilkan/O komoditas/O unggulan/O https://t.co/wLFzhNnsyZ/O 
<54>/O Nostalgia/O Game/O Contra/O Yuk!/O Masuk/O Sini/O Gan!/O https://t.co/4lHv20WZpM/O #ForumKaskus/O 
@KalimayaBaskara/O :/O Apa/O sih/O menurut/O kamu/O hal/O yg/O cuman/O ada/O di/O kota/O Malang/LOCATION dan/O bikin/O kangen/O ketika/O pergi/O ke/O kota/O lain/O ?/O Ada/O hadiah/O menarik/O loh/O buat/O yg/O gabungan/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 22/O :/O 28/O ,/O 5/O WIB/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Banda/LOCATION Aceh/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O 1/O Korporasi/O yg/O sdh/O meraup/O untung/O dr/O hsl/O hutan/O Indonesia/LOCATION ,/O jng/O hnya/O menyimpan/O uang/O keuntungannya/O di/O Singapura/LOCATION ,/O https://t.co/CQiDprMGPZ/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Sampai/O di/O Lombok/LOCATION ,/O langsung/O rebahan/O di/O hotelnya/O https://t.co/Uw6T1mAM35/O 
<36>/O Misteri/O sungai/O berwarna/O merah/O seperti/O darah/O terpecahkan/O #Global/O https://t.co/RDQm3WGdbk/O https://t.co/ZfQyHyAXi6/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Listrik/O tenaga/O surya/O terbesar/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION di/O Kupang/LOCATION Kita/O pakai/O energi/O baru/O &/O terbarukan/O yang/O ramah/O lingkungan/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/XWhPNc2szx/O 
<34>/O Kepada/O seluruh/O kader/O @Golkar5/O di/O DPP/O ,/O DPD/O serta/O simpatisan/O yg/O merayakan/O ,/O dalam/O kesempatan/O berbahagia/O ini/O saya/O ucapkan/O Selamat/O HR/O Idul/O Fitri/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Les/ORGANIZATION Bleus/ORGANIZATION Ditunggu/O Laga/O Emosional/O di/O Stade/LOCATION de/LOCATION France/LOCATION https://t.co/sz6vV950U5/O 
@Johor_Post/O :/O Gotong-royong/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Selamat/O datang/O PM/O Hongaria/LOCATION Yang/O Mulia/O Viktor/PERSON Orban/PERSON di/O negeri/O kepulauan/O Indonesia/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@COD_Surabaya/O :/O Kalung/O Aura/PERSON kebanggaan/O para/O artis/O SMS/WA/O :/O 081330511338/O -/O PIN/O :/O 2C0A20E4/O https://t.co/1tL699vFsW/O #Surabaya/O 
@rujak_mie/O :/O Mukti/PERSON Sulaiman/PERSON :/O Lulusan/O Stisipol/ORGANIZATION Harus/O Mampu/O Bersaing/O :/O Palembang/LOCATION ,/O Lulusan/O dari/O Sekolah/O Tinggi/O Ilmu/O Sosial/O https://t.co/te4dtm5QT8/O 
<33>/O RT/O @Golkar5:/O Ketua/O Dewan/O Pembina/O ,/O Ketua/O Umum/O ,/O Wakil/O Ketua/O Dewan/O Kehormatan/O beserta/O pengurus/O serta/O warga/O shalat/O Ied/O berjamaah/O https://t/O/Oco/nÖ 
@s_wibisono/O :/O @PTPERTAMINA/O tulisan/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @pakdekarwo1950/O :/O Saya/O jelaskan/O jembatan/O ini/O dibangun/O Tahun/O 1988/O dan/O masih/O bisa/O bertahan/O minimal/O 50/O tahun/O Secara/O teknis/O tidak/O ada/O masalah/O 
@aagym/O :/O Alhamdulillah/O di/O AirPort/O narita/LOCATION Jepang/LOCATION ada/O Musholla/LOCATION yang/O bersih/O dan/O nyaman/O di/O lantai/O kedatangan/O https://t.co/VDTt1IgFMq/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Semua/O tahu/O kemerdekaan/O pers/O penting/O Kontrol/O pers/O thdp/O kekuasaan/O penting/O Bukan/O sebaliknya/O pers/O dikontrol/O kekuasaan/O */O SBY/PERSON */O 
<42>/O [Populer]/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON :/O Pogba/PERSON akan/O Segera/O Bungkam/O Kritik!/O https://t/O/Oco/O 85d6IXrYk/O https://t/O/Oco/AdSobUvjIK/O 
<12>/O Selamat/O untuk/O Tontowi/PERSON dan/O Liliyana/PERSON Terima/O kasih/O untuk/O kado/O emasnya/O di/O HUT/O #RI71/O #ina/O #gold/O #badminton/O #Rio2016/O https://t/O/Oco/FrJQH8Bbwu 
@prabowo/O :/O Kader/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION harus/O yakin/O akan/O Pasal/O 33/O UUD/O 1945/O Kader/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION harus/O cinta/O tanah/O air/O Tidak/O boleh/O ada/O niat/O untuk/O mencuri/O dari/O bangsa/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Kantor/O KPUD/O Bojonegoro/LOCATION Dibobol/O Maling/O ,/O 14/O Ribu/O Surat/O Suara/O Hilang/O https://t.co/huFrTLlxRX/O 
<58>/O Kursi/O Parlemen/O Inggris/LOCATION Dikurangi/O ,/O Jumlah/O Pemilih/O Dinaikkan/O https://t/O/Oco/0c2zmeSdMk/O 
<54>/O PDI-P/ORGANIZATION :/O Kepercayaan/O Masyarakat/O Tinggi/O ,/O Cambuk/O Lakukan/O Perbaikan/O https://t/O/Oco/y8o3wVqatT/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Saya/O mengucapkan/O terima/O kasih/O atas/O kepercayaan/O teman-teman/O PB/O Pertina/O yg/O menunjuk/O saya/O menjadi/O Ketua/O Umum/O PB/O Pertina/O https://t.co/wdwRzR6PtD/O 
@aagym/O :/O Mata/O lihat/O pemandangan/O indah/O ,/O hati/O ingat/O yang/O Maha/O indah/O In/O syaa/O Alloh/O jadi/O amal/O https://t.co/kX8ZIFn3rY/O 
@UnkrisRadio/O :/O sekarang/O kita/O lagi/O dengan/O ibu/O nuke/PERSON nih/O selaku/O sekprodi/O teknik/O Informatika/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Smart/O City/O di/O kompleks/O Lido/O akn/O menjadi/O kawasan/O terintegrasi/O yg/O seluruhnya/O dikelola/O scr/O digital/O dgn/O teknologi/O tinggi/O https://t.co/WSYRZ47yDO/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyanyikan/O lagu/O Indonesia/LOCATION Raya/O di/O Institut/ORGANIZATION Agama/ORGANIZATION Islam/ORGANIZATION Negeri/ORGANIZATION (/O IAIN/O )/O Bengkulu/LOCATION Bengkulu/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O ,/O 17/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/Ql40OHuo30/O 
@BSJ_crew/O :/O RT/O @Ruben18_/O :/O Pendaftaran/O MNG/O BLINK/O INDONESIA/LOCATION resmi/O di/O buka/O !/O 
@WindaSukmawt/O :/O Semangat/O (/O SMK/ORGANIZATION Media/ORGANIZATION Informatika/ORGANIZATION Selatan/ORGANIZATION )/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Pengamat/O :/O Perkembangan/O IT/O Picu/O Model/O Ekonomi/O Kolaboratif/O https://t.co/W884TW9b8K/O 
<20>/O Foto:/O Ini/O Berlian/O Termahal/O di/O Dunia/O Seharga/O Rp/O 830/O M/O https://t.co/wW8BtVPdVv/O #KASKUSNews/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O sama2/O terima/O kasih/O https://t.co/fXoG7a2nH6/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Jangan/O terlalu/O sering/O mengulang/O cerita/O sukses/O masa/O lalu/O ,/O karena/O nanti/O orang/O mengira/O masa/O kini/O Anda/O kurang/O menghangatkan/O hati/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Lalu/O ada/O keluarga/O yang/O merasa/O lebih/O ningrat/O daripada/O tetangganya/O ,/O karena/O ada/O anaknya/O yang/O sarjana/O ,/O walau/O pun/O masih/O menganggur/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<4>/O Lupakan/O Sedot/O Lemak/O ,/O Ada/O Cara/O Murah/O dan/O Aman/O Turunkan/O Berat/O Badan/O https://t/O/Oco/O KxUteseHW/O 
<67>/O Mengintip/O Latihan/O Terbesar/O Militer/O Rusia/LOCATION https://t.co/UnyBu09s4i/O #KASKUSNews/O 
<66>/O Headshot:/O Film/O Action/O Terbaru/O Kebanggaan/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/JxwDUqLTNy/O #ForumKaskus/O 
@Prasetyo_Wisnu/O :/O @PTPERTAMINA/O pertamina/ORGANIZATION belum/O berubah/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Mudah/O sekali/O bagi/O kita/O untuk/O melihat/O kekurangan/O orang/O lain/O ,/O tapi/O sulit/O untuk/O menyadarinya/O pada/O diri/O kita/O sendiri/O MT/PERSON 
@KompasTV/O :/O 20/O Warga/O Binaan/O di/O Sumut/LOCATION Mendapat/O Remisi/O Hari/O Raya/O Nyepi/O https://t.co/bivTgtPJdk/O 
<56>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O Genjot/O Wisata/O ,/O Lampung/LOCATION Gelar/O Festival/O Taman/O Hutan/O Raya/O https://t.co/1QzYHi1tor/O https://t.co/mjK8VXJtyy/O 
@meyzamawarila/O :/O Semoga/O program/O JKN-KIS/O semakin/O bermanfaat/O bagi/O masyarakat/O Iuran/O Anda/O menolong/O sesama/O Dengan/O gotong/O royong/O ,/O semua/O tertolong/O 
@ClickRifkyDito/O :/O RT/O @infoBMKG/O :/O TimurLaut/O KEP-TALAUD/LOCATION -/O SULUT/LOCATION 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Info/O Gempa/O Mag/O :/O 4/O 2/O SR/O ,/O 10-Mar-16/O 18/O :/O 42/O :/O 05/O WIB/O ,/O Lok/O :/O 8/O 97/O LS/O ,/O 111/O 40/O BT/O (/O 93/O km/O Tenggara/O PACITAN/LOCATION -/O JATIM/LOCATION )/O ,/O Kedlmn/O :/O 22/O Km/O :/O :/O BMKG-PGR/O VII/O 
<19>/O RT/O @GNTMetroTV:/O Batik/O Papua/LOCATION memukau/O publik/O Belanda/LOCATION @kbridenhaag/O @Metro_TV/O @GNFI/O https://t/O/Oco/2jGsppU2sY/O 
@Harian_Jogja/O :/O LOWONGAN/O KERJA/O SEMARANG/LOCATION :/O Inilah/O Lowongan/O Pekerjaan/O yang/O Ditawarkan/O Job/O Fair/O UKSW/O https://t.co/FQCotg6x8B/O 
<69>/O Mengintip/O Latihan/O Terbesar/O Militer/O Rusia/LOCATION https://t.co/9mBna1q8xZ/O #KASKUSNews/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O #Pers/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION harus/O terus/O tumbuh/O berkembang/O ,/O terus/O belajar/O dan/O menjadi/O lebih/O cerdas/O dari/O pembacanya/O #HPN2016/O 
@cdcindonesia/O :/O Panduan/O untuk/O anda/O yang/O tertarik/O bekerja/O di/O perusahaan/O minyak/O dan/O gas/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION ,/O Chevron/ORGANIZATION ,/O Medco/ORGANIZATION ,/O BP/ORGANIZATION ,/O 
@HantuLaut23/O :/O heppy/O milad/O kota/O pekalongan/LOCATION yang/O ke/O 110/O tahun/O #kembalikanpekalongankuraa/O 
@jsoomie/O :/O RT/O @jjkurs/O :/O Kangen/O yang/O lain/O tp/O males/O manggil/O nick/PERSON Entar/O dikira/O absen/O sekolah/O 
@infodishub/O :/O RAPAT/O KOORDINASI/O WILAYAH/O KANTOR/O OTORITAS/O BANDAR/O UDARA/O WILAYAH/O VI/O http://t.co/gPijGgkCG1/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@detikcom/O :/O SBY/PERSON Kagumi/O Produksi/O Garmen/O Lokal/O Berkelas/O Internasional/O di/O Tasikmalaya/LOCATION https://t.co/3ktc9QWDUT/O 
@endahstyani26/O :/O @sfransisca_/O kekurangan/O ga/O selalu/O bkn/O jelek/O Iya/O liat/O aja/O dibanding/O artis/O Korea/LOCATION yg/O udah/O kaya/O triplek/O coba/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Saipul/PESON Jamil/PERSON Artis/O ,/O Polisi/ORGANIZATION Tak/O Boleh/O Salah/O https://t.co/7eK0zy1gNN/O via/O @detikHot/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Oppo/ORGANIZATION Kejar/O Penjualan/O 3/O ,/O 5/O Juta/O Unit/O https://t.co/yvyCf34cgU/O via/O @detikinet/O https://t.co/juPOb1TRUq/O 
@GoonersRomale/O :/O @KRMTRoySuryo/O udah/O hapal/O indonesia/LOCATION raya/O belum/O ?/O 
@detiksport/O :/O RT/O @AboutTheGame_/O :/O "/O Tak/O heran/O apabila/O David/PERSON Dein/PERSON menganggap/O Wenger/PERSON sebagai/O manajer/O terpenting/O dalam/O sejarah/O Arsenal/ORGANIZATION "/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Aspirasi/O rakyat/O (/O yg/O muncul/O dlm/O Tour/O de/O Java/O SBY/PERSON )/O bukan/O utk/O dihancurkan/O ,/O justru/O harus/O didengar/O Bukankah/O pemimpin/O mesti/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Rupiah/O Menguat/O ,/O Jokowi/PERSON :/O Kebijakan/O Pemerintah/O ,/O BI/ORGANIZATION ,/O dan/O OJK/ORGANIZATION Direspons/O Positif/O https://t.co/EPh5Gf8C0O/O via/O @detikFinance/O 
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @pekerjarumahan/O :/O Perwakilan/O #PekerjaRumahan/O dalam/O #Musrenbangcam/O #Blimbing/O @pemkotmalang/O @portalSURYA/O @jokowi/O @agatha_frogie/O @GNFI/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Ogitu/O cyin/O https://t.co/KGA9uloXhZ/O 
<15>/O Kalahkan/O Kahn/PERSON ,/O Buffon/PERSON Jadi/O Penjaga/O Gawang/O Terbaik/O Liga/O Champions/O https://t/O/Oco/NMs2imxdW0/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Red/ORGANIZATION Velvet/ORGANIZATION Rilis/O Album/O Mini/O '/O THE/O VELVET/O '/O 16/O Maret/O ,/O Ini/O Teaser/O Fotonya/O !/O https://t.co/TYbySkHB5S/O via/O @detikhot/O https://t.co/tapjoxF09O/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Porsche/ORGANIZATION Siap/O Jualan/O Mobil/O Listrik/O https://t.co/MdhocDsl5R/O via/O @detikoto/O https://t.co/VoljOrg4Qo/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Carrick/PERSON :/O Kemenangan/O yang/O Berarti/O Lebih/O dari/O Tiga/O Angka/O https://t.co/I8pzm2CvUX/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O ini/O Rencana/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION Setelah/O Blok/O Masela/O Diputuskan/O https://t.co/de5d95NZfu/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Pembukaan/O #MunasKadin/O https://t.co/YGqNBwImNV/O 
@ALorantifolia/O :/O RT/O @hariankompas/O :/O Pusat/O Ekonomi/O Baru/O Didorong/O "/O Konferensi/O Kota-kota/O Kreatif/O 2016/O Digelar/O di/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION https://t.co/RSDlkWlvBv/O 
<37>/O Jelajah/O Festival/O Budaya/O dari/O Timur/O ke/O Barat/O selama/O 017/O ,/O ini/O jadwalnya./O https://t.co/O ZpnWnRO7N/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Insya/O Allah/O besok/O pagi/O saya/O akan/O pimpin/O upacara/O penghormatan/O terakhir/O kepada/O beliau/O di/O rumah/O duka/O ,/O DPP/ORGANIZATION Gerindra/ORGANIZATION (/O Ragunan/O )/O jam/O 08.00/O WIB/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Bali/LOCATION Process/O Didorong/O Jadi/O Forum/O Dialog/O Kebijakan/O https://t.co/NPrdxvc7h0/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Apa/O pun/O yang/O terjadi/O hari/O ini/O ,/O jangan/O melemah/O Jangan/O menyerah/O Coba/O lagi/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON https://t.co/6pETatmAOp/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Tekad/O Chelsea/ORGANIZATION Berlari/O Kencang/O di/O Akhir/O demi/O Finis/O Sebaik/O Mungkin/O https://t.co/GfrkaqTu45/O https://t.co/ATgQ4dug9S/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Pulang2/O ada/O Yuda/PERSON Keling/PERSON di/O kasur/O gue/O Ini/O siapa/O yg/O bawa/O nih/O ?/O !/O https://t.co/zrAGKSBVOe/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Hahahaha/O kirimin/O dong/O !/O https://t.co/SATO9sTXJ4/O 
@gasa_nova/O :/O #RECOMMENDED4BO/O =/O @its_chanra/O :/O Makasih/O buat/O yg/O dah/O ikutan/O EXPO/O BSD/O SURABAYA/LOCATION n/O MALANG/LOCATION ,/O https://t.co/Jw8XIyrCEQ/O 
<19>/O Di/O era/O globalisasi/O ,/O para/O pemimpin/O dituntut/O utk/O lbh/O pragmatis/O ,/O adaptif/O &/O inovatif/O Namun/O ,/O utk/O urusan/O negara/O pemimpin/O haruslah/O visioner/O *SBY*/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Bertemu/O dengan/O John/PERSON Chen/PERSON CEO/O Blackberry/ORGANIZATION di/O sela-sela/O #APEC2015Philippines/O https://t.co/TWi8QhZusB/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Australia/LOCATION Punya/O Kepentingan/O soal/O Pencari/O Suaka/O https://t.co/F0U89gcEnP/O 
@Cambalado/O :/O Karawang/LOCATION pastikan/O tarif/O angkutan/O umum/O turun/O 
@HarifasLazuardi/O :/O 5/O Cara/O Yang/O Untuk/O Hilangkan/O Bosan/O Rumah/O https://t.co/sJLBU8Bt08/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Marilah/O kita/O lanjutkan/O perjuangan/O para/O pendahulu/O kita/O Kesampingkan/O ego/O pribadi/O Selalu/O pilih/O pilihan/O terbaik/O untuk/O bangsa/O dan/O rakyat/O 
@DeLimbong/O :/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION Gandeng/O Tiga/O BUMN/O Kembangkan/O PLTS/O 
@inpojabar/O :/O Harga/O Gabah/O di/O Kabupaten/O Cianjur/LOCATION Merosot/O Tajam/O ,/O Rp/O 3.700/O Per/O Kilogram/O -/O Tribun/O Jabar/LOCATION https://t.co/N48Z2kOtX3/O #Cianjur/O 
@syafiqshariff_/O :/O Semoga/O @D_Amerda/O dan/O ahli/O keluarga/O tabah/O 
<91>/O RS/LOCATION Milik/O Rohadi/PERSON sempat/O Beroperasi/O tanpa/O Izin/O https://t/O/Oco/GFXK5uEpFu/O https://t/O/Oco/8UxO6xTGEr/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Karena/O rekan-rekan/O media/O adalah/O sahabat/O saya/O http://t.co/yLjVL6hXSQ/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Selain/O lucu/O ,/O para/O komedian/O juga/O cerdas/O menangkap/O fenomena/O rakyat/O Saya/O ingin/O mendengar/O suara/O mereka/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/MD2rnK3sLr/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Meeting/O produksi/O film/O Koala/O Kumal/O https://t.co/hx2YUQl6jn/O 
@nkumaladev/O :/O Saya/O suka/O video/O @YouTube/O 
<72>/O Kapolri:/O Bendera/O Rasis/O di/O Pulau/O Pari/O Jakarta/LOCATION Sedang/O Diselidiki/O https://t.co/Ze1Bnpb0Is/O 
<5>/O Napoli/ORGANIZATION Bawa/O Pulang/O Tripoin/O dari/O Palermo/ORGANIZATION https://t/O/Oco/78yZiNkK6u/O 
@extremecareer/O :/O LEGAL/O STAFF/O -/O GRAHA/O Informatika/O NUSANTARA/O 
@FansParniHadi/O :/O Penghasilan/O Rp/O 4,5/O Juta/O per/O Bulan/O 
@MauJualBeli/O :/O Usul/O Gaji/O Rp/O 4,5/O Juta/Bulan/O Bebas/O Pajak/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Sebelum/O Beli/O ,/O Jajal/O Dulu/O SUV/O Mercedes/ORGANIZATION Pilihan/O Anda/O https://t.co/IiKkb8ufte/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 08/O :/O 34/O :/O 48/O ,/O 9/O WITA/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Makassar/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
<53>/O 74/O tahun/O sudah/O Kelompok/O Usaha/O Bakrie/O berdiri/O Kami/O akan/O terus/O berkarya/O untuk/O Negeri/O https://t/O/Oco/NXJ90q8YmR 
@infodishub/O :/O ANGKUTAN/O GRATIS/O KAPAL/O LAUT/O JADI/O FAVORIT/O PEMUDIK/O http://t.co/cYdxbtvsxx/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O Mari/O kita/O doakan/O mereka/O yang/O berpulang/O dalam/O tragedi/O AACC/O 9/O Februari/O 2008/O Semoga/O menjadi/O hikmah/O utk/O kita/O semuanya/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Di/O Jayapura/LOCATION ,/O pengamatan/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O #GMT9Mar16/O dilaksanakan/O di/O Halaman/LOCATION Kantor/LOCATION TVRI/ORGANIZATION Bhayangkara/ORGANIZATION Papua/LOCATION 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Kunker/O ke/O Jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION menghadiri/O Haul/O Gus/PERSON Dur/PERSON https://t.co/oZZ8yFNeBf/O 
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @iqbal_maind/O :/O @infomalang/O min/O ,/O di/O malang/LOCATION yg/O jualan/O voice/O recorder/O kayak/O gini/O dimana/O ya/O ?/O Selain/O hartono/LOCATION electronic/LOCATION ?/O Nuwus/O min/O 
@aan_dewo24/O :/O Selamat/O buat/O 460/O peserta/O Manajemen/O ,/O Informatika/O ,/O Elektro/O ,/O Elektronika/O ,/O Teknik/O Lingkungan/O ,/O Komunikasi/O yang/O ikut/O tes/O fisik/O PT/ORGANIZATION PLN/ORGANIZATION (/O Persero/ORGANIZATION )/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Menpora/O Terancam/O Hukuman/O Pidana/O dan/O Perdata/O https://t.co/VKjOx7Or3y/O https://t.co/F2jVD338j2/O 
@AstriyRahman/O :/O RT/O @ramada_fm/O :/O buat/O para/O jomblo/O yang/O lagi/O difrendzone/O in/O biar/O semangat/O nih/O stay/O tune/O di/O 107,7/O RAMADA/ORGANIZATION FM/ORGANIZATION Jogja/LOCATION w/O //O @wailestra/O &/O @andycip/O 
@everyonepiece/O :/O Hiduplah/O tanahku/O ,/O hiduplah/O negeriku/O ,/O bangsaku/O ,/O rakyatku/O ,/O semuanya/O Bangunlah/O jiwanya/O ,/O bangunlah/O badannya/O ,/O untuk/O Indonesia/LOCATION Raya/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Konvensi/O Partai/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION telah/O berakhir/O Kita/O sudah/O tahu/O hasilnya/O Pengalaman/O 8/O bulan/O terakhir/O tersebut/O istimewa/O bagi/O saya/O 
<81>https://t.co/O exYwrTP7q/O Kisah/O Sedih/O Aisyah/PERSON ,/O Korban/O Tewas/O JPO/O Ambruk/O Yang/O Baru/O Ultah/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Inna/O Lillahi/O wa/O inna/O ilaihi/O raji/O 'un/O Saya/O dan/O Partai/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION turut/O berduka/O atas/O kepergian/O bapak/O Ben/PERSON Mboi/PERSON ,/O pengayom/O masyarakat/O NTT/LOCATION 
@afieqsyauqie/O :/O Ada/O satu/O organisasi/O ni/O 
<85>/O Kuasa/O Hukum/O Sebut/O Agus/PERSON Belum/O Tentu/O Berniat/O Lakukan/O Pembunuhan/O Berencana/O https://t/O/Oco/PRDKz2CzJH/O 
@sandokah/O :/O @bellazoditama/O aku/O pun/O tau/O pas/O baca/O tribun/O Jogja/LOCATION tadi/O pagi/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Pandangan/O @FPD_DPR/O revisi/O UU/O KPK/ORGANIZATION berpotensi/O timbulkan/O konflik/O otoritas/O &/O melemahkan/O https://t.co/FhDO9ZCJRN/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Wajib/O Pajak/O Lapor/O SPT/O Online/O Dibidik/O Naik/O 3/O ,/O5 Kali/O Lipat/O https://t.co/79g6P8l82x/O 
<80>/O Merasa/O Sakit/O Setelah/O Bercinta?/O Bisa/O Jadi/O Ini/O Sebabnya/O https://t/O/Oco/Qsp26vou3G/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Jalur/O Kereta/O Tanah/LOCATION Abang/LOCATION -/O Manggarai/LOCATION Normal/O Kembali/O https://t.co/8nUFHtPeRd/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Sore/O https://t.co/TNwz5lHOKM/O 
@medan/O :/O Jenis/O baru/O ,/O "/O Solar/O Dex/O Lite/O "/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION berencana/O meluncurkan/O produk/O bahan/O bakar/O minyak/O (/O BBM/O )/O Solar/O varian/O baru/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Proyek/O Kereta/O Cepat/O Jakarta/LOCATION -/O Bandung/LOCATION ,/O Apa/O Kata/O SBY/PERSON ?/O https://t.co/JzlA2dtWKS/O 
<100>/O Tips/O anti/O gemuk/O santap/O makanan/O berlemak/O saat/O Hari/O Raya/O https://t.co/2LBz77luLi/O 
<86>/O Yusril/PERSON Galang/O Poros/O Baru/O untuk/O Tantang/O Ahok/PERSON di/O Pilgub/O DKI/LOCATION https://t.co/ciwcJXcXH3/O #KASKUSNews/O 
<74>/O Selamat/O Hari/O Raya/O Idul/O Adha/O 437/O H/O Semoga/O apa/O yang/O kita/O kurbankan/O hari/O ini/O ,/O membersihkan/O diri/O dan/O harta/O kita/O https://t/O/Oco/jBso5FEp0C/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Kemarin/O saya/O ke/O pembangunan/O stasiun/O kereta/O api/O Bandara/LOCATION Minangkabau/LOCATION Des/O 2015/O bisa/O digunakan/O masyarakat/O Sumbar/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON http://t.co/PnSrVBuGpV/O 
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @Anggiaewis/O :/O Saran/O untuk/O akses/O jln/O dr/O pasar/LOCATION mergan/LOCATION ke/O daerah/O bandulan/LOCATION di/O perlebar/O dan/O bila/O perlu/O ad/O traffic/O light/O jg/O @PemkotMalang/O 
@Akuandes/O :/O Mengapa/O kamu/O baru/O hadir/O di/O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O disaat/O aku/O udah/O lulus/O kuliah/O ?/O https://t.co/f2GJaXwI89/O 
@detikcom/O :/O 10/O Motor/O Terlaris/O Bulan/O Februari/O 2016/O https://t.co/ExHYj0wZf7/O via/O @detikOto/O https://t.co/gTUKqkBrOv/O 
@infodishub/O :/O 1200/O PERWIRA/O TRANSPORTASI/ yang/O HANDAL/O dan/O PROFESIONAL/O DILANTIK/O http://t.co/AWqNR0nreE/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O di/O Jayapura/LOCATION ,/O #GMT9Mar16/O akan/O teramati/O sejak/O pukul/O 08/O :/O 53/O :/O/O 42/O ,/O 8/O WIT/O hingga/O pukul/O 11/O :/O 48/O :/O 45/O ,/O 9/O WIT/O 
<53>/O #News/O #ZonaMPR/O Penyuluh/O Pertanian/O Berharap/O Bantuan/O Ketua/O MPR/ORGANIZATION Agar/O Menjadi/O PNS/O https://t.co/BkoIwRbHeS/O https://t.co/zfzu6SaeGn/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Anak/O muda/O yang/O super/O ,/O bekerja/O untuk/O digaji/O ,/O tapi/O dia/O menaikkan/O kepantasannya/O untuk/O digaji/O dengan/O baik/O sekali/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Bpk/O Gusti/PERSON Rusdi/PERSON Effendi/PERSON ,/O Pemimpin/O Umum/O Banjarmasin/LOCATION Post/O Banjarmasin/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 3/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/7msk4E1ZFP/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Buruh/O adalah/O aset/O bagi/O kemajuan/O bangsa/O Indonesia/LOCATION Sudah/O sepantasnya/O lah/O untuk/O dihargai/O Selamat/O hari/O buruh/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Yuk/O ,/O Buat/O Nasi/O Goreng/O Telur/O Asin/O yang/O Gurih/O Enak/O !/O https://t.co/XHX0GkUlnL/O via/O @detikFood/O https://t.co/qkvpPumT0O/O 
@irvandadank/O :/O pemandangan/O diatas/O bianglala/O ,/O alun-alun/O kota/O batu/O malang/LOCATION @xiaomiindonesia/O https://t.co/H14vv73XHe/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Kita/O tidak/O bisa/O menghindari/O kesedihan/O ,/O tapi/O kita/O tetap/O bisa/O menjadi/O pribadi/O yang/O tabah/O karena/O doa/O dan/O harapan/O kita/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<69>https://t.co/vDIMf7d2P3/O Intip/O Daftar/O Lengkap/O Para/O Pemenang/O Festival/O Film/O Bandung/LOCATION 016/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Walau/O Kecewa/O ,/O Menristek/O Takjub/O dengan/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O Total/O https://t.co/EvTRqdAieO/O 
@ferry_rinaldi/O :/O Solusi/O Cerdas/O DJP/O atasi/O Online/O Error/O 
@aagym/O :/O Teruslah/O berbuat/O kebaikan/O walaupun/O orang/O tak/O menghargai/O kebaikan/O kita/O ,/O karena/O Alloh/O pasti/O akan/O menyempurnakan/O balasanNya/O 
@MasjidJakarta/O :/O BNN/ORGANIZATION Ungkap/O Pabrik/O Sabu/O di/O Medan/LOCATION ,/O Empat/O Tersangka/O Dibekuk/O :/O Sebuah/O rumah/O yang/O dijadikan/O sebagai/O tempat/O pembuatan/O https://t.co/pSj2oacEJX/O 
@elkiram/O :/O Peran/O Penting/O Keluarga/O dalam/O Pendidikan/O Karakter/O Anak/O https://t.co/27vpKZVGGz/O 
@infomalang/O :/O #cuacamalang/O RT/O @bayu2bay/O :/O di/O sukun/LOCATION dan/O sekitarnya/O ujan/O deras/O listrik/O padam/O pula/O 
@GoGlobalStore/O :/O LOWONGAN/O KERJA/O KARYAWAN/O PT/ORGANIZATION SWADARMA/ORGANIZATION SARANA/ORGANIZATION Informatika/O PALEMBANG/LOCATION 
@radityadika/O :/O Video/O terbaru/O Dapet/O tips/O modus/O dari/O aktor2/O film/O :/O https://t.co/lHH5hfkLIt/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Ingin/O sharing/O sedikit/O ,/O ada/O yang/O bertanya/O mengapa/O mendukung/O Prabowo/PERSON -/O Hatta/PERSON ?/O 
@kelanabumi/O :/O #LoKer/O #Indonesia/O |/O Guru/O Akuntansi/O ,/O Matematika/O ,/O Biologi/O ,/O Fisika/O bimbel/O BLC/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/8SPwLpj0zW/O 
@ridwankamil/O :/O artina/O "/O geus/O peuting/O geura/O sare/O "/O https://t.co/1M1s2mO4UU/O 
@aagym/O :/O Bagi/O yang/O sibuk/O dengan/O asmara/O dan/O cinta/O membara/O ,/O inilah/O cinta/O para/O sahabat/O yang/O membawa/O kebahagiaan/O dunia/O akherat/O https://t.co/slV1k4wcrH/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O RT/O @DinasTA_Jakarta/O :/O Keg/O Penanganan/O saluran/O diperempatan/O joglo/O Kec/O Kembangan/LOCATION @PoskoDPUDKI/O @TMCPoldaMetro/O http://t.co/H8lvbuehhn/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Kepercayaan/O publik/O yang/O telah/O diraih/O KPK/ORGANIZATION harus/O terus/O dipertahankan/O dan/O ditingkatkan/O dengan/O terus/O bekerja/O secara/O lebih/O profesional/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Selamat/O berjuang/O para/O pengurus/O DPC/O Dapil/O 2/O Riau/LOCATION yang/O baru/O saja/O dilantik/O Indragiri/LOCATION Hulu/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 10/O Maret/O 2016/O https://t.co/vrJGbUtc4I/O 
@aagym/O :/O Mohon/O doa/O ,/O tugas/O dakwah/O menuju/O Oman/LOCATION ,/O semoga/O jadi/O amal/O soleh/O dan/O manfaat/O ,/O doakan/O ya/O Shbtku/O yg/O baik/O https://t.co/17JdiAbLKQ/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Datsun/ORGANIZATION Mulai/O Diproduksi/O Mobil/O Rp60/O Jutaan/O https://t.co/gQTBmqrD0y/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Pak/O Jokowi/PERSON ,/O teruslah/O emban/O amanah/O &/O bekerja/O hingga/O tahun/O 2019/O Jangan/O mau/O kita/O diprovokasi/O &/O diadu/O domba/O Semoga/O sukses/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Cinta/O tanpa/O kesetiaan/O akan/O mati/O muda/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Shawcross/PERSON :/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON Hancurkan/O Karier/O Saya/O di/O Timnas/O Inggris/LOCATION https://t.co/c3s0by3zGC/O 
<95>/O Festival/O Puputan/O Badung/LOCATION Segera/O Digelar/O di/O Denpasar/O https://t/O/Oco/HFxBWn02jC/O 
@IniBisnis/O :/O Usul/O Gaji/O Rp/O 4,5/O Juta/Bulan/O Bebas/O Pajak/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Warga/O Jatisari/LOCATION Cemooh/O Pelaku/O Pembunuhan/O Penggoda/O Istri/O Korban/O https://t.co/gPNmBozBRs/O 
@aligalendo/O :/O @PTPERTAMINA/O 1/O )/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION Lubricant/O 2/O )/O 15/O tikungan/O 3/O Urutan/O pertama/O 4/O )/O 2/O tulisan/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION 5/O )/O 3/O varian/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O cenderamata/O kepada/O Ibu/O Datin/PERSON Seri/PERSON Anggraini/PERSON Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O Jumat/O 11/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/S0RgADpxMD/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Golden/O State/O Terus/O Perpanjang/O Rekor/O Menang/O di/O Kandang/O https://t.co/55yL0YDtUX/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Acara/O pembukaan/O International/O Consultation/O on/O Multi-Religions/O Humanitarion/O Action/O di/O kantor/LOCATION wapres/LOCATION https://t.co/wl72lKAYPt/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Cantiknya/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O Kala/O Sunrise/O di/O Sumatera/LOCATION Utara/LOCATION https://t.co/Mk2Oif8giP/O via/O @detikTravel/O https://t.co/kQcBNfqERy/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Perlukah/O Revisi/O UU/O KPK/ORGANIZATION ?/O @PDemokrat/O berdiskusi/O bersama/O Netizen/O Apa/O pendapat/O kalian/O ,/O Tweeps/O ?/O @FPD_DPR/O https://t.co/Sb5bcudR2C/O 
<55>/O Kita/O bersyukur/O ,/O bangsa/O kita/O melahirkan/O pemimpin-pemimpin/O besar/O yang/O melahirkan/O Pancasila/O #HariPancasila/O 
@aagym/O :/O Yang/O membuat/O seseorang/O mulia/O bukanlah/O pangkat/O dan/O jabatannya/O ,/O melainkan/O kesanggupan/O memikul/O dan/O menyempurnakan/O amanahnya/O 
<39>/O RT/O @haluannegara:/O Konvensi/O naional/O haluan/O negara/O dihadiri/O oleh/O pak/O @aburizalbakrie/O https://t/O/Oco/ssnt9OiuO9 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 20/O :/O 42/O ,/O 4/O WIB/O :/O Fase/O Totalitas/O berakhir/O di/O Muko-muko/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
<17>/O Tiongkok/LOCATION dan/O Bahan/O Makanan/O Pokoknya/O https://t.co/tyDU9Gp1ED/O #KASKUSNews/O https://t.co/gJFCrJnwtY 
@detikcom/O :/O Shanghai/LOCATION Geser/O Bali/LOCATION dari/O Posisi/O 3/O Besar/O Lokasi/O Rumah/LOCATION Mewah/O di/O Asia/LOCATION https://t.co/JvNEDdYkZL/O via/O @detikfinance/O https://t.co/jaSOMV2o2o/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @GNFI/O :/O Inilah/O harapan/O untuk/O Indonesia/LOCATION di/O tahun/O 2016/O dari/O @Edhie_Baskoro/O yang/O disampaikan/O melalui/O #GNFI/O #2016wish/O https://t.co/W6oCtyJ0DL/O 
<98>/O Untuk/O rakyat/O ,/O utamanya/O pencinta/O &/O komunitas/O sepak/O bola/O ,/O diperlukan/O kearifan/O ,/O jiwa/O besar/O &/O solusi/O yg/O tepat/O dari/O para/O pemimpin/O *SBY*/O 
@RHDP_31/O :/O Ngebut/O Drama/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Jadi/O minggu/O ini/O lebih/O sering/O laper/O atau/O baper/O ?/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @opahcuki/O ditunggu/O saja/O pengumuman/O resmi/O dr/O partai/O utk/O pemenang/O konvensi/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Sukses/O selalu/O anak/O muda/O Indonesia/LOCATION CC/O :/O @husainabdullah1/O @imam_nahrawi/O https://t.co/2FfvgUxvsp/O 
@aagym/O :/O Senin/O pagi/O jam/O 5/O SMP/O jam/O 6/O hari/O ini/O Aa/O ada/O kajian/O di/O TVRI/ORGANIZATION ,/O silakan/O simak/O ya/O bagi/O yg/O berkesempatan/O 
@iki_Suroboyo/O :/O Ratusan/O Pekerja/O PT/ORGANIZATION Pelindo/ORGANIZATION III/ORGANIZATION Merasa/O Jadi/O Korban/O Perbudakan/O https://t.co/hEQBeJrZOn/O 
@radityadika/O :/O Kenapa/O baper/O https://t.co/KQZ7qlVRJO/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Pengemudi/O Lamborghini/ORGANIZATION Maut/O Ingin/O Jadi/O Wali/O Kota/O https://t.co/WFEa80k6Hi/O 
<8>/O Raffael/PERSON Khawatirkan/O Ancaman/O Sergio/PERSON Aguero/PERSON &/O Kevin/PERSON De/PERSON Bruyne/PERSON https://t.co/9eqfAOznGn/O #KASKUSLigaInggris/O #PL/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Politikus/O Senior/O Golkar/ORGANIZATION :/O ARB/PERSON -/O Agung/PERSON Kayak/O Amplop/O dan/O Prangko/O https://t.co/sUnDMWURi1/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Di/O DPR/ORGANIZATION ,/O Pendamping/O Dana/O Desa/LOCATION Cerita/O Ijazah/O SMA/O Bisa/O Lolos/O Seleksi/O Rekrutmen/O https://t.co/tpU6BBCarY/O 
@infomalang/O :/O @nouvalist/O @nu_garis/O keras/O ,/O kurang/O tahu/O Sejauh/O ini/O mimin/O blm/O pernah/O lihat/O langsung/O baliho/O itu/O 
@ghwijaya/O :/O RT/O @GNFI/O :/O Selamat/O Hari/O Jadi/O ke-102/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION Tercinta/O ,/O kota/O budaya/O ,/O kota/O pelajar/O ,/O dan/O kota/O yang/O bernafaskan/O keindahan/O 
<51>https://t.co/5J9gWwBNUd/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON Akhirnya/O Bersedia/O Temui/O Deddy/PERSON Corbuzier/PERSON Asalkan.../O 
@detikcom/O :/O '/O Shrek/O the/O Musical/O '/O Jakarta/LOCATION Berikan/O Hiburan/O Berkualitas/O bagi/O Keluarga/O https://t.co/FWqbQp0Yi4/O via/O @detikhot/O 
<19>/O Pemilik/O Brand/O Mode/O Asal/O Spanyol/O Ini/O Kalahkan/O Kekayaan/O Bill/PERSON Gates/PERSON !/O https://t.co/WVyJlc37QL/O #KASKUSNews/O 
@Mrzkhdyt/O :/O Efek/O Rumah/O Kaca/O https://t.co/Mi6xCtxWne/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Semoga/O para/O korban/O luka-luka/O dapat/O segera/O pulih/O dan/O kembali/O berkumpul/O bersama/O keluarga/O Amin/O 
<97>/O Pogba/PERSON Hengkang/O Bukan/O karena/O Higuain/PERSON https://t/O/Oco/D54tulzafB/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @FPD_DPR/O :/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION Konsisten/O Tolak/O Revisi/O KPK/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/AK0942l42P/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Tantang/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O Lulung/PERSON Juga/O Mau/O Jadi/O Gubernur/O Lewat/O Independen/O https://t.co/aIIjmkZAOB/O @basuki_btp/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Menghadiri/O Pembukaan/O Musyawarah/O Besar/O Masyarakat/O Maluku/LOCATION di/O Islamic/LOCATION Centre/LOCATION Ambon/LOCATION 25/O //O 11/O https://t.co/ViSeffbRt9/O 
@FrenkyChipenk/O :/O #nonton/O ryoharyanto/O dulu/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O Ketua/O PBMI/ORGANIZATION Bpk/O Sudirman/PERSON ,/O jajaran/O Pengurus/O PBMI/ORGANIZATION dan/O para/O atlet/O Muaythai/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/ERhbCevdqK/O 
<21>/O Sepasang/O Kekasih/O di/O AS/LOCATION Ditangkap/O Usai/O Tabrak/O hingga/O Tewas/O Remaja/O Kulit/O Hitam/O https://t/O/Oco/EvgRCmcdJm/O 
@SoniaApriani10/O :/O RT/O @Bahteranu/O :/O Sayangi/O keluarga/O kita/O dgn/O sepenuh/O hati/O ,/O karena/O saat/O semua/O orang/O menghindari/O kita/O ,/O keluarga/O kita/O selalu/O menyayangi/O kita/O dgn/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Uber/ORGANIZATION dan/O GrabCar/ORGANIZATION Siap/O Ikut/O Aturan/O Pemerintah/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/juEUgBi1tL/O https://t.co/jECiUwAakG/O 
@aagym/O :/O Silakan/O datang/O besok/O Ahad/O di/O masjid/LOCATION Istiqlal/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O mulai/O jam/O 9/O sampai/O dhuhur/O ,/O tolong/O infokan/O ke/O yg/O lain/O ya/O https://t.co/Ze3ZUAHrtX/O 
@zeears/O :/O RT/O @pepatah/O :/O Keluarga/O adalah/O hal/O terpenting/O yg/O kita/O miliki/O dalam/O hidup/O ini/O yg/O tak/O akan/O pernah/O berubah/O dan/O selalu/O ada/O ketika/O kamu/O butuhkan/O 
<51>/O Dirjen/O PEN:/O Deregulasi/O Permudah/O Bisnis/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t/O/Oco/bwsta5RNd3/O https://t/O/Oco/hMfgw0pU2O/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Mengintip/O Markas/O Uber/ORGANIZATION ,/O Startup/O Pengguncang/O Industri/O Taksi/O https://t.co/76CnlodMgA/O via/O @detikinet/O 
