@prabowo/O :/O Mari/O kita/O juga/O sama-sama/O doa/O kan/O agar/O bung/O @HattaRajasa/O terus/O mendapat/O kesehatan/O dan/O kesempatan/O berjuang/O untuk/O kehormatan/O bangsa/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Kita/O tak/O akan/O menjadi/O hina/O karena/O dihina/O orang/O lain/O ,/O kita/O hina/O karena/O kehinaan/O perilaku/O kita/O dan/O kesenangan/O menghina/O orang/O lain/O 
<11>/O Arsenal/ORGANIZATION Coreng/O Rekor/O Gol/O Tercepat/O Sepanjang/O Sejarah/O PSG/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/c809Y8FOxI/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Selamat/O atas/O terpilihnya/O Presiden/O Htin/PERSON Kyaw/PERSON ./O Kita/O terus/O tingkatkan/O kerja/O sama/O di/O berbagai/O bidang/O dengan/O Myanmar/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Wakil/O Rektor/O III/O Universitas/ORGANIZATION Negeri/O Padang/ORGANIZATION Syahrial/PERSON Bahtiar/PERSON ./O Padang/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O 9/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/W48Le17ghV/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Choe/PERSON Song-Hyok/PERSON ,/O Komunis/O Pertama/O di/O Liga/O Italia/LOCATION https://t.co/OG3XRFSpUH/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Lorenzo/PERSON :/O Apakah/O Rossi/PERSON Masih/O Marah/O Padaku/O ?/O https://t.co/TGOKnPBUxP/O https://t.co/m41b0v06Pv/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Jangan/O lewatkan/O Putaran/O 2/O Yonex/ORGANIZATION All/O England/O di/O KompasTV/ORGANIZATION pukul/O 19/O ./O 30/O WIB/O dan/O ikuti/O juga/O kuisnya/O !/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O https://t.co/53NcAGmEst/O 
<97>/O Pogba/PERSON Hengkang/O Bukan/O karena/O Higuain/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/D54tulzafB/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Harga/O minyak/O dunia/O kembali/O menguat/O ?/O Tonton/O #KompasBisnis/O pkl/O 12/O ./O 30/O WIB/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Ketahui/O ,/O Sembilan/O Bunga/O yang/O Dapat/O Dikonsumsi/O https://t.co/vmUemv3cPO/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Sebelum/O Tampil/O di/O Dahsyat/O ,/O Zaskia/PERSON Gotik/PERSON Ikut/O '/O Briefing/O '/O https://t.co/3obhxETCuN/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Satu-satunya/O hal/O yang/O bisa/O melogiskan/O cinta/O ,/O adalah/O biaya/O hidup/O yang/O ternyata/O tidak/O murah/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<17>/O Emas/O Dunia/O Turun/O Akibat/O Pedagang/O Pertimbangkan/O Keputusan/O Fed/O https://t/O .co/LrcYoGS8VE/O https://t/O .co/HO2HROnWfN/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Jadi/O Laskar/O Gerhana/O ,/O Pulang/O Dapat/O Smartphone/O Keren/O https://t.co/Q8iGPSu8S4/O via/O @detikTravel/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Surat/O Cabut/O Laporan/O Misterius/O di/O Praperadilan/O Saipul/PERSON Jamil/PERSON https://t.co/8IaWgO2hT0/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O RT/O @Manalumario/O :/O @edhiewibowo_55/O Artikel/O bagus/O Pak/O ./O 4/O Alasan/O Mendukung/O Perppu/O Pilkada/O by/O Putu/PERSON Suasta/PERSON http://t.co/aRyNvdaRPs/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Adik-adik/O yang/O saya/O sayangi/O ,/O pagi-pagi/O gini/O enaknya/O kita/O cool/O tweet/O tentang/O apa/O ya/O ?/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Mau/O tau/O cara/O merawat/O kulit/O agar/O tampak/O awet/O muda/O ?/O Ikutan/O #LiveChat/O nya/O aja/O yuk/O !/O https://t.co/a9N65zrynV/O https://t.co/rfSuawmqQZ/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Ketua/O DPD/ORGANIZATION Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION Kabupaten/O Bandung/LOCATION Bpk/O Atnov/PERSON Trison/PERSON Situmorang/PERSON https://t.co/SzjpIoISL6/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Bangganya/O Siswa/O SMA/O yang/O Karyanya/O Diangkut/O NASA/ORGANIZATION dan/O Cita-cita/O Jadi/O Astronot/O https://t.co/viXDV809R6/O https://t.co/11TXSz8dcn/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Barcelona/ORGANIZATION Hentikan/O Perburuan/O Bek/O Everton/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/rW4AhT4HDY/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Manakala/O kita/O melihat/O ketidakadilan/O ,/O maka/O kita/O harus/O memilih/O ./O Memilih/O berdiri/O membela/O kebenaran/O ,/O atau/O mengikuti/O yang/O dzolim/O ./O 
@jokowi/O :/O Turut/O berduka/O atas/O meninggalnya/O supporter/O sepak/O bola/O ./O Tragedi/O ini/O jangan/O terjadi/O lagi/O ,/O kita/O semua/O bersaudara/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Meski/O Gratis/O ,/O Argo/O Ongkos/O Blue/ORGANIZATION Bird/ORGANIZATION Tetap/O Menyala/O https://t.co/S5pPK60mL6/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Pertunjukan/O Broadway/O Shrek/O Segera/O Hadir/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/TPAI9d4Ufv/O 
<90>/O Hamsik/PERSON Tak/O Menyangka/O Bisa/O Lewati/O Maradona/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/tGjS1POTxr/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selamat/O pagi/O ,/O sudah/O ada/O yang/O berpuasa/O ?/O Selamat/O puasa/O bagi/O yang/O sudah/O berpuasa/O di/O hari/O pertama/O ./O Selamat/O berakhir/O pekan/O untuk/O semua/O ./O 
@prabowo/O :/O Atas/O nama/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION dan/O pribadi/O ,/O saya/O turut/O berbela/O sungkawa/O kepada/O rakyat/O Republik/O Singapura/LOCATION atas/O wafatnya/O bapak/O Lee/PERSON Kuan/PERSON Yew/PERSON ./O 
<60>/O Terlibat/O Tabrakan/O Mobil/O ,/O Bek/O Crystal/ORGANIZATION Palace/ORGANIZATION Cedera/O Serius/O ./O https://t/O .co/IrJwRsBE3t/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Raih/O informasi/O serta/O inspirasi/O baru/O dalam/O @sapa_indonesia/O sesaat/O lagi/O ./O #SapaIndonesia/O 
@aagym/O :/O Tak/O ada/O kata/O terlambat/O bagi/O yg/O tidak/O sahur/O ,/O asal/O belum/O makan/O pagi/O silakan/O niat/O shaum/O sunnah/O hari/O ini/O yaa/O https://t.co/ROXeCTDic9/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Film/O Pendek/O Animasi/O '/O Kapur/O Ade/O '/O Raih/O Penghargaan/O Viddsee/O https://t.co/a5nUxwafUg/O via/O @detikHot/O 
<59>/O Lady/PERSON Gaga/PERSON Sebut/O Pentolan/O Tame/O Impala/O Seorang/O Jenius/O https://t/O .co/M9RAHI7nhH/O https://t/O .co/UrtWDEIios/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Pose/O Tidak/O Biasa/O Pengantin/O ini/O Bikin/O Heboh/O https://t.co/DguKsEdCg1/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Kini/O masuki/O tahap/O penghitungan/O suara/O dan/O saya/O berharap/O seluruh/O kader/O Partai/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION tetap/O bekerja/O giat/O dalam/O mengawal/O proses/O ini/O ./O 
@detikcom/O :/O '/O Kungfu/O Panda/O 3/O '/O (/O 3D/O )/O :/O Tetap/O Kocak/O dan/O Hangat/O ,/O dengan/O Aksi/O Lebih/O Banyak/O https://t.co/ku308bnvqT/O via/O @detikhot/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O segera/O panggil/O Menhub/O ./O Ojek/O dibutuhkan/O rakyat/O ./O Jangan/O karena/O aturan/O rakyat/O jadi/O susah/O ./O Harusnya/O ditata/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O sore/O sahabat/O ./O Saya/O selaku/O pribadi/O dan/O Ketua/O Umum/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION mengucapkan/O Selamat/O Hari/O Raya/O Idul/O Adha/O bagi/O umat/O Islam/O dimanapun/O berada/O ./O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Alasan/O Wanita/O dan/O Anak/O Rentan/O Mengidap/O Infeksi/O Saluran/O Kemih/O https://t.co/lqo86DRDIt/O 
<89>/O Bursa/O Asia/LOCATION Tergelincir/O di/O Awal/O Pekan/O https://t.co/uvLgjxcD1Q/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Konvensi/O Partai/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION telah/O berakhir/O ./O Kita/O sudah/O tahu/O hasilnya/O ./O Pengalaman/O 8/O bulan/O terakhir/O tersebut/O istimewa/O bagi/O saya/O ./O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Team/O sepak/O bola/O favorit/O Om/O Mario/PERSON apa/O ?/O -/O Barca/ORGANIZATION cabang/O Malang/LOCATION ,/O Arema/ORGANIZATION ./O 
@prabowo/O :/O @geral_silitonga/O Terima/O kasih/O ./O 
<32>/O Proyek/O Reklamasi/O Dilanjutkan/O ,/O Luhut/PERSON Jamin/O Semua/O Masalah/O Sudah/O Beres/O ./O https://t/O .co/N51WziXrN2/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Tim/O Rowing/O Indonesia/LOCATION Jalani/O Uji/O Coba/O di/O Australia/LOCATION https://t.co/zh4tYAmz8D/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Kedatangan/O kapal/O ternak/O perdana/O ,/O angkut/O sapi/O dari/O NTT/LOCATION ke/O Jakarta/LOCATION ./O Ongkos/O kirim/O efisien/O ,/O daging/O sapi/O lebih/O murah/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/pdySuyqwkz/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O 2/O ./O Apa/O yg/O kita/O saksikan/O semalam/O di/O kompleks/O ini/O (/O Sidang/O MKD/O )/O ,/O adalah/O skandal/O yg/O besar/O jika/O itu/O benar/O ,/O 
<70>/O Pelita/O Hati:/O Jangan/O Menyerah/O (1)/O https://t/O .co/mVKcBZlvsd/O https://t/O .co/5TLSQKpJqd/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Evakuasi/O Senja/O Utama/O Solo/LOCATION Masih/O Berlangsung/O ,/O 1/O Gerbong/O Belum/O Terangkat/O https://t.co/iu2DBKh3uP/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Turis/O Mancanegara/O di/O Belitung/LOCATION Merinding/O dan/O Puas/O dengan/O Penampakan/O Gerhana/O https://t.co/Gn93uyWtBg/O https://t.co/mT63T0ja0u/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Begini/O Cara/O India/LOCATION Salip/O Pertumbuhan/O Ekonomi/O China/LOCATION https://t.co/jsAFweo2cv/O via/O @detikfinance/O https://t.co/b0qTzIQ2by/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Mau/O dapat/O iPod/O Shuffle/O ?/O Yuk/O ,/O ikutan/O kontes/O foto/O #GayaAllEngland/O ./O Berikut/O syarat/O dan/O ketentuannya/O !/O https://t.co/SiLcYRvpbL/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Selamat/O Hari/O Sumpah/O Pemuda/O ,/O jadilah/O Pemuda/O Indonesia/LOCATION yang/O menjaga/O tanah/O ,/O air/O dan/O hutan/O ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O sibuk/O berkomentar/O yang/O tak/O dipahami/O dan/O tak/O perlu/O dikomentari/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O Tahun/O Baru/O Imlek/O 2016/O untuk/O sahabat/O yang/O merayakan/O ./O Semoga/O kesuksesan/O menyertai/O kita/O semua/O ./O 
<85>/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O Amien/PERSON Rais/PERSON ,/O dan/O Khotbah/O Bermuatan/O Politis/O ./O ./O ./O ./O https://t/O .co/g5JhHpXdOw/O 
@aagym/O :/O RT/O @daarutauhiidBDG/O :/O Safari/O Dakwah/O @aagym/O di/O Jepang/LOCATION sabtu-ahad/O 21-22/O Nov/O 2015/O info/O lengkap/O https://t.co/0iQibiiRQd/O https://t.co/f5PWBpjhzB/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Titik/O ketujuh/O di/O jalur/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O adalah/O Ternate/LOCATION ,/O Maluku/LOCATION Utara/LOCATION ./O Tepatnya/O di/O Pantai/LOCATION Palajawa/LOCATION samping/O Masjid/LOCATION Almunawar/LOCATION ,/O Ternate/LOCATION ./O 
<12>/O Ini/O Bukti/O Cinta/O Song/PERSON Joong/PERSON Ki/PERSON untuk/O Song/PERSON Hye/PERSON Kyo/PERSON ?/O https://t.co/rbTWFwPNAL/O https://t.co/ZBFmWTDoSH/O 
<6>/O Trio/O MSN/O tampil/O luar/O biasa/O menjamu/O Celtic/ORGANIZATION FC/ORGANIZATION ,/O Sob!Nonton/O gak?/O https://t/O .co/qNExQm07IH/O https://t/O .co/PwrVAwAZNV/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O 1/O ./O Setelah/O kita/O berikhtiar/O berusaha/O keras/O memadamkan/O api/O kebakaran/O hutan/O ,/O melalui/O udara/O dan/O darat/O ./O 
<14>/O Contek/O Desain/O Rumah/LOCATION Tipe/O 48/O Berikut/O Ini/O https://t.co/wsEgcCUsbZ/O https://t.co/oJKQ4jowtb/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Jalan/LOCATION Tol/O Akses/O Tanjung/LOCATION Priok/LOCATION Terhubung/O dengan/O Kereta/O Pelabuhan/LOCATION https://t.co/VvmtnZZDYm/O via/O @detikfinance/O 
<94>/O Mushroom/O Picking/O Championship/O https://t/O .co/UWPyymNyFI/O https://t/O .co/rU1jsuOUDq/O 
@prabowo/O :/O RT/O @kutub_bumi/O :/O Tetaplah/O teriakkan/O kebenaran/O ,/O walaupun/O hanya/O sendiri/O https://t.co/auxVl9qSwI/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Ditangkap/O Bawa/O Sabu/O ,/O Ismet/PERSON :/O Saya/O Wartawan/O https://t.co/Mc5Cji0e2L/O https://t.co/3r6JBHUPzj/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Ini/O Dia/O Hasil/O Undian/O Putaran/O Final/O Piala/O Thomas/O dan/O Uber/O 2016/O https://t.co/bL197lNcXI/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Perang/O Mulut/O Anas/PERSON dan/O Nazaruddin/PERSON di/O Pengadilan/O Tipikor/O https://t.co/CqcThNbl5Z/O 
<39>/O Pianis/O Cilik/O Fenomenal/O Joey/PERSON Alexander/PERSON Rilis/O Album/O Terbaru/O https://t.co/fMXsTeifIR/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Campur/O Susu/O Bayi/O dengan/O Pestisida/O ,/O Pengusaha/O Dipenjara/O https://t.co/7sDI7qig7V/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Jay/PERSON Subiyakto/PERSON Yakin/O Ahok/PERSON Menang/O Pilkada/O Jakarta/LOCATION https://t.co/sqMRKkZ5wg/O @basuki_btp/O 
@infodishub/O :/O H/O +/O 2/O ,/O JUMLAH/O PENUMPANG/O ANGKUTAN/O LEBARAN/O SELURUH/O MODA/O RATA-RATA/O MENGALAMI/O PENURUNAN/O http://t.co/NpOPzoNTcr/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@detikcom/O :/O #MostPopular/O Gadis/O Pemanis/O Beraksi/O di/O Bangkok/LOCATION Motor/O Show/O 2016/O https://t.co/QMlotZoRyc/O via/O @detikOto/O https://t.co/vthhx0Ippa/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O !/O Kepada/O Tim/O Catur/O Pelajar/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O Terima/O kasih/O sudah/O berjuang/O mengharumkan/O nama/O bangsa/O ./O Saya/O doakan/O agar/O terus/O berprestasi/O ./O 
<89>/O "Saya/O Ingin/O Ronaldo/PERSON Pensiun/O di/O Sporting/ORGANIZATION Lisbon/ORGANIZATION "/O https://t/O .co/zUQ8gxe56K/O https://t/O .co/F7wk8Hv9J3/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Memaafkan/O adalah/O tanda/O kekuatan/O hati/O ./O Tapi/O memaafkan/O tanpa/O menghormati/O diri/O adalah/O tanda/O lemahnya/O kecerdasan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Dirgahayu/O Tentara/O Nasional/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O Selalu/O setia/O membela/O kebenaran/O dan/O berada/O di/O sisi/O rakyat/O ./O 
<50>/O Hanura/ORGANIZATION Nilai/O Tak/O Relevan/O Hasil/O Pileg/O 014/O Dipakai/O untuk/O Usung/O Capres/O 019/O ./O https://t/O .co/bmz2HP6pCZ/O 
@aagym/O :/O Pembukaan/O SSG/O santri/O siap/O guna/O angkatan/O 31/O ,/O Menjadi/O pribadi/O Mandiri/O ,/O pelopor/O kebaikan/O dan/O berjiwa/O khidmat/O https://t.co/MCRA9XXOya/O 
@aagym/O :/O Jauhi/O komentar/O ,/O celetak/O celetuk/O ,/O pertanyaan/O iseng/O yang/O dapat/O merusak/O suasana/O ,/O kebersamaan/O dan/O merusak/O kebahagiaan/O orang/O lain/O 
<32>/O Jadwal/O Siaran/O Langsung/O Liga/O Champions/O Tengah/O Pekan/O Ini/O ./O https://t/O .co/uD78XPFSOo/O 
<87>/O Atletico/ORGANIZATION Madrid/ORGANIZATION Menang/O Tipis/O atas/O PSV/ORGANIZATION Eindhoven/ORGANIZATION https://t/O .co/aByBTFibTU/O https://t/O .co/evwQEl1GVf/O 
<52>/O Chris/PERSON Brown/PERSON Kembali/O Disorot/O Netizen/O https://t/O .co/6YslcrTIaY/O https://t/O .co/ujOsfRGKA4/O 
@infodishub/O :/O LIMA/O MASKAPAI/O AJUKAN/O TAMBAHAN/O PENERBANGAN/O SELAMA/O ANGKUTAN/O LEBARAN/O http://t.co/q6O2enIAJI/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Merayakan/O '/O Polkadot/O '/O Seniman/O Melegenda/O Yayoi/PERSON Kusama/PERSON https://t.co/P5UK9p6VQF/O via/O @detikhot/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PENERAPAN/O ERP/O DIMULAI/O AKHIR/O TAHUN/O 2015/O http://t.co/Xj7MHO6Zqv/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@aagym/O :/O Salah/O satu/O penyebab/O mengapa/O kita/O menderita/O https://t.co/ydMZ1Sko9D/O 
<46>/O Oezil/PERSON Senang/O Flamini/PERSON Gabung/O ke/O Crystal/ORGANIZATION Palace/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/BH7LP0VF1u/O 
<66>/O Pelita/O Hati:/O Jangan/O Menyerah/O (3)/O https://t/O .co/GWdGkOA6Gq/O https://t/O .co/GXXyVXyYV8/O 
@aagym/O :/O Masyarakat/O Denmark/LOCATION menjaga/O masjid/O dari/O penyerangan/O orang/O yang/O belum/O memahami/O indahnya/O Islam/O https://t.co/2oW650M14x/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Membanggakan/O ./O Tujuh/O bupati/O sepakat/O membangun/O Danau/LOCATION Toba/LOCATION ./O Toba/LOCATION akan/O jadi/O tujuan/O wisata/O dunia/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/uhnIMtENBT/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Pembelajaran/O ,/O kajian/O ,/O perbaikan/O sudah/O ;/O saatnya/O PSSI/ORGANIZATION bersama/O pelatih/O ,/O pemain/O ,/O pers/O bersatu/O ciptakan/O peluang/O &/O prestasi/O sepak/O bola/O INDONESIA/LOCATION !/O !/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Caballero/PERSON Berharap/O Hart/PERSON Lekas/O Pulih/O https://t.co/rpuqK4aJHY/O https://t.co/rh6H9MCi7B/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Investigasi/O Kecelakaan/O Alonso/PERSON dengan/O Gutierrez/PERSON Dihentikan/O https://t.co/U6ShIffu5X/O https://t.co/9DSgV2epZf/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Katakanlah/O Aamiin/O atau/O Retweet/O ,/O jika/O doa/O pagi/O ini/O adalah/O doa/O Anda/O juga/O ./O https://t.co/GiunYmeBvA/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Adakah/O peningkatan/O kualitas/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION FC/ORGANIZATION bersama/O manajer/O baru/O ?/O https://t.co/76Jge9IXg5/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Tak/O Semua/O Kejang/O Dikategorikan/O Epilepsi/O https://t.co/orybdCMpGi/O 
@aagym/O :/O Latihan/O fokus/O dan/O sabar/O serta/O berani/O dan/O banyak/O hikmah/O lainnya/O dari/O olahraga/O Sunnah/O yang/O penuh/O berkah/O https://t.co/AhYBuXYtrg/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O 2/O ./O Berjuang/O bersama/O demi/O keputusan/O terbaik/O untuk/O Indonesia/LOCATION yang/O lebih/O baik/O ./O Kebenaran/O dan/O kebaikan/O perlu/O diperjuangkan/O ./O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Berdiskusi/O dan/O makan/O siang/O bersama/O Bupati/O Purbalingga/LOCATION Bpk/O Tasdi/PERSON ./O Rabu/O 16/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/Yhxg7CXwkf/O 
<65>/O #News/O #ZonaMPR/O Ketua/O MPR/ORGANIZATION Zulkifli/PERSON Hasan/PERSON :/O Perkuat/O Kesalehan/O Sosial/O https://t.co/GGwqnDrE4f/O https://t.co/Iv65NeUmh3/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Dipanggil/O Kejati/ORGANIZATION ,/O La/PERSON Nyalla/PERSON Ancam/O Bakal/O Mangkir/O Lagi/O https://t.co/CO4tziaYL4/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Yuk/O ,/O nonton/O serunya/O laga/O bulu/O tangkis/O Putaran/O 2/O Yonex/ORGANIZATION All/O England/O di/O KompasTV/ORGANIZATION sesaat/O lagi/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O https://t.co/2HLNJfGklK/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Dari/ Buffon/PERSON untuk/O yang/O Senantiasa/O Dipunggunginya/O ,/O dengan/O Cinta/O https://t.co/4r3g435OBk/O https://t.co/xLx0Bwx3Yx/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O kader-kader/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Kenjeran/LOCATION ./O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/VQdAiS1fOr/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Cinta/O itu/O utuh/O ,/O dan/O tidak/O mampu/O untuk/O menjadi/O kurang/O dari/O lengkap/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@KompasTV/O :/O Djan/PERSON Faridz/PERSON Tanggapi/O Positif/O "/O Jaringan/O Suka/O Haji/PERSON Lulung/PERSON "/O https://t.co/LanfVGcxUz/O 
<13>/O Bocoran/O Sementara/O Spesifikasi/O Samsung/ORGANIZATION Galaxy/O A3/O 017/O https://t/O .co/kMxMKd37Dl/O https://t/O .co/SmqlXPeThX/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SartonoHutomo/O :/O @SBYudhoyono/O @Edhie_Baskoro/O @PDemokrat/O https://t.co/8LwnreuEAs/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Innalillahi/O waina/O ilaihi/O rojiun/O ,/O duka/O cita/O mendalam/O atas/O wafatnya/O KGPAA/O Paku/O Alam/O IX/O di/O RSUP/LOCATION dr/LOCATION ./O Sardjito/LOCATION Yogyakarta/LOCATION Semoga/O khusnul/O khotimah/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Bertanding/O di/O Brazil/LOCATION ,/O tim/O Indonesia/LOCATION berhasil/O mengalahkan/O pecatur/O dari/O bangsa-bangsa/O besar/O ./O Bangsa/O Eropa/LOCATION ,/O Amerika/LOCATION Latin/LOCATION ,/O Asia/LOCATION ,/O dst/O ./O 
<61>/O Jese/PERSON :/O Saya/O ke/O PSG/ORGANIZATION Bukan/O untuk/O Menjadi/O Pemain/O Cadangan/O ./O https://t/O .co/RvnA9ihSoH/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Ahok/PERSON Pusing/O Soal/O Pilgub/O DKI/LOCATION ,/O Pilih/O Fokus/O Garap/O APBD/O 2017/O https://t.co/CYqfXKzlRM/O https://t.co/OnvPHXcrKJ/O 
@infodishub/O :/O 2016/O ,/O INDONESIA/LOCATION MULAI/O MANFAATKAN/O BIO/O FUEL/O UNTUK/O PENERBANGAN/O http://t.co/0DXZw1uGpj/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Ibu/O Mufidah/PERSON Kalla/PERSON meresmikan/O pelepasan/O ekspor/O bunga/O krisan/O pertama/O ke/O Jepang/LOCATION ./O @husainabdullah1/O https://t.co/HWMnvICwL0/O 
<91>/O Makna/O Kurban/O Idul/O Adha/O Bagi/O Jokowi/PERSON https://t.co/RJPX2z2ZkR/O https://t.co/aWeknwNv5D/O 
<70>/O Survei/O CSIS/ORGANIZATION :/O Kalahkan/O Ahok/PERSON dan/O Prabowo/PERSON ,/O Jokowi/PERSON Tokoh/O Politik/O Terkuat/O Saat/O Ini/O ./O https://t/O .co/Jfo3HsuiAl/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Setiap/O 21/O April/O ,/O kita/O peringati/O Hari/O Kartini/PERSON untuk/O mengingat/O jasa/O beliau/O dalam/O menginspirasi/O kita/O semua/O akan/O pentingnya/O emansipasi/O perempuan/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Cara/O Pasang/O 2/O SIM/O Card/O dan/O 1/O Kartu/O Micro/O SD/O di/O Samsung/ORGANIZATION Galaxy/O S7/O Edge/O https://t.co/3SuYewkJBY/O https://t.co/Bbpr02sTar/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Saat/O Ahok/PERSON Membandingkan/O Gaji/O Pengemudi/O TransJ/O Lebih/O Besar/O dari/O Sopir/O Taksi/O https://t.co/p1o6fhky5o/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Polres/ORGANIZATION Jepara/LOCATION akan/O Tindak/O Tegas/O Angkutan/O Berpelat/O Hitam/O https://t.co/V30rItmykG/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selamat/O berpesta/O demokrasi/O ,/O agar/O bangsa/O negara/O menjadi/O semakin/O baik/O ./O http://t.co/mYiuoMuOgc/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Pengguna/O Instagram/ORGANIZATION Antusias/O Unggah/O Foto/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O https://t.co/PN0DOmmPQ5/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Uber/ORGANIZATION Rilis/O '/O Peta/O Harta/O Karun/O '/O untuk/O Hacker/O https://t.co/eOdZSoLSjk/O via/O @detikinet/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Pembangunan/O Infrastruktur/O Jadi/O Prioritas/O Pengawasan/O KPK/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/jAFye1dJM6/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O para/O pimpinan/O perusahaan/O pemenang/O Apresiasi/O SINDO/O CSR/O 2016/O kategori/O Kesehatan/O ./O https://t.co/6YV2HyjPwe/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Yamaha/ORGANIZATION Segera/O Luncurkan/O Motor/O Matik/O dan/O Sport/O https://t.co/QDpiVarPAx/O 
<61>/O LPS/ORGANIZATION Turunkan/O Suku/O Bunga/O Penjaminan/O Simpanan/O 50/O Bps/O https://t/O .co/dSdKn1uJ5w/O https://t/O .co/J64okRgHJ1/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Bersih/O Lingkungan/O ,/O Yess/O !/O Stop/O Narkoba/O ,/O Yess/O !/O Hidup/O Sehat/O ,/O Yess/O !/O Tes/O urine/O serentak/O ?/O (/O Mubazir/O Brpkali/O )/O Apa/O iya/O perlu/O ./O ./O "/O Gajebo/O "/O deh/O #GakJelas/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Menerima/O @Yusrilihza_Mhd/O yg/O akan/O meluncurkan/O buku/O Ensiklopedia/O dlm/O rangka/O Ultah/O ke-60/O https://t.co/4Id31Dij5c/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Maju/O mundur/O ekonomi/O suatu/O bangsa/O tidak/O dilihat/O dari/O kursnya/O tetapi/O sebarapa/O banyak/O lapangan/O kerja/O yg/O tersedia/O ./O https://t.co/aLlCNmivGC/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Aamiin/O ,/O bung/O @AMislan10/O ./O Terima/O kasih/O ./O Mari/O kita/O sama-sama/O mendoakan/O agar/O amal/O ibadah/O beliau/O diterima/O oleh/O Allah/O SWT/O ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Jadi/O orang/O yang/O mudah/O tersinggung/O itu/O sangat/O cape/O dan/O menderita/O ,/O jadi/O orang/O yang/O pemaaf/O dan/O berlapang/O dada/O itu/O nyamaan/O sekali/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Ribuan/O Hektar/O Padi/O Mati/O Diserang/O Hama/O https://t.co/QluXHbYVO1/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Kontribusi/O sains/O &/O teknologi/O terhadap/O ekonomi/O hijau/O &/O pembangunan/O berkelanjutan-Penganugerahan/O doktor/O kehormatan/O ITB/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/DY4MfIDNwp/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Membanggakan/O !/O Fransiska/PERSON Dimitri/PERSON Inkiriwang/PERSON &/O Mathilda/PERSON Dwi/PERSON Lestari/PERSON dari/O Unpar/ORGANIZATION bisa/O menaklukkan/O Aconcagua/LOCATION ,/O puncak/O tertinggi/O benua/O Amerika/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Amerika/LOCATION Godok/O RUU/O untuk/O Menghukum/O Apple/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/ihp8X2adw0/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Rebut/O hadiah/O ratusan/O ribu/O rupiah/O dengan/O mengikuti/O Lomba/O Thread/O Of/O the/O Month/O (/O TOM/O )/O VIVAForum/O https://t.co/tqjyyBccUy/O https://t.co/BcY2T9PurI/O 
<36>/O Enrique/PERSON :/O Messi/PERSON Pemain/O Terbaik/O Sepanjang/O Masa!/O https://t/O .co/bSkIp5nnL1/O https://t/O .co/V9MDy3Tupc/O 
@aagym/O :/O Ayoo/O periksa/O berulang/O ulang/O niat/O kita/O dalam/O berbuat/O apapun/O ./O ./O ./O https://t.co/pcJx6o9QWo/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Selamatkan/O Anjing/O ,/O Wanita/O Berjilbab/O ini/O Tuai/O Pujian/O https://t.co/GYe3I7t4MC/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Yuk/O ,/O nonton/O Putaran/O 2/O Yonex/ORGANIZATION All/O England/O malam/O ini/O pukul/O 19/O ./O 30/O WIB/O dan/O ikuti/O kuis/O berhadiahnya/O ./O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O https://t.co/ORRWPqBMXJ/O 
<67>/O Horor/O di/O Kapal/O Pesiar/O Terbesar/O di/O Dunia/O ,/O Satu/O Tewas/O dan/O Dua/O Kritis/O ./O https://t/O .co/mi7aainJND/O 
<17>/O Sebentar/O Lagi/O ,/O Anda/O Bisa/O Buat/O Kicauan/O Lebih/O Panjang/O di/O Twitter/ORGANIZATION https://t/O .co/yWyk0lDHsv/O https://t/O .co/Kaj5dirE84/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Dispekulasikan/O Telah/O Kehilangan/O Kendali/O Ruang/O Ganti/O City/ORGANIZATION ,/O Pellegrini/PERSON Menepis/O https://t.co/xutYMnph2b/O https://t.co/I0eQFBES8K/O 
<26>/O Model/O Dunia/O Berpenghasilan/O Tertinggi/O https://t.co/tlrSCOtLrr/O https://t.co/K3Ebw7hpIZ/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Orang/O biasanya/O sulit/O berlaku/O tegas/O jika/O dia/O masih/O membutuhkan/O bantuan/O dari/O orang/O yang/O harus/O ditegasinya/O ./O MT/PERSON 
@basuki_btp/O :/O Syukurlah/O penganggaran/O APBD/O berbasis/O ebudgeting/O kami/O telah/O diterima/O dan/O disetujui/O oleh/O pihak/O kemendagri/O ./O Kami/O bisa/O fokus/O bekerja/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Bongkar/O Muat/O di/O Tanjung/LOCATION Priok/LOCATION Dijanjikan/O Dua/O Hari/O https://t.co/cugbLiO4IT/O 
@aagym/O :/O Suasana/O sepertiga/O malam/O terakhir/O di/O masjid/LOCATION nabawi/LOCATION ,/O semoga/O sahabat/O semua/O diundang/O Alloh/O ke/O tanah/O suci/O https://t.co/elot8wCa55/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Mulailah/O memikirkan/O cara/O agar/O orang/O membayar/O Anda/O Rp/O ./O 10/O ,/O 000/O ,/O -/O dengan/O senang/O ,/O agar/O jelas/O jalan/ naik/O Anda/O menuju/O bayaran/O besar/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<3>/O Ahok/PERSON :/O Amien/PERSON Rais/PERSON ,/O Khotbah/O Jangan/O Dipakai/O untuk/O Politik/O https://t.co/jTtHWl5o78/O https://t.co/23PoMNtDwj/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Ketahuan/O Sopir/O Blue/ORGANIZATION Bird/ORGANIZATION Minta/O Tarif/O ,/O Izin/O Operasi/O Disetop/O https://t.co/TOpySXqSrC/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Keylor/PERSON Navas/PERSON tentang/O Kerja/O Keras/O ,/O El/O Clasico/O ,/O dan/O Liga/O Champions/O https://t.co/H2w6POgGQY/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O RT/O @KotaJaksel/O :/O JKT/LOCATION Baru/O tdk/O sekedar/O slogan/O ,/O JKT/LOCATION Bersih/O nyata/O adanya/O @KotaJaksel/O cc/O @slankdotcom/O @basuki_btp/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 21/O :/O 46/O ,/O 7/O WIB/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Bandung/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Lihainya/O Keylor/PERSON Navas/PERSON dalam/O Duel/O di/O Titik/O 12/O Pas/O https://t.co/LC1tw5QFYL/O https://t.co/5lm5ITZ7gV/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Pelantikan/O pengurus/O DPC-DPC/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION se-Dapil/O 11/O Jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION ./O Madura/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/Vnno4POUmX/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Anak/O muda/O yang/O super/O ,/O bekerja/O untuk/O digaji/O ,/O tapi/O dia/O menaikkan/O kepantasannya/O untuk/O digaji/O dengan/O baik/O sekali/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O "/O Persatuan/O &/O Kesatuan/O ,/O kedamaian/O ,/O keadilan/O &/O Krisis/O lingkungan/O di/O dunia/O juga/O memerlukan/O perhatian/O "/O #SalatigaMeeting/O https://t.co/nIcX4yOwbm/O 
@detikcom/O :/O PDIP/ORGANIZATION Bicara/O Deparpolisasi/O ,/O NasDem/ORGANIZATION :/O Itu/O Upaya/O Melemahkan/O Ahok/PERSON https://t.co/RvSSATRjkf/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Dokter/O Penghina/O Pemkot/O Semarang/LOCATION via/O Medsos/O Shock/O ,/O Tak/O Jawab/O soal/O Motif/O https://t.co/Ngt95vRiBs/O 
@infodishub/O :/O WAMENHUB/O :/O PASTIKAN/O KAPAL/O ANGKUTAN/O LEBARAN/O LAIK/O LAUT/O http://t.co/TeTcExoF1C/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@detikcom/O :/O XL/ORGANIZATION Jual/O Menara/O &/O Lepas/O Saham/O Demi/O Bayar/O Utang/O Beli/O Axis/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/yl9kxxOJXj/O via/O @detikinet/O https://t.co/GeGIOsRIVo/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O Bupati/O Kabupaten/O Cirebon/LOCATION Bpk/O Sunjaya/PERSON Purwadisastra/PERSON di/O Pendopo/LOCATION Kabupaten/LOCATION Cirebon/LOCATION ./O Rabu/O 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/3uWK0J30OP/O 
<11>/O Anak/O Pilih/O Puding/O daripada/O "Shooting"/O ,/O Iis/PERSON Dahlia/PERSON Bangga/O ./O https://t/O .co/5bhmiH2Yal/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Turki/LOCATION -/O Yunani/LOCATION Tandatangani/O Kesepakatan/O Kerja/O Sama/O Migran/O https://t.co/MtEyY4UBrC/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Pulau/LOCATION Pianemo/LOCATION Raja/LOCATION Ampat/LOCATION ,/O sangat/O indah/O ./O Surga/O kecil/O di/O Tanah/LOCATION Papua/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/cnBCXGeez6/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Siap/O Lawan/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O Yusril/PERSON :/O Hampir/O Semua/O Partai/ORGANIZATION Politik/O Sudah/O Saya/O Temui/O https://t.co/X37ru8hce0/O 
<22>/O RT/O @GNTMetroTV:/O Mahasiswi/O @UnikaWM/O sulap/O barang/O bekas/O jadi/O alat/O penyaring/O asap/O https://t/O .co/WQvykWdhyj/O @Metro_TV/O https://t/O .co/78vmkh6WG9/O 
@jokowi/O :/O 6/O ./O Saya/O juga/O menuliskan/O impian/O saya/O sebagai/O rangkuman/O impian/O rakyat/O ,/O "/O Impian/O Indonesia/LOCATION "/O untuk/O 70/O tahun/O kedepan/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/FQUnqUXEWk/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Jangan/O Cuma/O Bermotif/O Menjegal/O ,/O Para/O Penantang/O Ahok/PERSON Harus/O Berkompetisi/O Sehat/O https://t.co/Kd6jak2TZq/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O Pagi/O ini/O saya/O akan/O memantau/O pelaksanaan/O hari/O pertama/O UN/O smp/O di/O jakarta/LOCATION ./O Sebagai/O gubernur/O ya/O ,/O bukan/O komika/O standup/O comedy/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Bangsa/O Indonesia/LOCATION kehilangan/O JS/O Badudu/O ./O Sepanjang/O hidupnya/O diabdikan/O untuk/O bahasa/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O Pengabdiannya/O jadi/O teladan/O kita/O bersama/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @ulil/O makasih/O ,/O mas/O ./O Sukses/O juga/O untuk/O mas/O Ulil/PERSON ./O Mari/O maju/O bersama/O ./O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Singgah/O di/O Angkringan/LOCATION Sejahtera/LOCATION ,/O UMKM/O binaan/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Kenjeran/LOCATION ./O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/rDAZA8j2gX/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Serius/O Mewaspadai/O Ducati/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/5cvMyG05es/O https://t.co/UhasvePMop/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Arahan/O Ketum/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION dalam/O pelantikan/O DPC-DPC/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION se-Dapil/O 11/O Jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION ./O Madura/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/X8KkA0xfnv/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Diskusi/O bersama/O Rektor/O UPN/ORGANIZATION &/O UGM/ORGANIZATION utk/O tingkatkan/O kualitas/O pendidikan/O Perguruan/O Tinggi/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION #Kunker/O #Komisi10/O https://t.co/9AL5UYFqGv/O 
@infodishub/O :/O RT/O @fs_massinai/O :/O "/O @VIVAnews/O :/O Turut/O Prihatin/O ,/O Bos/O AirAsia/ORGANIZATION :/O Kita/O Harus/O Tetap/O Kuat/O http://t.co/cyrl1UNLUQ/O http://t.co/UUCCLnFXmp/O "/O @infodishub/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Memberi/O arahan/O mengenai/O pemasangan/O sound/O system/O di/O Masjid/LOCATION Balai/LOCATION Kota/LOCATION Tua/LOCATION 18/O //O 3/O ./O https://t.co/HOm3IqD39W/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Djarot/PERSON Bantah/O Berkonflik/O dengan/O Ahok/PERSON https://t.co/JVFglJeBNn/O https://t.co/oL8CNbFRFM/O 
<9>/O Bebani/O Koruptor/O dengan/O Biaya/O Sosial/O ./O https://t/O .co/gWqiqCDK5A/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Silat/O Lidah/O Anas/PERSON vs/O Nazaruddin/PERSON di/O Pengadilan/O Tipikor/O https://t.co/CqcThNbl5Z/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O bantuan/O pendidikan/O pada/O mahasiswa/O -/O mahasiswi/O berprestasi/O Fakultas/O Ekonomi/O Universitas/ORGANIZATION Negeri/ORGANIZATION Padang/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t.co/W2ERX82nM9/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Southampton/ORGANIZATION Perpendek/O Ketinggalan/O dari/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION di/O Babak/O Kedua/O https://t.co/r2EPF3g0yp/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Salut/O ,/O Hendra/PERSON //O Ahsan/PERSON menjuarai/O badminton/O Dubai/LOCATION BWF/O Super/O Series/O ./O Indonesia/LOCATION bangga/O ./O #TerimaKasihHendraAhsan/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@Metro_TV/O :/O 20/O Tahun/O Berkarya/O ,/O Ada/O Band/O Luncurkan/O Album/O '/O Chemistry/O '/O https://t.co/6OU7k3RyOK/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Alhamdulillah/O ,/O genap/O sewindu/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION berkiprah/O di/O dunia/O politik/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O Bukan/O sesuatu/O yang/O mudah/O ./O 
@detikcom/O :/O Rio/PERSON Haryanto/PERSON di/O Antara/O Hamilton/PERSON ,/O Kimi/PERSON ,/O dan/O Vettel/PERSON https://t.co/F8osqQ6aag/O via/O @detiksport/O https://t.co/bm6dAyARgp/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Smartfren/ORGANIZATION Jamin/O VoLTE/O Juga/O Aktif/O di/O Andromax/O Lawas/O https://t.co/Dx7iTTvRpV/O https://t.co/fjMxUtLA3V/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Pendidikan/O adalah/O hak/O dan/O kewajiban/O segenap/O warga/O negara/O ./O Meratanya/O pendidikan/O adalah/O cita-cita/O kita/O ./O Mari/O wujudkan/O bersama/O ./O #HariPendidikan/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Nikmati/O Soto/O Betawi/O yang/O Gurih/O Hangat/O di/O 5/O Tempat/O Ini/O https://t.co/cv5JJRtXQp/O via/O @detikfood/O https://t.co/ajejNLajFf/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Anak/O muda/O yang/O malas/O melakukan/O yang/O baik/O ,/O sesungguhnya/O sedang/O rajin/O memburukkan/O kehidupannya/O sendiri/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Membuka/O secara/O resmi/O Muktamar/O VI/O dan/O Milad/O ICMI/O ke-25/O Lombok/LOCATION https://t.co/LvQMMTbZJY/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Pencarian/O Korban/O Longsor/O Hotel/O Club/O Bali/LOCATION Dilakukan/O dengan/O Berteriak/O https://t.co/mcREqtL2KE/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O sore/O sahabat/O ./O Hari/O ini/O ,/O 6/O Februari/O ,/O tujuh/O tahun/O yang/O lalu/O ,/O adalah/O hari/O berdirinya/O Partai/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION ./O http://t.co/e4hQ7Zq2Ro/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O siang/O bung/O @SutantoVjay93/O ./O Saya/O selalu/O buka/O FB/O dan/O Twitter/ORGANIZATION saya/O saat/O ada/O kesempatan/O ./O Mohon/O sampaikan/O salam/O saya/O untuk/O teman-teman/O ./O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Polri/ORGANIZATION Bersiap/O Tahan/O 2/O Tersangka/O Kasus/O Korupsi/O Pengadaan/O UPS/O https://t.co/SjgJRH0yz5/O 
@infodishub/O :/O JUMLAH/O PEMUDIK/O MENGGUNAKAN/O MOBIL/O PRIBADI/O NAIK/O 8/O ,/O 64/O %/O http://t.co/w5S0cqYSO7/O #BeritaPusat/O 
<7>/O Uber/O Kian/O Menggurita/O ,/O Taksi/O Legendaris/O London/LOCATION Terancam/O ./O https://t/O .co/tUUXteV242/O 
<31>/O Mau/O tahu/O alasan/O Arsene/PERSON Wenger/PERSON menolak/O PSG/ORGANIZATION sampai/O kali?/O Cek/O di/O sini/O .https://t/O .co/UAxirM61W3/O https://t/O .co/fRCbRxvWFE/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Betapa/O baik/O pun/O yang/O Anda/O lakukan/O untuk/O orang/O lain/O ,/O akan/O selalu/O ada/O orang/O yang/O mencela/O ./O Tetaplah/O upayakan/O yang/O terbaik/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<10>/O [Populer]/O Serang/O Trump/O ,/O Obama/PERSON 'Kampanye'/O Gantikan/O Clinton/PERSON https://t/O .co/5n6cqsbR43/O https://t/O .co/Jge3gEUjxf/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Selamat/O untuk/O PERSIB/ORGANIZATION yang/O menjadi/O Juara/O Piala/O Presiden/O 2015/O ./O 
@detiksport/O :/O Gol/O memang/O tidak/O terjadi/O atas/O backpass/O berbahaya/O tersebut/O ./O Tapi/O itu/O membuat/O Hart/PERSON mengalami/O cedera/O saat/O menyapu/O bola/O dari/O kejaran/O Martial/PERSON ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O mudah/O terpancing/O oleh/O hal/O yang/O tak/O enak/O ,/O jangan/O mudah/O Tersulut/O emosinya/O ,/O biasakan/O tenang/O dan/O jernih/O dalam/O segala/O situasi/O 
@infodishub/O :/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION BUKA/O PENDAFTARAN/O MUDIK/O GRATIS/O PESEPEDA/O MOTOR/O http://t.co/A6VUeIUY91/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@jokowi/O :/O 8/O ./O Hari/O ini/O di/O Merauke/LOCATION ,/O ujung/O paling/O timur/O Indonesia/LOCATION ,/O saya/O letakkan/O Kapsul/O Waktu/O :/O Impian/O Indonesia/LOCATION 2015-2085/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/LUXYvAQf1F/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Tak/O Sekadar/O Pikun/O ,/O Demensia/O dan/O Alzheimer/O Tergolong/O Penyakit/O Berat/O https://t.co/xgixBaSi04/O via/O @detikHealth/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Pembangunan/O #infrastruktur/O di/O desa/LOCATION tidak/O kalah/O penting/O dibanding/O kota2/O besar/O ./O Infrastruktur/O salah/O satu/O pendukung/O kegiatan/O perekonomian/O warga/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Jatuh/O itu/O biasa/O ,/O tapi/O jangan/O lama/O berbaring/O di/O situ/O ./O Masih/O banyak/O yang/O bisa/O kita/O lakukan/O untuk/O memperbaiki/O keadaan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@detiksport/O :/O Southampton/ORGANIZATION Perpendek/O Ketertinggalan/O dari/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION di/O Babak/O Kedua/O https://t.co/8ETFw4LncY/O 
@infodishub/O :/O FOKUS/O 2015/O ,/O PENGUTAN/O KONEKTIVITAS/O NASIONAL/O dan/O PENGEMBANGAN/O SISTEM/O TRANSPORTASI/O MASSAL/O PERKOTAAN/O http://t.co/cchnijQou0/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@aagym/O :/O Bagi/O saudaraku/O para/O mualaf/O silakan/O manfaatkan/O acara/O besok/O di/O Dt/LOCATION Bandung/LOCATION yaa/O https://t.co/jLaz77t7DB/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Semoga/O dgn/O Taman/O Teknologi/O Pertanian/O ini/O ,/O petani/O bisa/O tersenyum/O karena/O biaya/O bertani/O lbh/O hemat/O ,/O efektif/O &/O efisien/O https://t.co/Myj9MnAP7F/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Berawal/O dari/O Pertemanan/O ,/O Aming/PERSON Jadi/O Sutradara/O Film/O '/O #GilaJiwa/O '/O https://t.co/x0pumEghfO/O via/O @detikhot/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Insya/O Allah/O aspirasi/O itu/O kami/O sampaikan/O ./O @FPD_DPR/O berharap/O pemerintah/O mau/O menerima/O segala/O saran/O maupun/O koreksi/O yg/O diberikan/O ./O #SBYTourDeJava/O 
<51>/O Patrice/O Evra/O yakin/O timnya/O punya/O peluang/O besar/O untuk/O menjuarai/O Liga/O Champions/O musim/O ini/O ./O Sependapat?https://t/O .co/DfYusggjlb/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Demo/O Tolak/O Uber/ORGANIZATION ,/O Pengusaha/O Rental/O Bakal/O Temui/O Dishub/ORGANIZATION DKI/LOCATION https://t.co/vYidO0CxXK/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O buku/O dari/O Bupati/O Indragiri/LOCATION Hulu/LOCATION Bpk/O Yopi/PERSON Arianto/PERSON ./O Indragiri/LOCATION Hulu/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 10/O Maret/O 2016/O https://t.co/1XY1e6ryxS/O 
@infodishub/O :/O WAMENHUB/O :/O SISTEM/O TRANSPORTASI/O ke/O DEPAN/O TAK/O BISA/O ANDALKAN/O SATU/O MODA/O http://t.co/LCLC2y5OCC/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O BNI/ORGANIZATION Bagi-bagi/O Dividen/O Rp2,26/O Triliun/O https://t.co/oHefgfJJdv/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Tiket/O Kereta/O Long/O Weekend/O 25-27/O Maret/O Sebagian/O Besar/O Ludes/O Terjual/O https://t.co/XpBLKxzj21/O https://t.co/oXCU4Yr5IT/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Siaga/O &/O Dukung/O Pihak/O Kepolisian/ORGANIZATION ,/O TNI/ORGANIZATION ,/O BIN/ORGANIZATION &/O aparat/O bersikap/O tegas/O ,/O dapat/O menyelidiki/O hingga/O tuntas/O peristiwa/O #bom/O yg/O terjadi/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION 
@infodishub/O :/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION dan/O PT/ORGANIZATION ./O KAI/ORGANIZATION TANDATANGANI/O PERJANJIAN/O KERJASAMA/O KA/O BANDARA/O http://t.co/DGbeU1DNjg/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Jangan/O lewatkan/O laga/O bulu/O tangkis/O kelas/O dunia/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O hari/O ini/O pukul/O 19/O ./O 30/O WIB/O LIVE/O dari/O Birmingham/LOCATION !/O https://t.co/VMZ6oU1X59/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Kupang/LOCATION adalah/O lokasi/O dengan/O ketertutupan/O Matahari/O paling/O kecil/O dari/O semua/O lokasi/O pengamatan/O #GMT9Mar16/O yang/O dilaksanakan/O oleh/O #BMKG/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Sudah/O siap/O ketawa/O brg/O di/O Jagonya/O Comic/O The/O Battle/O KFC/ORGANIZATION Kantor/O Pos/O ?/O Acara/O ini/O dipersembahkan/O @KFCINDONESIA/O #Ad/O https://t.co/xcKX2j9kOs/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O RT/O @CimuetQaqa/O :/O Waktunya/O nonton/O all/O england/O Terima/O kasih/O @KompasTV/O yg/O udh/O nanyangin/O all/O england/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Dengan/O pelantikan/O ini/O total/O DPC/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION yang/O telah/O dilantik/O sebanyak/O 2/O ./O 651/O DPC/O ./O Cirebon/LOCATION 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/B5wHiiGapg/O 
<82>/O Chelsea/ORGANIZATION Gagal/O Pertahankan/O Tren/O Kemenangan/O ./O https://t/O .co/YvUplhm5zp/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Sempat/O Tertinggal/O di/O Babak/O Pertama/O ,/O Napoli/ORGANIZATION Kalahkan/O Genoa/ORGANIZATION 3-1/O https://t.co/g5Ozmd58tM/O https://t.co/zQVuINTQIi/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @CHOKYPARHAS/O kalau/O untuk/O Pilpres/O kali/O ini/O ,/O saya/O dukung/O nomor/O 1/O ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Waspada/O beli/O sendal/O atau/O sepatu/O ,/O ada/O yg/O dengan/O niat/O buruk/O membuat/O produk/O menggunakan/O lafadz/O Alloh/O ,/O naudzubillah/O http://t.co/pyLbyDwJX4/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Peringatan/O Dini/O Cuaca/O Jabodetabek/LOCATION tgl/O ./O 09/O Maret/O 2016/O ,/O pkl/O 14/O ./O 30/O WIB/O ./O Berpotensi/O terjadi/O hujan/O (/O cont/O )/O https://t.co/QAeB9OnbKb/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Oezil/PERSON Dikabarkan/O Menuju/O Pintu/O Keluar/O Arsenal/ORGANIZATION Andai/O Wenger/PERSON Bertahan/O https://t.co/eWoH2XwE2T/O https://t.co/RfA0R1Nx7O/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O RT/O @tvOneNews/O :/O Masih/O Bersama/O Wapres/O @Pak_JK/O dalam/O Wawancara/O Eksklusif/O @karniilyas/O https://t.co/vgLCaY5693/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O RT/O @PoskoDPUDKI/O :/O @BinaMargaJakBar/O Pek/O Jl/LOCATION ./O Joglo/LOCATION Raya/LOCATION ,/O Kembangan/O @basuki_btp/O http://t.co/UX6wqfFzQB/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Puluhan/O Advokat/O Berkumpul/O ,/O Tolak/O Kriminalisasi/O Cagub/O DKI/LOCATION 2017/O https://t.co/CWBSKXNbms/O https://t.co/YsqqzeG35i/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Penjelasan/O Blue/ORGANIZATION Bird/ORGANIZATION Terkait/O Ditangkapnya/O Feri/PERSON Yanto/PERSON karena/O Status/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION Provokasi/O https://t.co/BByQxL590Y/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Van/PERSON Gaal/PERSON Tak/O Aman/O ,/O Gattuso/PERSON Ngotot/O Mau/O Latih/O MU/ORGANIZATION '/O Besok/O '/O https://t.co/8dYSDOlSAC/O 
<91>/O Debutan/O Liga/O Champions/O ,/O Leicester/ORGANIZATION Ingin/O Ikut/O Jejak/O Nottingham/ORGANIZATION Forest/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/15TDaG5gBb/O 
<62>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O Surga/O Cantik/O Itu/O Terlihat/O Jelas/O dari/O Puncak/LOCATION Pulau/LOCATION Padar/LOCATION https://t.co/G1esIYuu5p/O https://t.co/YYBOGYcAMV/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Ini/O Jajaran/O Komisaris/O dan/O Direksi/O Baru/O BNI/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/XBw4Vd80ID/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Insya/O Allah/O ./O 
@detikcom/O :/O Tak/O Hanya/O Serang/O Orang/O Dewasa/O ,/O Penyakit/O Ginjal/O Juga/O '/O Incar/O '/O Anak-anak/O https://t.co/viGQE0hV8j/O via/O @detikHealth/O https://t.co/VFLByuFckL/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Investor/O Blok/O Masela/O Diyakini/O Akan/O Bertahan/O https://t.co/2ORBNYvayb/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Tapi/O alhamdulillah/O masih/O banyak/O anak/O dari/O keluarga/O miskin/O yang/O jujur/O dan/O rajin/O ,/O yang/O semoga/O menjadi/O para/O pemimpin/O masa/O depan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@aagym/O :/O Silakan/O simak/O jam/O 5-6/O pagi/O ini/O di/O TVRI/ORGANIZATION pusat/O tentang/O sabar/O dan/O sholat/O kunci/O pembuka/O pertolongan/O Alloh/O https://t.co/6pdB57B2h1/O 
<12>/O Akhirnya/O Man/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Menang/O Lagi/O di/O Old/LOCATION Trafford/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/kGIcIYzBao/O 
<99>/O Mabes/O Polri/ORGANIZATION Gelar/O Acara/O Pisah/O Sambut/O Wakapolri/O https://t/O .co/T7Yw3yZNkU/O https://t/O .co/dSb1O0czvT/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Di/O Ternate/LOCATION ,/O lama/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O adalah/O 2/O menit/O 40/O ,/O 8/O detik/O ,/O yaitu/O antara/O pukul/O 09/O :/O 51/O :/O 41/O ,/O 1/O WITA/O 09/O :/O 54/O :/O 21/O ,/O 9/O WITA/O ./O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Satpam/O Makelar/O Unit/O Rusun/LOCATION Marunda/LOCATION Dicokok/O https://t.co/OltlGPXjDp/O 
@aagym/O :/O Lihatlah/O bagaimana/O arti/O sujud/O bagi/O seorang/O mualaf/O ,/O mengapa/O kita/O banyak/O menyia-nyiakan/O nikmatnya/O sujud/O https://t.co/3r1xklyqHZ/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Tembus/O 11/O ./O 000/O Kaki/O ,/O Drone/O Ini/O bak/O Pesawat/O Terbang/O https://t.co/CxK1C29500/O via/O @detikinet/O https://t.co/1XmIwuF3wa/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Kendalikan/O emosi/O Anda/O ./O Anak/O muda/O yang/O kendali/O emosinya/O baik/O ,/O lebih/O dewasa/O daripada/O orang/O tua/O yang/O pemarah/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Parade/O Duel/O Bergengsi/O Antarnegara/O Sepanjang/O Pekan/O ini/O https://t.co/gY00B6kc0Z/O 
<16>/O 9/O Tanda/O Anda/O dan/O Pasangan/O Ditakdirkan/O Bersama/O Selamanya/O https://t.co/O k0H7KFdT5/O https://t.co/1z67nfQnjA/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Kemarin/O saya/O ke/O pembangunan/O stasiun/O kereta/O api/O Bandara/LOCATION Minangkabau/LOCATION ./O Des/O 2015/O bisa/O digunakan/O masyarakat/O Sumbar/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON http://t.co/PnSrVBuGpV/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersilaturahmi/O dengan/O Ketua/O Umum/O Pengurus/O Besar/O Nahdlatul/ORGANIZATION Ulama/ORGANIZATION ,/O Bpk/O KH/O Said/PERSON Aqil/PERSON di/O Pondok/ORGANIZATION Pesantren/ORGANIZATION Al-Tsaqafah/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/xmgDsykGkQ/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 10/O :/O 17/O :/O 39/O ,/O 9/O WIT/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Jayapura/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION oh/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION ./O ./O ./O ./O https://t.co/hW7MZzu4ka/O 
@aagym/O :/O Tugas/O kita/O bukan/O untuk/O tebar/O pesona/O melainkan/O tebar/O manfaat/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O keluarga/O dalam/O perayaan/O ulang/O tahun/O istri/O ,/O Liliana/PERSON Tanoesoedibjo/PERSON ./O Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O Minggu/O ,/O 20/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/OrDh1hddL3/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Setelah/O pertemuan/O kami/O yang/O bermanfaat/O ,/O Presiden/O Obama/PERSON mengajak/O menyusuri/O Rose/LOCATION Garden/LOCATION yang/O bersejarah/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/uD5ldho6TH 
@KompasTV/O :/O Revisi/O UU/O Pilkada/O Diminta/O Pertegas/O Sanksi/O Politik/O Uang/O https://t.co/qChh9kmr29/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Meninjau/O studio/O radio/O bersama/O Datuk/PERSON Seri/PERSON Fateh/PERSON Iskandar/PERSON dan/O Seelan/PERSON Paul/PERSON ,/O CEO/O Media/ORGANIZATION Prima/ORGANIZATION Radio/ORGANIZATION Networks/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/Ha8VKmhA17/O 
<26>/O Peluncuran/O The/O Last/O Guardian/O Mundur/O Sampai/O Desember/O https://t/O .co/kCIv50QI04/O https://t/O .co/iZEnI5qrxR/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Prakiraan/O Cuaca/O pada/O saat/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O Total/O #GMT9Mar16/O -/O update/O 8/O Maret/O 2016/O pukul/O 20/O ./O 00/O WIB/O https://t.co/roB6uUkmRJ/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selamat/O hari/O kemerdekaan/O RI/ORGANIZATION ./O Sekali/O merdeka/O ,/O tetap/O merdeka/O ./O Jaga/O terus/O persatuan/O ,/O hargai/O perjuangan/O pahlawan/O ./O 
<74>/O Survei/O CSIS/ORGANIZATION :/O Pesona/O Jokowi/PERSON Masih/O Pikat/O Hati/O Pemilih/O Perempuan/O https://t.co/h6G8d6e4t9/O 
<16>/O Putri/O Iis/PERSON Dahlia/PERSON Berjualan/O Puding/O di/O "Car/O Free/O Day"/O ./O https://t/O .co/sopJpdTsQ9/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Singapura/LOCATION Masih/O Jadi/O Kota/O dengan/O Biaya/O Hidup/O Termahal/O di/O Dunia/O https://t.co/CQB2vOicza/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Hidup/O ini/O tentang/O kebaikan/O ./O Kalau/O Anda/O baik/O untuk/O orang/O lain/O ,/O kebaikan/O Anda/O menjadi/O urusan/O langsung/O Tuhan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O suka/O mempersulit/O diri/O dan/O mendramatisir/O masalah/O ,/O tetap/O tenang/O ./O ./O Ada/O Alloh/O yang/O maha/O dekat/O dan/O maha/O baik/O sudah/O mengukur/O segalanya/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Saya/O ingatkan/O juga/O ,/O jangan/O golput/O ./O Pilihlah/O yang/O sesuai/O dengan/O harapan/O teman-teman/O ,/O yg/O dirasa/O akan/O membawa/O RI/ORGANIZATION lbh/O maju/O lagi/O ./O 
@prabowo/O :/O @siti_muawanah_7/O Terima/O kasih/O Siti/PERSON ./O Mohon/O sampaikan/O salam/O saya/O untuk/O keluarga/O saudara/O ./O 
@prabowo/O :/O @elqieot/O Semoga/O sukses/O ./O 
@detikcom/O :/O Leonardo/PERSON DiCaprio/PERSON Sapa/O Fans/O di/O Jepang/LOCATION https://t.co/O8rBHq6yJV/O via/O @detikhot/O https://t.co/CHqEMOwdY5/O 
<34>/O Risma/PERSON Deportasi/O 6/O Tenaga/O Kerja/O Asing/O Ilegal/O ./O https://t/O .co/2jbToB2piT/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Berbagi/O pengalaman/O membangun/O usaha/O dan/O wawasan/O kebangsaan/O kepada/O ribuan/O santri/O Pondok/ORGANIZATION Pesantren/ORGANIZATION Al/ORGANIZATION Falah/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t.co/tZ7ym2doXi/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Akun/O instagram/ORGANIZATION saya/O yang/O resmi/O ini/O :/O https://t.co/8vlQtgMaLM/O ./O Yang/O lain/O bukan/O akun/O saya/O lho/O ya/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/FWA7vF3eeg/O 
<73>/O Joko/O Anwar/O Terilhami/O Lukisan/O Abad/O ke-19/O ./O https://t/O .co/ywXAeTBcnl/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Ingin/O hidari/O macet/O ?/O Pantau/O CCTV/O jalur/O berkendara/O Anda/O di/O sini/O https://t.co/waVIHk9rKw/O #infolalinVIVA/O @lewatmana/O https://t.co/RwMtanKPmV/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Nikmati/O Soto/O Betawi/O yang/O Gurih/O Hangat/O di/O 5/O Tempat/O Ini/O https://t.co/cv5JJRcmYR/O via/O @detikFood/O https://t.co/wj6gGbkDaH/O 
@infodishub/O :/O MRT/O MAMPU/O ALIHKAN/O LEBIH/O dari/O 20/O PERSEN/O PENGGUNA/O KENDARAAN/O PRIBADI/O http://t.co/4hmZbseZcK/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Djan/PERSON Faridz/PERSON Usung/O Lulung/PERSON Jadi/O Cagub/O DKI/LOCATION dari/O PPP/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/zwhhVgu3Dj/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Ahok/PERSON :/O Seharusnya/O Bangsa/O Kita/O Bisa/O Bikin/O Aplikasi/O Taksi/O Daring/O Sendiri/O https://t.co/Yay6w7SJZt/O 
<57>/O Jasad/O Tiga/O Santri/O Tenggelam/O di/O Sungai/LOCATION Brantas/LOCATION Ditemukan/O https://t/O .co/yi2dEFMESM/O https://t/O .co/dgUJHDGpCA/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersilaturahmi/O dgn/O Bpk/O KH/O Nursyahid/PERSON Ramli/PERSON ,/O Ketua/O Yayasan/O Pondok/ORGANIZATION Pesantren/ORGANIZATION Al/ORGANIZATION Falah/ORGANIZATION ,/O Banjarbaru/LOCATION ,/O Kalsel/LOCATION ,/O 3/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/hDHGDJl1Eh/O 
<74>/O Pemerintah/O Ancam/O Pengembang/O yang/O tak/O Taati/O Ketentuan/O Reklamasi/O https://t/O .co/oiJyzXtUMM/O https://t/O .co/1oRsOF04UV/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Dilarang/O Istri/O ,/O Sopir/O Blue/ORGANIZATION Bird/ORGANIZATION Tak/O Berani/O Ikut/O Demo/O https://t.co/ziHmvssSlv/O 
@infodishub/O :/O KESELAMATAN/O PELAYARAN/O TANGGUNG/O JAWAB/O BERSAMA/O http://t.co/oyQXYopTVm/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Semoga/O #Natal/O tahun/O ini/O ada/O dalam/O damai/O &/O bahagia/O ./O ./O Sehingga/O terciptanya/O kerukunan/O antar/O umat/O beragama/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION 
@detiksport/O :/O '/O 25/O Sterling/PERSON cedera/O dan/O harus/O diganti/O ./O Manuel/PERSON Pellgerini/PERSON memasukkan/O Fernando/PERSON 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Mari/O panjatkan/O doa/O untuk/O penumpang/O pesawat/O Air/ORGANIZATION Asia/ORGANIZATION yang/O hilang/O dan/O juga/O bagi/O tim/O penyelamat/O agar/O dpt/O bertugas/O dgn/O baik/O ./O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Berbagi/O ilmu/O dan/O pengalaman/O dgn/O para/O santri/O Pondok/ORGANIZATION Pesantren/ORGANIZATION Al-Tsaqafah/ORGANIZATION asuhan/O Bpk/O KH/O Said/PERSON Aqil/PERSON ./O Minggu/O 13/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/utHf5hCecV/O 
@infodishub/O :/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION AKAN/O SIAPKAN/O ROAD/O MAP/O PEMBATASAN/O KECEPATAN/O MOTOR/O http://t.co/zpSI67yiij/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Pilkada/O hari/O ini/O adalah/O kegembiraan/O politik/O yang/O kita/O meriahkan/O bersama-sama/O ./O Yang/O menang/O jangan/O jumawa/O ,/O yang/O kalah/O jangan/O ngamuk/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Innalillahi/O waina/O ilaihi/O rojiun/O ./O Duka/O cita/O mendalam/O atas/O wafatnya/O Ibunda/O tercinta/O dr/O Pak/O @pramonoanung/O ,/O semoga/O Almarhumah/O khusnul/O khotimah/O ./O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Ardi/PERSON Bakrie/PERSON Ajak/O Insan/O Televisi/O Bahas/O Peraturan/O Penyiaran/O https://t.co/ePwN8GQ4nq/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Sopir/O Angkot/O dan/O Go-Jek/ORGANIZATION di/O Tambora/LOCATION Tandatangani/O Perjanjian/O Damai/O https://t.co/TAty0Qta84/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PUNCAK/O ARUS/O MUDIK/O DIPERKIRAKAN/O JATUH/O PADA/O H-3/O SAMPAI/O DENGAN/O H-1/O http://t.co/lr0qYCCNuv/O #BeritaPusat/O 
<98>/O Warga/O Bogor/LOCATION Sambut/O Antusias/O Rombongan/O Kirab/O Api/O PON/O https://t/O .co/AlhgrAkxLn/O https://t/O .co/VtjgYfPyVg/O 
@aagym/O :/O Bismillah/O hari/O ini/O diluncurkan/O aplikasi/O Aa/O utk/O android/O silakan/O buka/O https://t.co/aamLqSvF4F/O https://t.co/9lOrtHvBXE/O 
@infodishub/O :/O MENHUB/O BUKA/O PENYELENGGARAAN/O RA/O V/O -/O 16/O http://t.co/AAUlb9HGgD/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Tidak/O ada/O pergantian/O pemain/O dilakukan/O kedua/O kubu/O ./O MU/ORGANIZATION sementara/O masih/O unggul/O 1-0/O berkat/O gol/O Rashford/PERSON ./O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Innalilahi/O waina/O ilaihi/O roji/O 'un/O ./O Duka/O cita/O mendalam/O atas/O terjadinya/O #tragedimina/O ,/O semoga/O yg/O wafat/O khusnul/O khotimah/O &/O yg/O terluka/O segera/O pulih/O 
@prabowo/O :/O ./O @Gerindra/O adalah/O gerakan/O menjadikan/O Indonesia/LOCATION swasembada/O pangan/O dan/O energi/O ,/O menjadi/O negara/O produsen/O tidak/O hanya/O konsumen/O produk/O impor/O ./O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O SBY/PERSON Cup/O XIII/O 2016/O ./O International/O Karate/O Championship/O ./O Ajang/O karate/O kebanggaan/O Indonesia/LOCATION penghasil/O atlet/O berkualitas/O https://t.co/RIeU5SnREw/O 
<77>/O Pesan/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON agar/O Rashford/PERSON Sukses/O ./O https://t/O .co/Ada3LdiEjD/O 
<10>/O Hasil/O Liga/O Champions/O ,/O 3/O September/O 016/O ./O https://t/O .co/qhZNhJQkbj/O 
@aagym/O :/O Insyaa/O Alloh/O Ahad/O besok/O di/O TV/O kajian/O nikmatnya/O bertauhid/O dalam/O hidup/O ini/O https://t.co/ZFMNOuhEsZ/O 
<13>/O Persib/ORGANIZATION Bandung/LOCATION Resmi/O Perkenalkan/O Marcos/PERSON Flores/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/secWrGujJM/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Bangganya/O Van/PERSON Gaal/PERSON dengan/O Kemenangan/O MU/ORGANIZATION di/O Derby/O https://t.co/5Zn1OX3YSf/O https://t.co/OsdqvByHg3/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Honda/ORGANIZATION Luncurkan/O Mobil/O Hidrogen/O ,/O Hanya/O 200/O Unit/O https://t.co/hbiGIxYjkF/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Tingkatkan/O Kualitas/O Layanan/O ,/O Prodia/O Tabanan/LOCATION Resmikan/O Gedung/O Baru/O https://t.co/B7X9bEZlbB/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Jajaran/O DPP/ORGANIZATION Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION bersama/O jajaran/O pimpinan/O United/ORGANIZATION Malays/ORGANIZATION National/ORGANIZATION Organisation/ORGANIZATION ./O Kinabalu/LOCATION ,/O Sabtu/O 5/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/ThXPjfvpxS/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @kompascom/O :/O SBY/PERSON Merasa/O Pemerintahannya/O Masih/O Jadi/O Kambing/O Hitam/O Pihak/O yang/O Kini/O Berkuasa/O https://t.co/uw2GDFkguZ/O 
<88>/O 4/O Tips/O Mudah/O Hilangkan/O Stres/O dan/O Malas/O Saat/O Bekerja/O https://t.co/V43RDtNYer/O https://t.co/VbpGdMPegc/O 
<2>/O Woyo-woyo/O itu/O apa/O ya?/O https://t.co/c9mgjFowLK/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O Peluncuran/O Jakarta/LOCATION smart/O city/O ./O Aplikasi/O terintegrasi/O untuk/O pemantauan/O kota/O dan/O penanganan/O aduan/O warga/O http://t.co/sRjK3hjQCb/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O di/O Negeri/O Laskar/O Pelangi/O yang/O Membawa/O Rezeki/O https://t.co/iDZK4FjPtN/O https://t.co/Dfozu8A5Ny/O 
@aagym/O :/O Ayoo/O berani/O jujur/O berapa/O banyak/O waktu/O yang/O digunakan/O untuk/O masing/O masing/O ?/O Mana/O yang/O bakal/O jadi/O bekal/O pulang/O https://t.co/myA4QalSL0/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PENGELOLAAN/O LAYANAN/O NAVIGASI/O BANDARA/LOCATION SIBORONG/LOCATION -/O BORONG/LOCATION dan/O HANG/LOCATION NADIM/LOCATION DISERAHKAN/O KEPADA/O AIRNAV/ORGANIZATION INDONESIA/ORGANIZATION http://t.co/B5kp0yMNP0/O #BeritaPusat/O 
<95>/O Pose/O Yoga/O Sophia/PERSON Latjuba/1O/O Ini/O Membuat/O Takjub/O https://t.co/R68qh4BEb3/O https://t.co/t8gKcxRgMY/O 
@aagym/O :/O Kita/O sama/O sekali/O tak/O bisa/O membolak/O balik/O hati/O orang/O ,/O maka/O lakukanlah/O segalanya/O dengan/O ikhlas/O ,/O semata/O agar/O Alloh/O ridho/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O Selamat/O siang/O ,/O udah/O lama/O saya/O nggak/O ngetwit/O ./O Sambil/O di/O perjalanan/O mau/O twit/O beberapa/O hal/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O BNN/ORGANIZATION Siap-siap/O Naik/O Jadi/O Setingkat/O Kementerian/O https://t.co/h1nqmpzFGq/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Contohnya/O pembangunan/O rel/O ganda/O yang/O menghubungkan/O Jakarta/LOCATION -/O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O yang/O sebelumnya/O memakan/O waktu/O tempuh/O 11/O jam/O menjadi/O sekitar/O 8/O jam/O saja/O ./O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O #Kaltara/O adalah/O provinsi/O termuda/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION yg/O resmi/O terbentuk/O pada/O masa/O pemerintahan/O Pak/O SBY/PERSON tahun/O 2012/O 
<61>/O Pilot/O Tempur/O Cantik/O Ini/O Rela/O Mati/O untuk/O Batalkan/O Serangan/O 9/11/O https://t.co/Sf4HKpLLP4/O https://t.co/xAiRrdxST7/O 
<66>/O Kekalahan/O dari/O Sriwijaya/ORGANIZATION FC/ORGANIZATION Bikin/O Pelatih/O Persib/ORGANIZATION Susah/O Tidur/O ./O https://t/O .co/JX8cJMT0pL/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Mancini/PERSON Tetap/O Optimistis/O dengan/O Inter/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/907GszaLlq/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Keluarga/O Pak/O Raden/PERSON Datangi/O Kemendikbud/O Minta/O Dibantu/O Kelola/O Aset/O Peninggalan/O https://t.co/neblVSFlvU/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Orang/O yang/O suka/O mencela/O ,/O selalu/O mencela/O orang/O yang/O bisa/O melakukan/O yang/O lebih/O baik/O daripada/O yang/O bisa/O dilakukannya/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@infodishub/O :/O RT/O @DennyAJD/O :/O Mantabb/O @infodishub/O ./O Penertiban/O parkir/O liar/O di/O sepanjang/O Jalan/LOCATION Tebet/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION Raya/LOCATION ./O Cc/O :/O @TMCPoldaMetro/O http://t.co/IlrCKS1qJQ/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Buwas/PERSON :/O Kemarin/O di/O Bareskrim/ORGANIZATION Saya/O Bikin/O Gaduh/O ,/O Sekarang/O di/O BNN/ORGANIZATION Saya/O Bikin/O Gila/O https://t.co/SrvQVCLK8y/O https://t.co/AOXvATCgHM/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Indonesia/LOCATION Ingin/O Tambah/O Wakil/O di/O Olimpiade/O Rio/O 2016/O https://t.co/4xaq4PIYPz/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Sopir/O Provokator/O yang/O Pasang/O Status/O Seram/O di/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION Masih/O Aktif/O Bekerja/O https://t.co/CsAa7GvRp0/O https://t.co/SIa5Dwbz9h/O 
<81>/O Demi/O Konsumen/O ,/O Samsung/O Bisa/O Matikan/O Galaxy/O Note/O 7/O dari/O Jarak/O Jauh/O https://t/O .co/1UR3jH1QwB/O https://t/O .co/aPyRwQRpgz/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PT/ORGANIZATION KAI/ORGANIZATION DIMINTA/O BANGUN/O FASILITAS/O PETIKEMAS/O di/O SEJUMLAH/O STASIUN/O http://t.co/uObGKXpo1k/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@prabowo/O :/O @Arthanurwansyah/O Aamiin/O ./O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Harapan/O Alex/PERSON Usman/PERSON atas/O Vonis/O Hakim/O Hari/O Ini/O https://t.co/BajjXoFyxu/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Wanita/O Ini/O Nyaris/O Buta/O Usai/O Nonton/O Drama/O Korea/LOCATION 18/O Jam/O Tanpa/O Henti/O https://t.co/fJ728cPrcG/O 
@aagym/O :/O Ayoo/O tahajjud/O dan/O kirim/O doa/O kepada/O orang/O orang/O yg/O telah/O berbuat/O baik/O juga/O doa/O kebaikan/O bagi/O yg/O berbuat/O kurang/O baik/O https://t.co/kVPNc02vDm/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PENDAFTARAN/O MUDIK/O GRATIS/O KAPAL/O LAUT/O DIMULAI/O 1/O JULI/O 2014/O http://t.co/J8FKoj42ol/O #BeritaPusat/O 
<61>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O Arus/O Besar/O ,/O Penyelam/O Labuan/LOCATION Bajo/LOCATION Diserbu/O Banyak/O Ikan/O https://t.co/1TuBqzuOmD/O https://t.co/vOhIO7qd4y/O 
<27>/O Satu/O Lagi/O Tren/O Cantik/O ala/O Korea/LOCATION yang/O Bikin/O Geleng-geleng/O Kepala/O ./O https://t/O .co/LJo9IDeezS/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Mengunjungi/O UMKM/O binaan/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Kenjeran/LOCATION ./O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/HPsnjQL6Ut/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Terima/O kasih/O sudah/O berkenan/O datang/O ke/O padepokan/O @melfeyadin/O @elephunx25_85/O 
<68>/O Ups/O ,/O iPhone/O 7/O Warna/O Jet/O Black/O Ternyata/O Rentan/O Kena/O Goresan/O https://t.co/tJXSK1F9RF/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O RT/O @husainabdullah1/O :/O @Pak_JK/O meresmikan/O @KompasTV/O sebagai/O tv/O berita/O @Rosianna766Hi/O https://t.co/lh7uc9g5lq/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O bantuan/O dana/O untuk/O perangkat/O Mini/O Lab/O Komunikasi/O FISIP/O Universitas/ORGANIZATION Jenderal/ORGANIZATION Soedirman/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t.co/lD1jbyUkt7/O 
<29>/O Polisi/ORGANIZATION Siapkan/O 7/O Pertanyaan/O untuk/O Reza/O Artamevia/O ./O https://t/O .co/uAEsDC2nMd/O 
<96>/O Enrique/PERSON :/O Messi/PERSON adalah/O Sepak/O Bola/O ./O https://t/O .co/msauFtUxFf/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Grab/ORGANIZATION Car/ORGANIZATION Tetap/O Beroperasi/O Gunakan/O Mobil/O Pelat/O Hitam/O https://t.co/v9zUH5VE7n/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Anda/O setuju/O ?/O https://t.co/NFBGqq81PC/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Uang/O memang/O tidak/O dibawa/O mati/O ,/O tapi/O tanpa/O uang/O hidup/O ini/O rasanya/O setengah/O mati/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<22>/O Memilih/O pasta/O gigi/O ternyata/O tidak/O bisa/O sembarangan/O ,/O harus/O memenuhi/O beberapa/O faktor/O kesehatan/O seperti/O berikut/O ini./O https://t.co/bn6XeeigLW/O 
@aagym/O :/O Ayoo/O ada/O yang/O mau/O ikutan/O belajar/O olah/O raga/O Sunnah/O berkuda/O memanah/O di/O Daarussunnah/LOCATION ecopsantren/LOCATION Dt/LOCATION Bandung/LOCATION https://t.co/IoGFZJMUQ3/O 
<11>/O PDIP/ORGANIZATION akan/O Usung/O Calon/O Sendiri/O di/O Pilkada/O 017/O https://t/O .co/H8IuCf72uf/O https://t/O .co/O GKiJzMNqY/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Audiensi/O @FPD_DPR/O bersama/O DPRD/ORGANIZATION DKI/LOCATION ,/O Jabar/LOCATION &/O Depok/LOCATION ./O FPD/O solid/O satu/O tujuan/O mengawal/O aspirasi/O demi/O kesejahteraan/O rakyat/O https://t.co/vVHZPeQbE9/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Ronaldo/PERSON Siap/O Libas/O Siapa/O Pun/O di/O Perempat/O Final/O Liga/O Champions/O https://t.co/vSNfBJ7tHz/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Pakai/O Lensa/O Kontak/O Sembarangan/O ,/O Hati-hati/O Bakteri/O di/O Mata/O Makin/O Menumpuk/O https://t.co/OjfO1RTke3/O via/O @detikHealth/O https://t.co/OMozB02Ibh/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Polisi/ORGANIZATION :/O Kecelakaan/O Putra/O Rano/PERSON Karno/PERSON Diselesaikan/O secara/O Kekeluargaan/O https://t.co/fvdv7RBbxR/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Tottenham/ORGANIZATION Hotspur/ORGANIZATION Kalahkan/O Bournemouth/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/HEMS4q1jE2/O https://t.co/FdYscp6fPm/O 
@detiksport/O :/O RT/O @AboutTheGame_/O :/O Dari/O analisis/O @panditfootball/O ,/O Man/ORGANIZATION Utd/ORGANIZATION sebenarnya/O tidak/O tampil/O istimewa/O ./O Sementara/O itu/O ,/O City/ORGANIZATION justru/O tampil/O buruk/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Saya/O akan/O membantu/O membangun/O koperasi/O untuk/O nelayan/O ./O Khusus/O untuk/O aktivitas/O produktif/O nelayan/O ./O https://t.co/mNJkCnvB2m/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Jaga/O Kulit/O Cantik/O Anda/O dengan/O Kombinasi/O Susu/O Bubuk/O https://t.co/mvNq9jIqR3/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Kisah/O Inspiratif/O Seorang/O Anak/O Haram/O https://t.co/DI3qhETglM/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Bagi/O yang/O luka/O serta/O dirawat/O akibat/O kecelakaan/O Metro/O Mini-KCL/O Semoga/O lekas/O sembuh/O seperti/O sedia/O kala/O ,/O aamiin/O 
<70>/O Mengapa/O Yogyakarta/LOCATION Masih/O Diminati/O Turis/O Indonesia/LOCATION ?/O ./O https://t/O .co/3sAbwloGZp/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PEMERINTAH/O REVISI/O TARIF/O BATAS/O ATAS/O http://t.co/zYCi5wQplw/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Cinta/O tidak/O bisa/O dicari/O ,/O tapi/O dibiarkan/O terjadi/O kepada/O diri/O kita/O yang/O kita/O indahkan/O ./O Indahnya/O diri/O =/O indahnya/O cinta/O ./O MT/PERSON 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Saatnya/O Hindari/O '/O Saling/O Memanfaatkan/O '/O di/O Pilkada/O https://t.co/c5uowmwTEf/O 
<46>/O John/PERSON Terry/PERSON Absen/O Lawan/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION ?/O ./O https://t/O .co/cWZpwfgwcC/O ./O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Sepp/PERSON Blater/PERSON Terkejut/O Kantor/O FFF/ORGANIZATION Digeledah/O https://t.co/xxYjLGJviS/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Aamiin/O ./O Terima/O kasih/O ./O Salam/O hormat/O untuk/O keluarga/O ./O https://t.co/FQRw3vg1ky/O 
@aagym/O :/O Hanya/O Alloh/O yg/O kuasa/O menurunkan/O hujan/O ,/O ayo/O kita/O istigfar/O dan/O sholat/O memohon/O hujan/O ,/O agar/O asap/O segera/O sirna/O https://t.co/GRNaXTLHt7/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Di/O Mukomuko/LOCATION -/O Bengkulu/LOCATION ,/O #GMT9Mar16/O teramati/O antara/O pukul/O 06/O :/O 21/O WIB/O (/O saat/O Matahari/O terbit/O di/O Mukomuko/LOCATION )/O hingga/O pukul/O 08/O :/O 27/O :/O 08/O ,/O 7/O WIB/O ./O 
<57>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O TUI/ORGANIZATION Travel/ORGANIZATION PLC/ORGANIZATION Pun/O Bersemangat/O Memasarkan/O Wonderful/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/Rg6oDSqnAq/O https://t.co/k0Ai3AKXfq/O 
@aagym/O :/O Jengkel/O itu/O bila/O keinginan/O tak/O terpenuhi/O ,/O supaya/O tak/O gampang/O jengkel/O jangan/O diperbudak/O keinginan/O dan/O tuntutan/O 
<67>/O Bunuh/O Rival/O Politiknya/O ,/O Seorang/O Wali/O Kota/LOCATION di/O Honduras/LOCATION Ditangkap/O ./O https://t/O .co/XMb6Q23N4v/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Soal/O Santoso/PERSON Masuk/O Daftar/O Teroris/O Global/O AS/LOCATION ,/O Menko/O Luhut/PERSON :/O Bagus/O !/O https://t.co/M7ZnpeNPCa/O 
@detikcom/O :/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION Nyatakan/O Uber/ORGANIZATION dan/O GrabCar/ORGANIZATION Status/O Quo/O Saat/O Masa/O Transisi/O https://t.co/9JMCGQjOSK/O https://t.co/X8N1IyuVUe/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Kemarin/O ,/O Bumi/O mengalami/O kegelapan/O sesaat/O ./O Cari/O tahu/O lebih/O dalam/O tentang/O fenomena/O ini/O dlm/O #GMT2016/O @hariankompas/O https://t.co/Nyw34RJ8pI/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Presiden/O SBY/PERSON berbagi/O gagasan/O &/O pandangan/O politik/O pribadi/O lewat/O akun/O Youtube/O :/O http://t.co/BAxHsgJbZw/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Om/O Mario/PERSON ini/O ternyata/O lucu/O juga/O ya/O ?/O -/O Ya/O ,/O terkadang/O saya/O harus/O agak/O lucu/O ,/O supaya/O tidak/O terlihat/O terlalu/O bijak/O ./O 
<89>/O Isu/O SARA/O Dinilai/O Sudah/O tidak/O Relevan/O https://t/O .co/2RtUUFepiJ/O https://t/O .co/JDgUr4cqR2/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Kenali/O Jenis-jenis/O Kejang/O pada/O Epilepsi/O https://t.co/nSInYNqRZN/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 25/O :/O 09/O ,/O 9/O WIB/O :/O Fase/O Totalitas/O berakhir/O di/O Tanjung/LOCATION Pandan/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
<1>/O Terseret/O Ombak/O Pantai/LOCATION Payangan/LOCATION ,/O Dua/O Pelajar/O Ditemukan/O Tewas/O ./O https://t/O .co/nsn63G93VS/O 
<98>/O Arsenal/ORGANIZATION Tahan/O Imbang/O PSG/ORGANIZATION -1/O https://t/O .co/8yIlGLaWxK/O https://t/O .co/Q8ZQv14kIr/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Di/O Manado/LOCATION ,/O #GMT9Mar16/O berlangsung/O selama/O 2/O jam/O 41/O menit/O 27/O ,/O 3/O detik/O dgn/O magnitudo/O gerhana/O saat/O puncak/O ,/O pukul/O 08/O :/O 49/O :/O 25/O ,/O 5/O WITA/O ,/O adalah/O 0/O ,/O 972/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Saat/O ujian/O ,/O menundukkan/O dalam/O doa/O ,/O melihatlah/O ke/O atas/O untuk/O inspirasi/O ,/O ke/O depan/O untuk/O keamanan/O ,/O dan/O ke/O kiri/O dan/O kanan/O untuk/O informasi/O ./O MT/PERSON 
@basuki_btp/O :/O instagram/ORGANIZATION resmi/O saya/O hanya/O satu/O :/O basukibtp/O 
<71>/O Daftar/O 07/O Jemaah/O Haji/O Indonesia/LOCATION Wafat/O di/O Arab/LOCATION Saudi/LOCATION https://t.co/2z2M8LllRa/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Seribu/O Ide/O Cerita/O untuk/O Film/O Filosofi/O Kopi/O :/O Ben/PERSON &/O Jody/PERSON https://t.co/6GHOucXJMn/O https://t.co/e4hm5OMy2k/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PETUGAS/O di/O LAPANGAN/O DIMINTA/O AWASI/O PELAKSANAKAAN/O MUDIK/O DENGAN/O BAIK/O http://t.co/bOKBiU5Z2F/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Sedih/O melihat/O aset/O negara/O di/O proyek/O Hambalang/O mangkrak/O ./O Penuh/O alang-alang/O ./O Harus/O diselamatkan/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/LPM3BEfnhS/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Ambillah/O pelajaran/O dari/O kesalahan/O masa/O lalu/O Anda/O ,/O dan/O lupakan/O rasa/O sakitnya/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@jokowi/O :/O Titik/O api/O sudah/O mulai/O muncul/O lagi/O ./O Segera/O antisipasi/O jangan/O sampai/O meluas/O ./O Kita/O semua/O harus/O bergerak/O ./O Jangan/O sampai/O asap/O datang/O lagi/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@KompasTV/O :/O Bambang/PERSON Widjojanto/PERSON Menilai/O Pimpinan/O Lembaga/O Penegak/O Hukum/O Rentan/O Konflik/O Kepentingan/O https://t.co/rIET0W8ehV/O 
<12>/O iOS/O 0/O Sempat/O Bikin/O iPhone/O dan/O iPad/O "Membeku"/O ./O https://t/O .co/J2jpPccSNW/O ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Apa/O yang/O kita/O sombong/O kan/O dari/O diri/O ini/O ,/O asal/O hanya/O setetes/O mani/O ,/O akhirnya/O jadi/O bangkai/O ,/O dan/O Kemana/O mana/O membawa/O kotoran/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Polisi/ORGANIZATION Tangkap/O Empat/O Perampok/O Toko/O Emas/O https://t.co/jruOZe9EoA/O https://t.co/d3Y01gnyqA/O 
<76>/O Totti/PERSON Akhirnya/O Merasa/O Cemas/O untuk/O Eksekusi/O Penalti/O ./O https://t/O .co/DCKxFW9riX/O 
@prabowo/O :/O @thanmusttri/O Benar/O ./O Karena/O itu/O tidak/O ada/O setoran/O liar/O ,/O pungutan/O liar/O di/O Partai/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION ./O Kalau/O mau/O kaya/O ,/O jangan/O masuk/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O ikut/O ikutan/O tiup/O terompet/O ,/O selain/O tak/O jadi/O amal/O juga/O bekas/O ditiup/O pembuatnya/O ,/O pedagangnya/O dll/O ,/O tidak/O terjamin/O kebersihannya/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Pemkab/O Kupang/LOCATION Mutasi/O Kepsek/O yang/O Pecat/O Guru/O Honorer/O https://t.co/nG4zbYbf11/O 
<26>/O Tabiat/O di/O Ujung/O Pilkada/O DKI/LOCATION https://t/O .co/b8ZqV4CHkj/O https://t/O .co/c0VmN4tCFg/O 
<29>/O Duterte/O Izinkan/O AL/ORGANIZATION Indonesia/LOCATION Kejar/O Bajak/O Laut/O ke/O Perairan/O Filipina/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/iGhh8OFwTY/O 
<27>/O MU/ORGANIZATION Kokoh/O di/O Puncak/O Klasemen/O ./O https://t/O .co/P1Qd12vnhv/O 
<52>/O Beli/O Galaxy/O on/O 7/O +/O bonus/O #FreedomCombo/O M/O setahun/O utk/O streaming/O musik/O UNLIMITED/O di/O Spotify!/O https://t.co/THHjCh2c0m/O https://t.co/0Eu5QUQqdl/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Tujuh/O Indeks/O Sektoral/O Kompak/O Memerah/O ,/O IHSG/O Dibuka/O Turun/O 0/O ,/O 82/O Persen/O https://t.co/3jvXNS4z7b/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 31/O :/O 27/O ,/O 9/O WIB/O :/O Fase/O Totalitas/O berakhir/O di/O Palangkaraya/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O potongan/O tumpeng/O kepada/O Ketua/O Perwakilan/O Luar/O Negeri/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION Malaysia/LOCATION Bpk/O M/PERSON Tohong/PERSON Hasibuan/O https://t.co/zlnpwT9fgf/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Lokasi/O pertama/O di/O Utara/O jalur/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O yaitu/O Banda/LOCATION Aceh/LOCATION ,/O Aceh/LOCATION ./O Tepatnya/O di/O gedung/O TDMRC/O ,/O samping/O Masjid/LOCATION Raya/LOCATION Baiturrahman/LOCATION 
@jokowi/O :/O 5/O ./O Saya/O telah/O membaca/O 238/O butir/O impian/O rakyat/O dari/O 34/O provinsi/O di/O seluruh/O Indonesia/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/PoBzGQeeXu/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Kerja/O keras/O &/O Perjuangan/O sudah/O dilakukan/O ,/O saatnya/O berdoa/O ,/O berikhtiar/O dan/O berserah/O diri/O memohon/O terbaik/O demi/O kemenangan/O yg/O sempurna/O -/O KPP/O PD/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Guru/O Mashudi/PERSON '/O untuk/O Sementara/O '/O Dibebaskan/O Polda/ORGANIZATION Metro/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/X0CGXB5Pp2/O 
@infodishub/O :/O PEMBERLAKUAN/O ERP/O di/O JAKARTA/LOCATION PALING/O LAMBAT/O AKHIR/O 2015/O http://t.co/y1jj2R9apd/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O RT/O @kotaindramayu/O :/O RT/O @PakdeWinar/O :/O Gema/O Istighfar/O menjelang/O sholat/O gerhana/O di/O Masjid/LOCATION Jatibarang/LOCATION Indramayu/LOCATION ./O #GMT9Mar16/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O kader-kader/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Malaysia/LOCATION ./O Kuala/LOCATION Lumpur/LOCATION ,/O 5/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/ZO3Pw0egFM/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Selamat/O berjuang/O para/O pengurus/O DPC/O Kabupaten/O Kuningan/LOCATION ,/O Indramayu/LOCATION ,/O Cirebon/LOCATION dan/O Kota/O Cirebon/LOCATION ./O Cirebon/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/0LeCEw6MSd/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Bendungan/LOCATION Jatigede/LOCATION mengairi/O 90/O ribu/O ha/O sawah/O ,/O pembangkit/O listrik/O 110/O MW/O ,/O pengendali/O banjir/O ,/O tempat/O wisata/O baru/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/si6R61aXpt/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Infrastruktur/O penting/O tapi/O Guru/O Honorer/O ,/O Praktek/O Bidan/O &/O Dokter/O dan/O BPJS/O utk/O rakyat/O sangat/O penting/O #DengarHatiRakyat/O https://t.co/eL9vVVrgRC/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Berbincang/O sesaat/O sebelum/O take/O off/O ke/O Tiongkok/LOCATION untuk/O kunjungan/O kenegaraan/O ./O @husainabdullah1/O https://t.co/OifFA9JOHz/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Pagi/O ini/O saya/O bersepeda/O dengan/O masyarakat/O Surabaya/LOCATION &/O pengurus/O DPD/ORGANIZATION Gerindra/ORGANIZATION Jatim/LOCATION ./O Luar/O biasa/O semangat/O arek/O Suroboyo/LOCATION ./O https://t.co/VsrtMposN5/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Bocah/O Keterbelakangan/O Mental/O Berusia/O 11/O Tahun/O Diikat/O Orangtuanya/O https://t.co/opZAxZuqS1/O 
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Ketua/O DPD/ORGANIZATION Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION Kota/O Bandung/LOCATION Bpk/O Muhammad/PERSON Ferrari/PERSON Nurrachadian/PERSON https://t.co/g5HAVrsGAb/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O RT/O @sa_rinahe/O :/O RT/O mBatangUpdate/O :/O #Batang/O Fatkhur_27/O Subahanallah/O area/O kabupaten/O batang/LOCATION tertutup/O hampir/O semuanya/O #GMT9Mar16/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Selamat/O dan/O turut/O berbahagia/O atas/O kelahiran/O cucu/O pertama/O dr/O Pak/O @jokowi/O semoga/O jd/O anak/O yg/O Sholeh/O dan/O berbakti/O ,/O aamiin/O ./O 
@aagym/O :/O Mohon/O doa/O ,/O tugas/O dakwah/O di/O Qatar/LOCATION semoga/O diberkahi/O Alloh/O yaa/O ,/O nuhuuun/O ,/O sobat/O di/O Qatar/LOCATION sampai/O jumpa/O nanti/O sore/O https://t.co/LhSDr2QST3/O 
<6>/O Senin/O ,/O Aji/PERSON Santoso/PERSON Akan/O Mulai/O Pimpin/O Latihan/O Persela/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/ZQ6oZOWgwO/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @PDemokrat/O :/O Jangan/O Paksa/O Bangun/O Infrastruktur/O Saat/O Ekonomi/O Sulit/O https://t.co/8eIPOCU0V1/O @SBYudhoyono/O @hincapandjaitan/O @FPD_DPR/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Rajin/O dan/O sabar/O pangkal/O dicintai/O oleh/O Tuhan/O ./O jika/O dicintai/O oleh/O Tuhan/O ,/O kita/O akan/O dikhususkan/O dan/O didahulukan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
@detikcom/O :/O Menderita/O Leukemia/O Diduga/O Jadi/O Penyebab/O Suwito/PERSON Gantung/O Diri/O https://t.co/DrFqU2HPUj/O 
<47>/O Paul/PERSON Kern/PERSON ,/O Manusia/O yang/O Tak/O Pernah/O Tidur/O Selama/O 40/O Tahun/O https://t.co/QeC5X70ZQl/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Mendengarkan/O harapan/O &/O aspirasi/O rakyat/O ,/O Jika/O pemerintah/O baik/O kita/O dukung/O ,/O namun/O jika/O kurang/O tepat/O kita/O kritisi/O #SBYTourDeJava/O 
@basuki_btp/O :/O Woyo-woyo/O itu/O apa/O ya/O ?/O https://t.co/c9mgjFowLK/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Cucu/O Pertama/O Jokowi/PERSON Lahir/O ,/O JK/PERSON Ucapkan/O Selamat/O https://t.co/H8gepxhLiF/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Tulisan/O netizen/O penting/O dalam/O menumbuhkan/O optimisme/O ,/O kejujuran/O dan/O etos/O kerja/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@aagym/O :/O Seringkali/O kita/O sibuk/O dengan/O kecemasan/O akibat/O mendramatisir/O masalah/O ,/O padahal/O sesudah/O dilalui/O tak/O Segawat/O yang/O dicemaskan/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Final/O Piala/O Jenderal/O Sudirman/PERSON nanti/O malam/O pasti/O seru/O ./O Klub/O mana/O yg/O kalian/O favoritkan/O juara/O ?/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/s48BPN97ea/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Anas/PERSON :/O Penuntasan/O Kasus/O Hambalang/O Tergantung/O KPK/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/2YA5P8OXbm/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O sore/O ,/O sahabat/O ./O Semoga/O dalam/O keadaan/O baik/O ./O 
@detikcom/O :/O Soal/O Demo/O Sopir/O Taksi/O ,/O Mensesneg/O :/O Tahan/O Diri/O ,/O Jangan/O Kecewakan/O Masyarakat/O https://t.co/q8JWNijIfv/O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O Lokasi/O keempat/O di/O Selatan/O jalur/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O adalah/O Karangkates/LOCATION Jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION ,/O tepatnya/O adalah/O di/O Masjid/LOCATION Kepanjen/LOCATION ./O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Call/O of/O Duty/O :/O Black/O Ops/O III/O Kedatangan/O Map/O Multiplayer/O Gratis/O https://t.co/Hi7ivEtFPn/O https://t.co/LNJ1DriLPU/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Alhamdulillah/O ./O Terima/O kasih/O saya/O dan/O @HattaRajasa/O kepada/O seluruh/O rakyat/O Indonesia/LOCATION atas/O kepercayaan/O yang/O telah/O diberikan/O kepada/O kami/O ./O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Ihsan/PERSON Maulana/PERSON Melaju/O ke/O Babak/O 16/O Besar/O New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION Terbuka/O 2016/O https://t.co/l8WNhaK6Zs/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Status/O Siaga/O Gunung/LOCATION Lokon/LOCATION https://t.co/C61aScN3mQ/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Anak/O muda/O harus/O cepat/O ./O Anak/O muda/O tidak/O boleh/O lamban/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON https://t.co/R2jifJRnkm/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Impor/O ilegal/O harus/O diberantas/O tuntas/O ./O Industri/O nasional/O dirugikan/O ,/O pendapatan/O negara/O hilang/O -/O Jkw/PERSON http://t.co/Iiastf6WbZ/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Strategi/O Bank/ORGANIZATION Mandiri/ORGANIZATION Bikin/O Pertumbuhan/O Kredit/O Melejit/O https://t.co/3eXc3huFYZ/O 
@aagym/O :/O Masya/O Alloh/O ,/O bila/O setiap/O perusahaan/O seperti/O ini/O mengutamakan/O sholat/O dan/O profesionalisme/O niscaya/O berkaah/O https://t.co/5wVNCaduuo/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Bismillahirrahmanirrahim/O ./O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Iklan/O Motor/O Forza/O Bocor/O ,/O ini/O Kata/O Honda/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/rbJrHmI8Gt/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Intip/O Betapa/O Mewahnya/O Lincoln/ORGANIZATION Navigator/O ,/O Mobil/O Fitur/O Seabrek/O https://t.co/LGibKa8iEc/O 
<80>/O Juventus/ORGANIZATION Dilarang/O Terbuai/O oleh/O Pujian/O ./O https://t/O .co/LvwqjehsE3/O 
<14>/O Pemerintah/O Australia/LOCATION Kembali/O Bantu/O Sebuah/O Sekolah/ORGANIZATION Islam/O di/O Canberra/O ./O https://t/O .co/KyAzRlo4st/O 
@infodishub/O :/O ANGKUTAN/O TIDAK/O BOLEH/O MENAIKKAN/O TARIF/O http://t.co/QBmEIFj1Dx/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Hari/O ini/O ,/O apa/O pun/O yang/O terjadi/O ,/O yang/O sabar/O ya/O ?/O Anda/O tahu/O bahwa/O kalau/O Anda/O mau/O ,/O Anda/O bisa/O ./O https://t.co/XE2Xuwi8uH/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Coba/O bagaimana/O pengalaman/O #Pilkada2015/O tadi/O ?/O Saya/O ingin/O tahu/O ./O Ada/O yang/O foto-foto/O ?/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@detikcom/O :/O Ibu/O Menyusui/O di/O Negara/O Berkembang/O Lebih/O Banyak/O Ketimbang/O di/O Negara/O Maju/O https://t.co/SmrEkL8YEP/O via/O @detikHealth/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Demo/O Ricuh/O Sopir/O Taksi/O ,/O 1/O Orang/O jadi/O Tersangka/O dan/O 3/O Sopir/O Masih/O Ditahan/O https://t.co/d8E5EEkkWG/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O 5/O ./O Pajak/O tersebut/O digunakan/O pemerintah/O untuk/O membangun/O infrastruktur/O #munaskadin/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Komentar/O Jay/PERSON Subiyakto/PERSON soal/O Musisi/O Jadi/O Politikus/O https://t.co/IUy0QlYt37/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Bom/O Brussels/LOCATION ,/O Uber/ORGANIZATION dan/O Google/ORGANIZATION Gratiskan/O Layanan/O https://t.co/HRPqlVRzpT/O 
@prabowo/O :/O @rimelfitr/O Selamat/O siang/O dan/O semoga/O sukses/O ./O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Izin/O UMKM/O Akan/O Dipermudah/O untuk/O Kejar/O Target/O https://t.co/ZHdgVQIE5r/O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O Saya/O meminta/O kader-kader/O HMI/ORGANIZATION agar/O menjaga/O toleransi/O ,/O keadilan/O dan/O ikut/O memakmurkan/O ekonomi/O bangsa/O https://t.co/ge4DKF2EuA/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Seruan/O Boikot/O Produk/O Israel/LOCATION ,/O ini/O Tanggapan/O DPR/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/K1bj3n6mpT/O 
@infodishub/O :/O SERTIJAB/O KETUA/O UMUM/O DEWAN/O PENGUJI/O KEAHLIAN/O PELAUT/O (/O DPKP/ORGANIZATION )/O http://t.co/8opcjKmtKm/O #BeritaPusat/O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Bersama/O Presiden/O @Jokowi/O ,/O SBY/PERSON menghadiri/O peresmian/O gedung/O baru/O KPK/ORGANIZATION di/O Jakarta/LOCATION ./O Dukungan/O kpd/O KPK/ORGANIZATION sangat/O diperlukan/O ./O 
<2>/O Blunder/O ,/O Bravo/PERSON Tetap/O Dipuji/O Guardiola/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/MDEsjYv30j/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Satu/O tahun/O ini/O KMP/ORGANIZATION telah/O memperjuangkan/O kelangsungan/O demokrasi/O ,/O dan/O berperan/O mempertahankan/O kedaulatan/O dan/O kepentingan/O nasional/O ./O #1TahunKMP/O 
<25>/O Berlapis/O Emas/O ,/O Begini/O Penampakan/O Hotel/LOCATION Termewah/O di/O Dunia/O https://t.co/7AGyCrStWe/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Indonesia/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION Kian/O Populer/O bagi/O Warga/O Australia/LOCATION https://t.co/PxebPWOCZI/O 
@aagym/O :/O Sebesar/O apapun/O amal/O kita/O ,/O segera/O kita/O lupakan/O cukup/O Alloh/O yang/O ingat/O ,/O sekecil/O apapun/O kebaikan/O orang/O kita/O harus/O berterima/O kasih/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Kemarin/O adalah/O pengalaman/O luar/O biasa/O ./O Saya/O memilih/O di/O dekat/O rumah/O ,/O di/O TPS/LOCATION 06/LOCATION di/O Kecamatan/O Gunung/LOCATION Putri/LOCATION bersama/O istri/O dan/O putra/O saya/O ./O 
<33>/O Resep/O Sederhana/O Zaskia/PERSON Sungkar/PERSON Ini/O Bikin/O Suami/O Bahagia/O https://t.co/S3D7jnwMHG/O 
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Putuskanlah/O untuk/O berbahagia/O ./O Sesungguhnya/O lebih/O banyak/O alasan/O bagimu/O untuk/O bersyukur/O daripada/O bersedih/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON 
<31>/O Penolakan/O BEM/ORGANIZATION UI/ORGANIZATION terhadap/O Proyek/O Reklamasi/O Teluk/O Jakarta/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/RqnUnfqAE1/O 
@detikcom/O :/O Rio/PERSON Haryanto/PERSON ,/O Satu/O di/O Antara/O Tiga/O Debutan/O F1/O https://t.co/3fMiP1VUo4/O via/O @detikSport/O https://t.co/brVmzkuZQp/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O BPJS/ORGANIZATION Ketenagakerjaan/ORGANIZATION Resmi/O Buka/O Layanan/O 7/O Hari/O Kerja/O https://t.co/YhMtQUAUGg/O https://t.co/r8HNH8cvZ0/O 
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O ./O @PDemokrat/O hari/O ini/O memutuskan/O akan/O netral/O ./O Saya/O mendukung/O 100/O %/O keputusan/O ini/O ./O 
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 22/O :/O 28/O ,/O 5/O WIB/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Banda/LOCATION Aceh/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O 
<69>/O PB/O PON/O Tolak/O Permintaan/O Penambahan/O Atlet/O https://t/O .co/cCthAuD3HL/O https://t/O .co/edagPJLD9g/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Senang/O dengar/O laporan/O Yusuf/PERSON Ali/PERSON ,/O pemilik/O LuLu/ORGANIZATION Grup/ORGANIZATION ./O Sejak/O kunjungan/O saya/O ke/O Arab/LOCATION lalu/O ,/O ekspor/O RI/LOCATION naik/O 2X/O lipat/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/CBHz1USX9Q/O 
@prabowo/O :/O Begitu/O banyak/O yang/O dapat/O kita/O pelajari/O dari/O perjuangan/O para/O pendahulu/O kita/O ./O Salah/O satunya/O :/O Seorang/O pejuang/O tidak/O mengenal/O kata/O pensiun/O !/O 
@aagym/O :/O Banyak/O orang/O yang/O punya/O kekayaan/O tapi/O tak/O punya/O kemuliaan/O dan/O kebahagiaan/O ,/O karena/O tak/O punya/O jujur/O 
@KompasTV/O :/O Tingginya/O intensitas/O hujan/O di/O Kota/O Palangkaraya/LOCATION membuat/O ratusan/O rumah/O terendam/O air/O ./O Saksikan/O #KompasUpdate/O dipersembahkan/O @Fitbar_ID/O #Ad/O 
@prabowo/O :/O ./O @Gerindra/O kini/O partai/O politik/O terbesar/O ketiga/O di/O negara/O terbesar/O keempat/O di/O dunia/O ,/O dan/O berhasil/O mendorong/O banyak/O perubahan/O baik/O ./O 
@jokowi/O :/O Setujukah/O orang/O yang/O buang/O sampah/O sembarangan/O tidak/O memiliki/O tanggung/O jawab/O sosial/O ?/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@KompasTV/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O 6/O Pengedar/O Sabu/O Diringkus/O BNN/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/xgaPzJYEza/O 
@Metro_TV/O :/O Tarif/O Progresif/O Timbun/O Kontainer/O Bakal/O Dicabut/O https://t.co/NUMwfEySru/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O DPR/ORGANIZATION Harus/O Konsisten/O dengan/O Kebijakan/O yang/O Ada/O https://t.co/DnwYAxKPig/O 
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Diskusi/O Empat/O Jam/O ,/O Bali/LOCATION Process/O Hasilkan/O Dua/O Dokumen/O https://t.co/tfMJqjjBsz/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Djokovic/PERSON dan/O Kontroversi/O Kesetaraan/O Hadiah/O Uang/O Tenis/O Putra-Putri/O https://t.co/a4ZbUhVzWu/O 
<36>/O Misteri/O sungai/O berwarna/O merah/O seperti/O darah/O terpecahkan/O #Global/O https://t.co/RDQm3WGdbk/O https://t.co/ZfQyHyAXi6/O 
@detikcom/O :/O KPPU/ORGANIZATION Tak/O Sungkan/O Ambil/O Upaya/O Eksekusi/O Paksa/O ke/O Pelaku/O Kartel/O Tarif/O SMS/O https://t.co/YrtnGTEDa8/O 
@detiksport/O :/O Les/ORGANIZATION Bleus/ORGANIZATION Ditunggu/O Laga/O Emosional/O di/O Stade/LOCATION de/LOCATION France/LOCATION https://t.co/sz6vV950U5/O 
@aagym/O :/O RT/O @daarutauhiidBDG/O :/O Kajian/O Tauhiid/O brsama/O @aagym/O https://t.co/yrPQzNgNXd/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Selamat/O datang/O PM/O Hongaria/LOCATION Yang/O Mulia/O Viktor/PERSON Orban/PERSON di/O negeri/O kepulauan/O Indonesia/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@KompasTV/O :/O Jangan/O lewatkan/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O mulai/O hari/O ini/O pukul/O 19/O ./O 30/O WIB/O https://t.co/J4ORme2fj0/O 
@infodishub/O :/O RENSTRA/O 2015-2019/O USUNG/O TIGA/O CIRI/O KHAS/O http://t.co/jl7tL4XqkJ/O #BeritaPusat/O 
<57>/O Petugas/O Dishub/O Dikeroyok/O Saat/O Akan/O Tertibkan/O Bus/O di/O Terminal/LOCATION Pulogadung/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/nYsjzxp6z0/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Terima/O kasih/O kepada/O semua/O kepala/O negara/O sahabat/O yang/O memberi/O dukungan/O bagi/O rakyat/O Indonesia/LOCATION melawan/O terorisme/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
@detiksport/O :/O Soal/O Klub/O Tujuan/O Berikutnya/O ,/O Conte/PERSON Belum/O Ambil/O Keputusan/O https://t.co/c0NUayDF1z/O https://t.co/dBjIQZKjdX/O 
@prabowo/O :/O @puttire/O Terima/O kasih/O ./O 
@Pak_JK/O :/O 1/O ./O Kami/O sepakat/O dengan/O Presiden/O untuk/O menuntaskan/O kasus/O pencatutan/O nama/O Presiden/O dan/O Wapres/O ./O 
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Serap/O aspirasi/O &/O sosialisasi/O RUU/O Kebudayaan/O dlm/O upaya/O perlindungan/O produk/O kebudayaan/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O #Kunker/O #DPR/O https://t.co/9hqqlrJ73E/O 
@jokowi/O :/O Tahukah/O Hari/O Ibu/O yang/O kita/O peringati/O ini/O dimulai/O dengan/O spirit/O melawan/O diskriminasi/O terhadap/O perempuan/O ?/O -/O Jkw/PERSON 
